<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Atlassian Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/atlassian?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Atlassian from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:13:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Web &amp; Visual Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/693dd97a-8cfc-4613-8f4a-be12a5fdefa7</link><description>In a nutshell 
Invisible Technologies is searching for a brand and marketing designer, aka communication artist, to join our team. Candidates for this role must be driven to express what our company can do and why it matters in a wide-variety of mediums for an even wider variety of audiences, while enforcing brand consistency or stepwise evolution at every turn.

This role will not be right for many designers, but its sheer diversity will make this a dream opportunity for a curious, conceptual communication artist who would love to challenge their range without having to start their own business. 

Why is this role important for Invisible Technologies? 
Invisible Technologies offers a novel combination of outsourcing and automation to leaders at fast-growing companies and storied enterprises in more than 20 industries. You’re helping us introduce Invisible, explain a novel offering, and inspire a wide variety of leaders in a way that words alone never could. 

The Role: 
You’ll work closely with the marketing, sales, product, and talent teams to create visual assets that sell our services and inspire people to join our company. 

</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 20:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Technical Lead (Application Engineering)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/efbaff13-ceab-4401-be48-9081b7e597ae</link><description>Invisible Technologies is on a mission to industrialize work by fine-tuning automation and human interaction, powered by our team of Partners and Agents around the world.  We’ve been a globalized, distributed team, since before the pandemic, and we pride ourselves on transparent, effective communication to collaborate and take ownership as needed. 

What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

As a Technical Lead, your job is to write quality code, act with strong ownership, execute on and add to the vision of the engineering team, working with product and wider stakeholders. You will be working on developing Process Builder — our proprietary platform that orchestrates work across an automation engine and a labor marketplace.

Culture

Every engineer should be constantly learning and growing. As an experienced engineer, you should be eager to learn and grow every day. We expect you to raise the bar for performance on the engineering team. 

Our team currently consists of 7 partner engineers and a dozen more agents and interns. The team will double in the coming year — you have an opportunity to mentor and lead.

Execution

The first principle of execution is reliable delivery — you honor your commitments. You should set clear expectations for your deliverables and drive through to success. The formula for success? Say what you’re going to do, do it, and then let everyone know that it’s done.

The second principle of execution is intelligent prioritization. Your job is to put the puzzle pieces together in a sensible, expedient way. We’re not just building a product or a platform. We’re building a company. 

Architecture

We are always striving to build the right thing. You are a key partner for Product, and you’re a critical stakeholder because you know what can be built and what will work. You will focus your energy on one of our core products and act as an owner.

The ideal candidate has learned from experience that technical decisions have far-reaching consequences. As an experienced professional engineer, you are always mindful to avoid technical debt and waste.

Technical Leads are Architects and Leaders

Technical Leads at Invisible are able to follow multiple paths. Some are technical leads of teams and are responsible for people management of those teams. They oversee the technical vision for their area and ensure that there is proper mentorship
Others lead through technical initiatives. Technical Leads oversee broad multi-team technical initiatives and own parts of our software stack (ex. Technical Leads might research and roll out new technical frameworks or might develop a new generation of our UI component.

Whether you're leading people or leading new tech rollouts you'll have a broad team-wide impact.

The Technology

Our platform is TypeScript from top to bottom.

We’re opinionated about modern JavaScript and about the best way to use it. Our stack trends towards the latest and greatest:

We believe that a monorepo with micro frontends is the best approach for us. We’re avid users of NextJS, React, Prisma, Postgres, NX Workspaces, Kubernetes , and tRPC.

We’re always eager to learn and grow and try new technologies.

Requirements

Significant experience developing applications in team environments.
Able to work well with Product Managers to develop technical specifications for large projects with complex scope
Able to research and synthesize new technologies (frameworks, libraries, techniques) and explain and evangelize them to more junior engineers.
Experience using React for front-end development. (We use React, Next.js and Prisma)
Backend language experience including Node, Python (Flask/Django/etc.), Ruby on Rails, Symphony, etc.
Strong understanding of relational databases (MySQL, PostgreSQL, etc.)
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 16:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Strategic Content Developer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/70ba5916-99b0-4689-827a-c22cd9435520</link><description>A sales enablement role that feels like product development. Use discovery and communication superpowers to scale a novel service while earning sales-style incentives

Website | Video Demo | Core Values

The Business Context

Invisible is a strategic partner to fast-growing companies like DoorDash, Klarna, and Canon, helping them create more value at less cost by streamlining operations. For example, they’ve used a blend of outsourcing and automation to help scale up menu production for the delivery industry, to improve the efficiency of claims processing, and to help catalog the world’s contemporary artists. Invisible’s novel approach has been featured in The New Yorker and by ARK Invest. Greycroft-backed, majority-employee owned.

Mission, Success Measures &amp; Ownership

This role sits at the intersection of sales and marketing and its mission is singular: create collateral, campaigns, and content that help a wide variety of prospects and leads sense how Invisible could transform their business.  Success means that, as a result of your content, more sales targets become leads, more leads become opportunities, and more opportunities become happy clients. Your areas of ownership include:

Custom Sales Collateral (40%)
- Curate follow-up materials from the library for key sales calls within 24 hours. 
- Create new decks, case-studies, or explainer videos which are relevant to the audience and which support complex sales, adding them all back to the library. 

Creative Campaign Management (30%)
- Conceive, direct, and execute campaigns which lead to booked meetings with qualified prospects and leads. 
- Work with a designer to create custom ‘contact marketing’ materials for top leads.

A User-Friendly Content Library (30%)
- Own and evolve a content library that makes it easier for sales reps to drive conversion for a wide range of ICPs and which captures sales-call learnings as product-ready insights.
- Grow that library by adding client stories (use cases) to the library on a consistent basis.
- Continuously improve this library’s usability, content quality, and strategic acumen in collaboration with marketing, sales, product, and operations.

Depending on what you want and how you perform, you’ll have the opportunity to become an increasingly strategic individual contributor,  manage more and more of Invisible’s content production, and/or move closer to product marketing. 

We’ll make adjustments to the scope together at the 90 day mark. 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 18:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff Software Engineer (Application Engineer)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/d101d889-1efb-49c5-8344-4b5fd908e62c</link><description>We are actively recruiting for this position and are excited to have the right person join us soon.

Invisible Technologies is on a mission to industrialize work by fine-tuning automation and human interaction, powered by our team of Partners and Agents around the world.  We’ve been a globalized, distributed team, since before the pandemic, and we pride ourselves on transparent, effective communication to collaborate and take ownership as needed. 

What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

As a Staff Software Engineer your job is to write quality code, act with strong ownership, execute on and add to the vision of the engineering team, working with product and wider stakeholders. You will be working on developing Process Builder — our proprietary platform that orchestrates work across an automation engine and a labor marketplace.

Culture

Every engineer should be constantly learning and growing. As an experienced engineer, you should be eager to learn and grow every day. We expect you to raise the bar for performance on the engineering team. 

Our team currently consists of 7 partner engineers and a dozen more agents and interns. The team will double in the coming year — you have an opportunity to mentor and lead.

Execution

The first principle of execution is reliable delivery — you honor your commitments. You should set clear expectations for your deliverables and drive through to success. The formula for success? Say what you’re going to do, do it, and then let everyone know that it’s done.

The second principle of execution is intelligent prioritization. Your job is to put the puzzle pieces together in a sensible, expedient way. We’re not just building a product or a platform. We’re building a company. 

Architecture

We are always striving to build the right thing. You are a key partner for Product, and you’re a critical stakeholder because you know what can be built and what will work. You will focus your energy on one of our core products and act as an owner.

The ideal candidate has learned from experience that technical decisions have far-reaching consequences. As an experienced professional engineer, you are always mindful to avoid technical debt and waste.

Staff Engineers are Architects and Leaders

Staff engineers at Invisible are able to follow multiple paths. Some are technical leads of teams and are responsible for people management of those teams. They oversee the technical vision for their area and ensure that there is proper mentorship
Others lead through technical initiatives. These engineers oversee broad multi-team technical initiatives and own parts of our software stack (ex. Staff engineers might research and roll out new technical frameworks or might develop a new generation of our UI component.

Whether you're leading people or leading new tech rollouts you'll have a broad team-wide impact.

The Technology

Our platform is TypeScript from top to bottom.

We’re opinionated about modern JavaScript and about the best way to use it. Our stack trends towards the latest and greatest:

We believe that a monorepo with micro frontends is the best approach for us. We’re avid users of NextJS, React, Prisma, Postgres, NX Workspaces, Kubernetes , and tRPC.

We’re always eager to learn and grow and try new technologies.

Requirements

Significant experience developing applications in team environments.
Able to work well with Product Managers to develop technical specifications for large projects with complex scope
Able to research and synthesize new technologies (frameworks, libraries, techniques) and explain and evangelize them to more junior engineers.
Experience using React for front-end development. (We use React, Next.js and Prisma)
Backend language experience including Node, Python (Flask/Django/etc.), Ruby on Rails, Symphony, etc.
Strong understanding of relational databases (MySQL, PostgreSQL, etc.)
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 16:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/11ccd951-b7db-4725-b13f-624d6bf53f7e</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position as soon as possible. We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** Once you apply, we will be sending you a questionnaire and engineering test. In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the test and questionnaire. We are also currently receiving a large number of applications, so you may not hear from us immediately. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

What is Invisible?

Website - inv.tech
Blog -  https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo
https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

Who are we?

We are the Invisible’s Technologies Team. We solve problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. How?

We Believe That

Invisible is a world-changing company and the Technologies Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere.
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake.
-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know.
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where

--Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.

Technical Details

Requirements
-- Deep operational understanding and proven experience in functional JavaScript (Typescript) programming
-- Familiarity with our stack, and desire to learn more on the job

Our Stack:
Whenever possible, we use the best tools for the job. Since a lot of what we do is asynchronous, and talking with external APIs, we saw Typescript as a natural fit for most of our stack (though this decision can always be questioned).

-- React.js (functional components + hooks), Apollo Graphql, Next.js
-- Node.js, TypeScript, Postgresql, Redis, Kafka
-- Serverless functions on Vercel

We love open source! We share publicly as much of our code as possible. 
Share your Github/Gitlab/StackOverflow or similar profiles. If you are contributing to an open source projects, proudly flaunt them!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/a8ec8f37-e8f8-41b1-bd4c-f37d86874437</link><description>We are actively recruiting for this position and are excited to have the right person join us soon. 

Invisible Technologies is on a mission to industrialize work by fine-tuning automation and human interaction, powered by our team of Partners and Agents around the world.  We’ve been a globalized, distributed team, since before the pandemic, and we pride ourselves on transparent, effective communication to collaborate and take ownership as needed. 

What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

As a Senior Software Engineer your job is to write quality code, act with strong ownership, execute on and add to the vision of the engineering team, working with product and wider stakeholders. You will be working on developing Process Builder — our proprietary platform that orchestrates work across an automation engine and a labor marketplace.

Culture

Every engineer should be constantly learning and growing. As an experienced engineer, you should be eager to learn and grow every day. We expect you to raise the bar for performance on the engineering team. 

Our team currently consists of 7 partner engineers and a dozen more agents and interns. The team will double in the coming year — you have an opportunity to mentor and lead.

Execution

The first principle of execution is reliable delivery — you honor your commitments. You should set clear expectations for your deliverables and drive through to success. The formula for success? Say what you’re going to do, do it, and then let everyone know that it’s done.

The second principle of execution is intelligent prioritization. Your job is to put the puzzle pieces together in a sensible, expedient way. We’re not just building a product or a platform. We’re building a company. 

Architecture

We are always striving to build the right thing. You are a key partner for Product, and you’re a critical stakeholder because you know what can be built and what will work. You will focus your energy on one of our core products and act as an owner.

The ideal candidate has learned from experience that technical decisions have far-reaching consequences. As an experienced professional engineer, you are always mindful to avoid technical debt and waste.

The Technology

Our platform is TypeScript from top to bottom.

We’re opinionated about modern JavaScript and about the best way to use it. Our stack trends towards the latest and greatest:

We believe that a monorepo with micro frontends is the best approach for us. We’re avid users of NextJS, React, Prisma, Postgres, NX Workspaces , Kubernetes and tRPC.

We’re always eager to learn and grow and try new technologies.

Location

Currently, we are looking to hire for a team that works primarily in US timezones and are preferably seeking out engineering talent in these time zones: 

--  North/South America
--  Europe
--  Africa

Working Schedule

The candidate should be available between 10am to 3pm EDT from Monday to Friday.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 01:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Revenue Ops Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/85d82fe0-0e4a-4b1b-ad4b-cac9aa7bfe55</link><description>Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 


Invisible Technologies helps fast-growing companies scale efficiently, so they can improve margins and capture market share at the same time. We partner with our clients to run their business operations using our modern outsourcing platform to deliver efficiency, quality, and flexibility at scale.

We Believe That:
-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Growth Team is responsible for sourcing, closing, and developing clients until they no longer execute their digital repetitive work themselves  
-- Great client relationships are predicated on trust, sincerity &amp; achievement of the customer’s goals
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake
-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
 
Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where...
-- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.

The Role
The goal of the Growth Analyst (GA) is to support the Head of Growth in scaling Invisible’s revenue engine. Daily responsibilities for a GA vary, but will often entail weekly reporting for leadership, creating analyses to identify bottlenecks, supporting the Head of Growth in managing relations with strategic enterprise partnerships, and monitoring channel ROI + spend. We need a passionate individual eager to play a key role in driving the go-to-market efforts of a fast-growing company that will be the next iconic brand (imagine being one of the first 100 people at Amazon or Google).  
 
The GA role is a center for immense learning. You will be the first Growth Analyst on the team, working heavily with the Head of Growth and key managers on the Growth team, as we sprint towards 3x’ing again in ‘22 as we have in ‘20 and ‘21. 
 
Pairing directly with a senior partner and interacting regularly with various facets of the company (from operations managers to senior management), GAs will receive a frequent and diverse range of experiences, coaching, and opportunities. We envision our best GAs will go on to become Consultants on the Growth team or move on to roles in other teams at the company.

Who We Want
Growth Analysts (GAs) are very flexible, hybrid partners that have a high growth trajectory and can thrive (with proper coaching) in multiple dimensions. This flexibility is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew over 3x for two consecutive years in a row (2020 &amp; 2021) and are on-track to do so again in 2022. We are looking for GAs who can harness both the humble trait of being coachable and the ambitious trait of constantly desiring learning. The spirit animal of a junior GA is a sponge. And, over time, they will evolve with more learning, experience, and responsibility.

There are 3 key areas we will focus on growing the skillset of an GA to prepare them for a promotion to Associate Consultant or another role in the company: Executive Acumen, Project Management &amp; Stakeholder Management. See job description for Associate Consultant for more context on these skills.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 12:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Python Automation Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/e3f21175-7605-4b30-8790-5ddbd97ab3b5</link><description>What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

Invisible is a group of people with a mission to revolutionize knowledge work. We execute our clients' repetitive business processes using a combination of best-in-class automation tools and scalable human intelligence. We call this model work-sharing. Invisible is a world-changing company. The Technology Team is responsible for leading the development of the technology that will fuel Invisible's journey into the stratosphere. 

Team Profile: 

The Automation Team at Invisible solves problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. The problems we solve range from point solutions for specific clients to large-scale long-term platform projects. We automate, scrape, compare, search, utilize APIs, fill forms, and create plugins. 

Our team is responsible for critical work, creating systems that will allow Invisible to continue expanding quickly and to reach our next stage of growth. 

Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
What one of us knows, all of us should know
Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

As we grow and scale as a company, we are looking for talented Python Automation Engineers who can evolve our existing services. Our user base, number of clients, and services are continuously growing, and we want you to be at the forefront of developing, maintaining, and improving our services whilst not compromising on code quality, development culture, and security of our environments.

Job Responsibilities:
Create crawlers for each source URL by using Python modules [scrapy, selenium, requests, BeautifulSoup, and splash]
Create and maintain Scrapy pipelines and middlewares to manage the output from the crawlers. 
Create crawlers for all types of websites irrespective of the technical roadblocks.
Manage the crawlers to overcome technical challenges like IP ban, geolocation ban, captcha, and bot blocking services.
Write SQL queries to manage database operations using Python modules like SQLAlchemy.
Deploy the Python scripts/crawlers in Docker utilizing Kubernetes.

Skills and Qualifications:
Minimum 3+ years of hands-on experience in Python programming.
Strong experience with scraping libraries such as Requests, BeautifulSoup, Selenium, and Scrapy.
Experience with frameworks such as Flask, Django, FastAPI, Tornado, Pandas, etc.
Knowledge of building APIs and services using REST.
Experience with any RDBMS and strong SQL knowledge.
Proficient understanding of code versioning tools like Git, SVN, Bitbucket, etc.
Proficiency in object-oriented design skills.
Troubleshoot issues and solve problems as they arise.
Experience with front-end technologies, such as JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3 would be a plus.
Understanding of fundamental design principles behind a scalable application.
Context switching - able to jump between projects, and priorities.

Preferred Skills and Qualifications:
Knowledge of UI frameworks like Angular/ReactJS.
Knowledge of data engineering platforms such as Airflow.
Familiarity with Google Cloud, Docker, Agile, and Scrum.
Experience with Jira and Confluence would be a plus.
Experience with ETL, Celery, etc.
Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to work with a diverse team.

Compensation:
$1750 - $3500 USD/month DOE - we are a meritocracy - show us what you are worth and we’ll compensate you accordingly.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Manager - Automation</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/02b519a6-3b03-40ee-b07f-bffb15fbbeb6</link><description>What is Invisible?

 Invisible is a group of people with a mission to revolutionize knowledge work. We execute our clients' repetitive business processes using a combination of best-in-class automation tools and scalable human intelligence. We call this model work-sharing. Invisible is a world-changing company. The Technology Team is responsible for leading the development of the technology that will fuel Invisible's journey into the stratosphere.

The Opportunity

We are looking for an Automation Product Manager to lead the planning &amp; delivery of technology projects for our clients. The person will run projects that automate a lifetime's worth of manual work and bring the power of automated work-sharing to millions of people. The role demands great technical depth, a high bar for quality, and bold innovation.

What you'll do

- Manage projects with top-down oversight throughout the entire execution to ensure success as defined by adherence to standards of scope, budget, and timeline.
- Develop comprehensive project plans that merge customer requirements with company goals and coordinate managers and technical personnel during all project phases.
- Monitor project progress continuously and make detailed scheduled reports on measurable items, such as milestones and deliverables.
- Communicate proactively with all involved stakeholders to provide encouragement, identify problems, create solutions, and implement efficiency improvements.
- Make a name for yourself at Invisible as a person who reliably gets amazing things done, and rapidly see your sphere of influence increase.

About You

- You have a fervent desire to automate the world's repetitive work and liberate workers from monotony
- 3+ years of management experience in an IT field, including development work and interactions with customers (required)
- 3+ years experience leading complex client-facing technical projects globally (preferred)
- Experience working with engineering to break down requirements into tasks, estimate effort, and plan sprints
- Create technical requirements to convey your ideas and communicate your solutions to the Engineering team and other stakeholders. 
- Be a thought partner to both Product and Engineering teams, balancing product requirements with engineering scope
- Familiarity with at least 1 modern programming language (even if you don't code regularly)
</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 19:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Principal Software Engineer (Application Engineer)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/f43bedba-a2c3-4c9a-8f34-ebf338a3166a</link><description>We are actively recruiting for this position and are excited to have the right person join us soon.

Invisible Technologies is on a mission to industrialize work by fine-tuning automation and human interaction, powered by our team of Partners and Agents around the world.  We’ve been a globalized, distributed team, since before the pandemic, and we pride ourselves on transparent, effective communication to collaborate and take ownership as needed. 

What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

As a Principal Software Engineer your job is to write quality code, act with strong ownership, execute on and add to the vision of the engineering team, working with product and wider stakeholders. You will be working on developing Process Builder — our proprietary platform that orchestrates work across an automation engine and a labor marketplace.

Culture

Every engineer should be constantly learning and growing. As an experienced engineer, you should be eager to learn and grow every day. We expect you to raise the bar for performance on the engineering team. 

Our team currently consists of 7 partner engineers and a dozen more agents and interns. The team will double in the coming year — you have an opportunity to mentor and lead.

Execution

The first principle of execution is reliable delivery — you honor your commitments. You should set clear expectations for your deliverables and drive through to success. The formula for success? Say what you’re going to do, do it, and then let everyone know that it’s done.

The second principle of execution is intelligent prioritization. Your job is to put the puzzle pieces together in a sensible, expedient way. We’re not just building a product or a platform. We’re building a company. 

Architecture

We are always striving to build the right thing. You are a key partner for Product, and you’re a critical stakeholder because you know what can be built and what will work. You will focus your energy on one of our core products and act as an owner.

The ideal candidate has learned from experience that technical decisions have far-reaching consequences. As an experienced professional engineer, you are always mindful to avoid technical debt and waste.

Principals are Architects and Leaders

Principal engineers at Invisible are able to follow multiple paths. Some of our Principal engineers are technical leads of teams and are responsible for people management of those teams. They oversee the technical vision for their area and ensure that there is proper mentorship
Other principal engineers lead through technical initiatives. These engineers oversee broad multi team technical initiatives and own parts of our software stack (ex. Principal engineers might research and roll out new technical frameworks or might develop a new generation of our UI component.

Whether you're leading people or leading new tech rollouts you'll have broad team wide impact.

The Technology

Our platform is TypeScript from top to bottom.

We’re opinionated about modern JavaScript and about the best way to use it. Our stack trends towards the latest and greatest:

We believe that a monorepo with micro frontends is the best approach for us. We’re avid users of NextJS, React, Prisma, Postgres, NX Workspaces , Kubernetes and tRPC.


We’re always eager to learn and grow and try new technologies.

Location

Currently we are looking to hire for a team that works primarily in US timezones and are seeking out engineering talent in these timezones:

--  North/South America
-- Europe
-- Africa

Working Schedule

The candidate should be available between 10am to 3pm EDT from Monday to Friday.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 14:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Relations Partner</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/ea7c75f3-c378-455a-a100-f4cd661339c0</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position as soon as possible. We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. 

Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. We will start interviewing immediately, so please be sure to complete the questionnaire, as it will lag the process if it is not complete. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

THIS IS A FULL TIME REMOTE POSITION

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck: - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values: https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

Who are we?
We are Invisible’s People Team. We believe that People are our #1 Competitive Strategy. We create an environment where business performance, growth, and scale can be accomplished with the least amount of friction and is sustainable long term. Our mission is to seek out, recruit, retain and develop top-notch talent for our Partner, Specialist, and Agent workforce.
We are building an aligned talent mindset, every one of us at Invisible is a Growth Partner.. We embrace change: the ceiling is the new floor! We focus on Culture and Sustainability, and we like to “Keep it Weird” at Invisible!

</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 19:04:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Data Analytics Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/962d4b07-a8ad-460d-af79-7f67bdcc93e7</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position as soon as possible. We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. We will start interviewing immediately, so please be sure to complete the questionnaire, as it will lag the process if it is not complete. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

THIS IS A FULL-TIME REMOTE POSITION

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck: - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values: https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d

Who are we?
We are Invisible’s People Team. We believe that People are our #1 Competitive Strategy. We create an environment where business performance, growth, and scale can be accomplished with the least amount of friction and is sustainable in the long term... Our mission is to seek out, recruit, retain and develop top-notch talent for our Partner, Specialist, and Agent workforce.
We are building an aligned talent mindset, every one of us at Invisible is a Growth Partner. We embrace change: the ceiling is the new floor! We focus on Culture and Sustainability, and we like to “Keep it Weird” at Invisible!

</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 19:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Operations Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/a2fd214b-a4a8-40b1-b18b-0844c05b5506</link><description>We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. 
Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d


Who are we?
We’re Invisible’s Operations Team. We strive to create world-class outcomes for our clients as a strategic partner. 

We Believe That:
-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Who We Want
-- Trainers who love to teach and create training material. Fast.
-- Polymaths and independent thinkers
-- Someone who is unlike anyone else on the team

The Mission
The goal of an Operations Delivery Manager (DM) at Invisible is to ensure that clients under his or her charge receive world-class operational service: high-quality results delivered quickly, within budget, customized to the client’s needs. To achieve this, a DM manages a team of agents who produce these deliverables. In addition to managing their team, DMs work directly with their clients to identify goals, map out processes, measure quality, measure impact, and move the client’s business forward. As clients grow with us, DMs also drive platform and point automations on behalf of their clients in partnership with our Product &amp; Engineering teams to ensure we operationally become better, faster, and cheaper.

Who We Want
Operations Delivery Managers are very flexible, hybrid partners that excel in multiple dimensions. This flexibility is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew over 3x for two consecutive years in a row (2020 &amp; 2021) and plan to do so again in 2022. There are  3 critical spikes in capabilities that we look for in this role. The best DMs are strong across all 3 dimensions, though they all spike in Operational Management, the most critical to their role. A DM who spikes in only 1 will fail in the role out of the gate; a DM who spikes in only 2 will likely succeed in the medium-term but will likely not scale with the business. Thus, we are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 22:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Operations Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/a934a35d-0b29-4201-a9a6-82ffe5b62a13</link><description>Invisible Technologies helps fast-growing companies scale efficiently, so they can improve margins and capture market share at the same time. We partner with our clients to run their business operations using our modern outsourcing platform to deliver efficiency, quality, and flexibility at scale.

Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck: https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI

We believe that…

Mission. Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere.
Ownership. Every partner on the team is the “CEO” of their area - each of us are empowered  to jump in and solve the problems in front of us.
Communication. Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
Transparency. What one of us knows, all of us should know.
Self-Improvement. Every new mistake is a learning opportunity.
Meritocracy. The value someone produces should be reflected back in the position of responsibility and compensation that they receive.

The Role

The goal of an Operations Analyst (OA) is to unlock efficiencies and quality improvements in our operations through analysis, process design, and project management. OAs are paired with Operations Directors and serve as an extra pair of eyes, ears, hands, and brain —  a catalyst for the Director to achieve their department’s overall objectives. Daily responsibilities for an OA vary, but often times include efficiency &amp; quality analyses on process work, financial analyses on different areas of our operations, project management of certain client work, and process design improvement work on important client or internal processes.

The life of an OA is a difficult one, one where a persevering work ethic needs to be paired with an active, creative mind. That said, the OA role is a center for immense learning. Pairing directly with a senior partner and interacting regularly with various facets of the company (from individual agent operators to product managers), OAs will receive a frequent and diverse range of experiences, coaching, and opportunities. Our best OAs go on to become Operations Managers or move on to related roles in other teams at the company.

Who We Want

Operations Analysts (OAs) are very flexible, hybrid partners that have a high growth trajectory and can thrive (with proper coaching) in multiple dimensions. This flexibility is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew over 3x for two consecutive years in a row (2020 &amp; 2021) and plan to do so again in 2022. We are looking for OAs who can harness both the humble trait of being coachable and the ambitious trait of constantly desiring learning. The spirit animal of a junior OA is a sponge. And, over time, they will evolve with more learning, experience, and responsibility.

There are 3 key areas we will focus on growing the skillset of an OA to prepare them for a promotion to Operation Manager: Operations Management, Client Management, &amp; Product Ownership. See job description for Operations Manager for more context on these skills.

Compensation &amp; Benefits

Working Times: US (EST or PST) Hours
2022: $60,000 annual OTE (base + bonus) + equity!
Additional opportunities to earn more equity and increase your ownership percentage of the company, through promotions and through re-distribution of re-acquired shares via buybacks.
Healthcare Benefits (or Stipend Option)
Flexible Work Schedule / Unlimited Vacation Days
Work Remotely
</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 15:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Growth Consultant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/7a420a1a-6d44-43d4-a0b3-bc693088c420</link><description>We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. We will start interviewing immediately, so please be sure to complete the questionnaire, as it will lag the process if it is not complete. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon! THIS IS A FULL-TIME REMOTE POSITION
 
What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 

 
Who are we?

We’re Invisible’s Growth Team. We are an irreplaceable strategic growth partner for the world's fastest-growing &amp; most innovative companies, powering their digital workflows so they can focus on building their businesses - not running them.  
 
The Job

Reporting to the Head of Sales, you will be responsible for closing clients and generating your own leads. This is a role for someone looking to join a fast-growing sales team. We’re looking for true leaders and sales professionals. We need a passionate individual eager to play a key role in driving the go-to-market efforts of a fast-growing company that will be the next iconic brand (imagine being one of the first 100 people at Amazon or Google). The goal of a Growth Consultant is to help enable Invisible’s mission to automate repetitive work for every company so people can focus on their real work. You will be responsible for leading a Sales team to hit monthly targets, build pipeline, and play a key role in helping us grow 3x again in 2022.
 
Who We Want

Growth Consultants are the foundation of our team. Our ability to achieve our goals comes down, in large part, to the type and number of clients you add. Our GAs represent expert engagement layered on top of product-led process discovery. GAs will work with the Customer Success, Operations &amp; Product teams to ensure clients under his or her charge receive world-class operational service: high-quality results delivered quickly, within budget, customized to the client’s needs. We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. The ideal candidate is a blend of 3 key strengths: 
 
- Consultative Selling (Customer-Centric): Ability to work with multiple internal stakeholders at a midmarket company to bring a sale from concept to across the finish line. Strong business acumen to identify cross-functional business needs and anchor Invisible’s solution to multiple teams.

- Hunter-Mentality: The right candidate will proactively build and manage their pipeline to exceed their monthly, quarterly &amp; annual targets while closing good-fit clients. Whether things are going well or not as well, the right candidate will find a way to win. 

-Executive Presence: Strong gravitas the ability to sell to VP-level and C-level executives within midmarket companies. Strong relationship-building skills. 
 
This ‘consultative-selling’ is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew 3x in 2020, 4x in 2021, and plan to grow rapidly by 3x again in 2022.  We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. 



</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 12:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Stack Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/214f6779-872c-43c0-a56c-ac3221d6377c</link><description>We are currently looking to fill multiple positions asap. We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. 
Note** Once you apply, you will receive a questionnaire and engineering test. In order to be considered for this position, we must receive your completed test and questionnaire answers before you will be moved to the interview round. We are also currently receiving many applications, so you may not hear from us immediately. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch.

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck -https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI

Who are we?
We are Invisible’s Technologies Team. We solve problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. How?

We Believe That
-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Technologies Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake
-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where
-- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.

What is it like to be on the Engineering team?
Invisible is a meritocracy and a startup. There’s plenty of responsibilities to go around. You’ll be expected to absorb responsibilities whenever you see them and figure out how to abstract yourself away from the job—be your own mini-CEO. Our team is small, but growing quickly. The work you do will directly impact how successful we are as a company. You’ll also have the opportunity to be part of the product development. Our product work is done by squads: product manager, designers, customers, and an engineer like you, focused on solving a customer problem. Together, your squad will have the autonomy to own key parts of our roadmap and build the things that will have the greatest impact on solving customer problems.

What you'll do:
As an engineer on our CX team, you'll be responsible for scoping and delivering high-impact product features that define the experience our customers have with our technology. This is an exciting role with a lot of visibility to our user base.

Our Stack:
We move rapidly and our tech stack changes often as we scale. Here's a brief list of some of our current stack in the CX space:

Frontend: React, Typescript, GraphQL, React-Query, NextJS, Storybook
Backend: PostgreSQL, Prisma, Nexus

Compensation
--  $2000-$4000 USD per month DOE - we are a meritocracy - show us what you are worth and we’ll compensate you accordingly.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance Reporting Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/3e0f291e-c2ae-467a-a4f0-5d0061266dc5</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position ASAP.

What is Invisible?
Website 
Blog 
Strategy Blog 
Overview / Sales Deck
Recorded Demo
Meet Invisible

Who are we
We are Invisible’s Finance Team. We solve problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. 

We Believe That
- Invisible is a world-changing company 
- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
- What one of us knows, all of us should know
- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where
- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all
- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team
- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source


The right person already called me and told me these words: I know numbers. I love them and they love me.  I live for finding the lines that aren’t exactly lining up in the financial statements.  I find problems, I fix them and feel very satisfied with a tremendously valuable, perhaps a little tedious,  job well done. I can respond to emails in my sleep and take little joy in perfectly aligned reports. I am detail oriented, contentious, and trustworthy.  I’m a team player but don’t mind working independently.  I am reliable and will make my supervisor breathe a huge sigh of relief when they see an email from me stating, “don’t worry. I’ve got this one.”  I know the value of steadfastness and kindness, standing by your teammates, and providing excellent service to my customers. My work is flawless and I’m very proud of that fact.  At the end of the day, I’ll know that Invisible will be dramatically improved by my modest, but essential, contribution.  I will take great pride in the work we do at Invisible. I’ll know, without my efforts, the company couldn’t function and continue to grow into an unstoppable, paradigm-altering force.  
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 21:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Recruiting</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/d3eb57b6-f1f6-4b9b-8426-7ff10bb3eac5</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position as soon as possible! We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 

Who are we?

We’re Invisible’s Hiring Team. We aim to provide measurable business impact and leverage across all teams of the organization. Our Hiring team's mission is to seek out, recruit and retain top-notch talent for both our Partner and Agent workforce. Scale is our North Star. 

We Believe That:

-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Executive Team is responsible for leading the charge. 
-- We expect excellence from ourselves and hold ourselves to a high bar. 
-- We lead by example.
-- People are the foundation of success, but without proper systems and process, even the best people will fail. 
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity. 

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where...

-- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.


What You Will be Doing

-- Manage the Partner &amp; Specialist Recruiting efforts.
-- You need to be able to think both strategically and tactically to qualify for a Director level position and not just a Recruiting Manager role. 
-- Manage and oversee sourcing efforts and not be afraid to get your hands dirty sourcing yourself.
-- Be a domain expert, what are the latest trends in hiring? How and why are they applicable to us? What is the implementation ROI? How does it get the best people to fit our needs?
-- Shoot for the stars in creating a talent brand so strong, the perfect candidates come to us en mass, dreaming of working here.
-- Commitment to excellence who will drive the team to hold the same bar
-- Systems oriented and able to create, document and roll out process but able to be flexible and play basketball (not baseball)

Who We Want

-- "Intrapreneurs"
-- Polymaths and independent thinkers
-- A hunter mindset, that treats Recruiting as a sales function.
-- Someone who is unlike anyone else on the team, someone who has the confidence to state "Without me as a partner, you would not be able to hire the best in class, at the speed needed, to keep up with our growth".
-- Proactive attitude, outcomes mindset: A great Director of Recruiting will seek out creative solutions to the most challenging hiring problems and proactively attack them - always focusing on business outcomes.
-- Doers, not just thinkers: A great Director of Recruiting will direct their team to own the success of incoming talent and make recommendations to the process, but also can roll up their sleeves and burn the midnight oil recruiting excellent talent.
-- Stellar communicator: In a remote culture, communication is everything. A great Director of Recruiting ensure their stakeholders are always kept up-to-date on the current issues and are always in sync with the current and future plays.
-- Ownership Mentality: Our Director of Recruiting  will see every problem the business is facing as their own personal mission to solve through recruiting and retaining excellent talent. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Operations - AI Training</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/948c6969-552f-4dc6-9c62-32dca9d259dc</link><description>Who we are
Invisible Technologies helps fast-growing companies scale efficiently, so they can improve margins and capture market share at the same time. We partner with our clients to run their business operations using our modern outsourcing platform to deliver efficiency, quality, and flexibility at scale.


Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck: https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI

We believe that…
Mission. Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere.
Ownership. Every partner on the team is the “CEO” of their area - each of us are empowered  to jump in and solve the problems in front of us.
Communication. Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
Transparency. What one of us knows, all of us should know.
Self-Improvement. Every new mistake is a learning opportunity.
Meritocracy. The value someone produces should be reflected back in the position of responsibility and compensation that they receive.

What you will be doing
You will be on the cutting edge of training artificial intelligence (AI) systems by managing a team of over 100 AI trainers and supporting and strategizing with the global leaders in AI development.

Reporting to the VP of Operations, you will be ensuring your clients in the AI space receive world-class service through strategic partnership, high-quality results, and constant improvement.

To achieve this, your direct reports will include a team of operations managers and analysts and your indirect reports (reporting to operations managers) will be a team of over 100 AI trainers who have been hand-selected and coached to train AI systems for our clients.

In addition to managing your team and clients, you work with other Invisible senior leaders to identify company goals, create and map out new processes, measure quality, measure impact, and move Invisible forward.
 - Operations Management: Managing a team of several Operations Managers and Operations Analysts as they manage the production of high-quality work efficiently, on time, and within budget.
 - Client Management: Partnering with a small set of clients at both the strategic and tactical level, working with them to define their needs, map their processes, and ensure the target hits the mark.
 - Product Ownership: Pairing with an Invisible Product Manager to upgrade our platform to better achieve client goals. An ability to “speak Product” and think in systems is essential to individual and company success.

Who we want
A Director of Operations is a very tech-savvy and flexible partner that excels in multiple dimensions. This flexibility is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew over 3x for two consecutive years in a row (2020 &amp; 2021) and plan to do so again in 2022.
 
There are 3 critical skills and capabilities that we look for in this role:
1)     The best Directors are strong, creative technical project managers who understand how to lead, motivate, and manage a global team (experience with international freelancers is ideal).
2)     You must be a client-facing leader. This role requires high-level strategic interaction with some of the largest and most well-known companies in the world as you help them solve complex technical problems. Have you led a client-facing team before?
3)     You’ll be one of the first 100 employees at a company that’s changing the way humans do business every day, a company that will be a household name very soon. The expectation is that you’re a highly entrepreneurial and innovative leader and thinker capable of seeing the future.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Operations</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/b19982c3-b5d1-4f1a-9e27-a7405201356b</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position as soon as possible! We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon!

What is Invisible?
Website: http://www.inv.tech/
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 
 
Who are we?
We’re Invisible’s Operations Team. We strive to create world-class outcomes for our clients as a strategic partner. 

We Believe That:
-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity
 
What You Will Be Doing: 
Reporting to the VP of Ops, a Director of Operations at Invisible ensures that clients under his or her charge receive world-class service: high-quality results delivered quickly, within budget, customized to the client’s needs. To achieve this, the Director manages a team of Operations Managers who in turn manage a large international team of agents (global freelance workers) who produce these complex and highly technical deliverables. In addition to managing their team, Directors work with other Invisible senior leaders to identify company goals, create and map out new processes, measure quality, measure impact, and move Invisible forward.

o   Technical Operations Management: Managing a team of 2-3 Operations Managers as they perform high-quality work efficiently, on time, and within budget. 
o   Client Management: Partnering with 20 - 30 high-growth businesses at both the strategic and tactical level. Working with them to define their needs, map their processes, and ensure the target hits the mark.
o   Product Ownership: Each operations teams pairs with an Invisible Product Manager to develop the platform to better achieve client goals. An ability to “speak Product” and think in systems is essential to individual and company success.

Who We Want
A Director of Operations is a very tech-savvy and flexible partner that excels in multiple dimensions. This flexibility is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew over 3x for two consecutive years in a row (2020 &amp; 2021) and plan to do so again in 2022. 
 
There are 3 critical skills and capabilities that we look for in this role: 
1)     The best Directors are strong, creative technical project managers who understand how to lead, motivate, and manage a global team (experience with international freelancers is ideal). 
2)     You MUST be an experienced technical client-facing leader. This role requires high-level strategic interaction with some of the largest and most well-known companies in the world as you help them solve complex technical problems. Have you led a client-facing team before? 
3)     You’ll be one of the first 100 employees at a company that’s changing the way humans do business every day, a company that will be a household name very soon. The expectation is that you’re a highly entrepreneurial and innovative leader and thinker capable of seeing the future, or at least seeing opportunities for growth and efficiency early. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 19:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Commercial Sales</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/a9c081cc-cabd-4c49-864a-82e779ff657d</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position by June 1st 2022. We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. We will start interviewing immediately, so please be sure to complete the questionnaire, as it will lag the process if it is not complete. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon! THIS IS A FULL-TIME REMOTE POSITION
 
What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 
 
Who are we?

We’re Invisible’s Growth Team. We are an irreplaceable strategic growth partner for the world's fastest growing &amp; most innovative companies, powering their digital workflows so they can focus on building their businesses - not running them.  
 
The Job

Reporting to the Head of Sales, you will be managing our Commercial Sales team. This is a role for someone looking to manage and build a fast-growing sales team, we’re looking for a builder...a true creative leader. We need a passionate individual eager to play a key role in driving the go-to-market efforts of a fast-growing company that will be the next iconic brand (imagine being the first Sales Manager at Amazon or Google). The goal of the Sales Manager is to help enable Invisible’s mission to automate repetitive work for every company so people can focus on their real work. You will be responsible for leading a Sales team to hit monthly targets, building pipeline, and building the processes to allow sellers to focus on selling and play a key role in helping us grow 3x again in 2022.
 
Who We Want

The Sales Manager is the tip-of-the-spear for our Growth team. Our ability to achieve our goals comes down, in large part, to the type and number of clients you add. We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. The ideal candidate is a blend of 3 key strengths: 
 
1) You have demonstrated success building-and-running an inside sales teams - both AEs and SDRs - selling at a $100k-$500k ACV

2) You have experience in complex sales and consultative selling methodologies, you're a competitive leader always looking for creative ways to sell. 

3) Executive Presence: You have a strong presence, inspiring confidence in both your team and prospects a like. You have strong relationship-building skills, and a demonstrated ability to sell to VP- &amp; C-level executives within midmarket companies.
 
Previous experience in sales teams is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew 3x in 2020, 4x in 2021, and plan to grow rapidly by 3x again in 2022.  We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. 
 
Capabilities &amp; Requirements: 

Capabilities &amp; Requirements: 
3-5 years of experience B2B selling as an inside sales rep or to midmarket accounts
3-5 years as a manager scaling B2B inside or mid-market sales team in a SaaS, BPO, or high-growth organization with a headcount of at least 6 reps
Experience with direct management of outbound lead generation programs
Experience building and training account executives and business development representatives
Work with Operations to ensure clients successfully activate within their first 30-days after close
Help the team to identify target accounts and prospects, and effectively be able to pitch Invisible’s solutions to set appointments with qualified prospects 
Analyze data to identify trends and communicate appropriately to senior management
Passion for training, motivating, and coaching in a fast-growth environment
Have a deep understanding of how to leverage and implement a multi-pronged approach (calls, emails, Linkedin, Direct Mail, social selling, and more)
 
 
We Believe That:

-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Growth Team is responsible for sourcing, closing, and developing clients until they no longer execute their digital repetitive work themselves  
-- Great client relationships are predicated on trust, sincerity &amp; achievement of the customer’s goals
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake
-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
 
Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where...

-- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.
 

</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BPO Consultant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/1aeff7fe-4018-48fd-97c5-539c002b5f49</link><description>We'd like to ask you a few questions to jump-start the process and get to know you a bit. Note** In order to be considered, you must submit your completed answers to the questionnaire. We will start interviewing immediately, so please be sure to complete the questionnaire, as it will lag the process if it is not complete. Good luck with the hiring process and we'll be in touch soon! THIS IS A FULL-TIME REMOTE POSITION
 
What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/a8tthk8bwi9dbhk6
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values - https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 

 
Who are we?

We’re Invisible’s Growth Team. We are an irreplaceable strategic growth partner for the world's fastest-growing &amp; most innovative companies, powering their digital workflows so they can focus on building their businesses - not running them.  
 
The Job

Reporting to the Head of Sales, you will be responsible for closing clients and generating your own leads. This is a role for someone looking to join a fast-growing sales team. We’re looking for true leaders and sales professionals. We need a passionate individual eager to play a key role in driving the go-to-market efforts of a fast-growing company that will be the next iconic brand (imagine being one of the first 100 people at Amazon or Google). The goal of the BPO Consultant is to help enable Invisible’s mission to automate repetitive work for every company so people can focus on their real work. You will be responsible for leading a Sales team to hit monthly targets, build pipeline, and play a key role in helping us grow 3x again in 2022.
 
Who We Want

BPO Consultants are the foundation of our team. Our ability to achieve our goals comes down, in large part, to the type and number of clients you add. Our GAs represent expert engagement layered on top of product-led process discovery. GAs will work with the Customer Success, Operations &amp; Product teams to ensure clients under his or her charge receive world-class operational service: high-quality results delivered quickly, within budget, customized to the client’s needs. We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. The ideal candidate is a blend of 3 key strengths: 
 
- Consultative Selling (Customer-Centric): Ability to work with multiple internal stakeholders at a midmarket company to bring a sale from concept to across the finish line. Strong business acumen to identify cross-functional business needs and anchor Invisible’s solution to multiple teams.

- Hunter-Mentality: The right candidate will proactively build and manage their pipeline to exceed their monthly, quarterly &amp; annual targets while closing good-fit clients. Whether things are going well or not as well, the right candidate will find a way to win. 

-Executive Presence: Strong gravitas the ability to sell to VP-level and C-level executives within midmarket companies. Strong relationship-building skills. 
 
This ‘consultative-selling’ is key to continuing our high growth trajectory: we grew 3x in 2020, 4x in 2021, and plan to grow rapidly by 3x again in 2022.  We are looking for individuals with the full spectrum of abilities and we are extremely selective. 



</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Data Trainer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/98e88f07-713d-4766-a1ca-576a548331da</link><description>What is Invisible

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values: https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 


Who We Are
Invisible Technologies helps fast-growing companies scale efficiently, so they can improve margins and capture market share at the same time. We partner with our clients to run their business operations using our modern outsourcing platform to deliver efficiency, quality, and flexibility at scale.

This role will be the primary tool in developing an AI model, and that candidate must operate with respect for the position and command the responsibilities within each project. The candidate must execute high-level work within a defined grading rubric or risk replacement. 

This position will be a summer internship with an opportunity to develop into a full-time job upon project completion. The AI training model offers a multitude of projects with a continuous timeline for ongoing development. 

We Believe That
* Mission. Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere.
* Ownership. Every partner on the team is the “CEO” of their area - each of us are empowered  to jump in and solve the problems in front of us.
* Communication. Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
* Transparency. What one of us knows, all of us should know.
* Self-Improvement. Every new mistake is a learning opportunity.
* Meritocracy. The value someone produces should be reflected back in the position of responsibility and compensation that they receive.

Who We Want
The AI Data Trainer role is ideally targeted towards academically inclined, native English-speaking collegiate students; Data Labelers must be responsible and possess a strong work ethic, schedules are flexible within US working hours but some projects could have more strict requirements. Ideal Data Labelers are passionate about organising data sets, researching and synthesising data, and responding to prompts based on abstract concepts and other similar traits; successful applicants likely have a background working on projects that require labeling sets of data by following procedures and guides. Access to a personal computer strong internet connection advanced analytical skills advanced writing skills.

About the Role
This role is focused around providing accurate data by labeling AI-generated prompts and generating high-quality responses for prompts covering general topics. A successful candidate is able to follow detailed instructions that direct the way each section of the process should be executed. Candidates must execute high-level work within a defined grading rubric and be able to upgrade and improve in a fast-paced environment. 

What you will be doing
The goal of an AI Data Trainer is to help train and develop AI systems through model interaction, interpretation of prompts, researching topics, evaluating use cases, and dictating best results. The AI Data Labeler will work closely with our operations team to execute multiple projects within a defined scope and deliver results on a predetermined timeline. This role works closely with operations to provide up-to-date feedback and review of the system models through analytical reporting and presentations. 
 
Candidates must possess the following:
* Access to a personal computer
* Strong internet connection
* Advanced analytical skills
* Advanced writing/spoken English skills

Other details :
*Candidates should be ready to work under deadline pressure and manage multiple projects
*Candidates should be organized and their work should be aligned with defined guidelines through the different steps. 

Job Type: Contract, 20-40 hours per week dependent on volume.

Required language: English
</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 13:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Agent Operator : General Application</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/7335d0e5-5eca-4375-81d3-55f4454f3b85</link><description>What is Invisible?

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Recorded Demo: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI

Who are we?

We are Invisible’s Operation Team. We solve problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. How?

We Believe That
-- Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operation Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere
-- Exponential gains from systems &gt; Short term linear work &gt; Systems for system's sake
-- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
-- What one of us knows, all of us should know
-- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where

-- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all.
-- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team.
-- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source.

What is an Agent?

An Agent is a member of Invisible’s elite workforce.

Who are the Agents?
Invisible’s agents are an international group of passionate, restless humans striving to constantly grow, learn, and build a better future for themselves and the world.

An agent is… 
— a father in the Philippines, providing for his whole family. 
— a college student in Kenya, searching for a bright future. 
— a stay-at-home mom in Texas, desiring to learn but constrained at home. 
— a high school student in Ohio, frustrated by a dysfunctional school system. 
— a bachelor in Poland, seeking to both work and learn.
An agent is you.

What do Operators do?
The Operator is the starting position of Invisible’s Agents. Operators are the frontline of the Digital Assembly Line. As its name implies, the operator operates. They are the infantry that makes up most of our workforce, doing work for clients, executing Process instructions, and organizing data.

Operates processes.
An operator reads the instructions of a process and operates them to accomplish work for a client.
- Example: an operator will read these instructions (screenshot) to send a legal agreement. 

Assigned to a prime.
A prime is a group of processes. An operator is assigned to a Prime, or a series of primes, to gain expertise in related processes. In a prime, an operator will interact closely with the Manager and other operators of that prime.
- Example: an operator assigned to the Calendar prime will do processes like “Scheduling a Meeting”, “Sending a Reminder”, “Sending a Daily Agenda”, etc.

Communicates with clients.
An operator will communicate to the client according to the instructions of a process. Much of this communication is templated in a process, but it will stray from the instructions from time-to-time and the operator will need to create a unique response. When communicating to a client, an operator will have to write in the voice of the client’s synthetic Assistant, and not in the operator’s own voice.
- Example: John Keats is the assistant for client Francis Pedraza. When responding to Francis, the operator will have to be communicating in the voice of John Keats.

Gives feedback.
An operator gives feedback on process instructions to other agents, who upgrades the process based on that feedback. This feedback can be proactive from the operator seeing potential improvements, or reactive from the operator making an implicit mistake that can be avoided with clearer instructions.
- Proactive Example: an operator realizes that two steps involving navigating a website can be consolidated into one step, with a link leading to the desired destination. The operator will give the builder constructive feedback and offer a suggestion on how to upgrade the process.
- Reactive Example: an operator uses the wrong format to name a calendar event, but it was never stated to use that format in the process. The operator will then let the builder know of this mistake and offer a suggestion on how to upgrade the process.

Tracks time.
An operator tracks the time it takes for them to operate an instance of a specific process. 

Tracks work.
An operator tracks every instance of process operation for a specific client in the client’s dashboard—located in a Google Sheet. The operator also logs any mistake they make and any preference the client sets.
- Example: an operator will track the name of the prime, process, and specific instance, along with start and end dates, and the minutes it took to complete the instance.

*This position is constantly monitored for new applicants and a member of our hiring team will reach out once there is a new project available. This may take some time, however, once a project begins we will reach out to you to begin the hiring process.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Advanced AI Data Trainer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/d702ee49-7b8f-401d-b62e-25648b16fdb3</link><description>What is Invisible

Website : http://www.inv.tech/
Blog: https://inv.tech/blog
Overview / Sales Deck - https://invtech.docsend.com/view/6kp3ixp
Recorded Demo - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4135pGQh8yvHRwKatYrMDuKL7ODHBXHI
Core Values: https://www.notion.so/invisibletech/d8add47d17584715a62aa4d46f0270b8?v=187ce27ec02f4bfaa2aed9f3f2c6ad6d 


Who We Are
Invisible Technologies helps fast-growing companies scale efficiently, so they can improve margins and capture market share at the same time. We partner with our clients to run their business operations using our modern outsourcing platform to deliver efficiency, quality, and flexibility at scale.

This role will be the primary tool in developing an AI model, and that candidate must operate with respect for the position and command the responsibilities within each project. The candidate must execute high-level work within a defined grading rubric or risk replacement. 

This position will be a summer internship with an opportunity to develop into a full-time job upon project completion. The AI training model offers a multitude of projects with a continuous timeline for ongoing development. 

We Believe That
* Mission. Invisible is a world-changing company and the Operations Team is responsible for creating the systems that will launch Invisible into the stratosphere.
* Ownership. Every partner on the team is the “CEO” of their area - each of us are empowered  to jump in and solve the problems in front of us.
* Communication. Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better.
* Transparency. What one of us knows, all of us should know.
* Self-Improvement. Every new mistake is a learning opportunity.
* Meritocracy. The value someone produces should be reflected back in the position of responsibility and compensation that they receive.

Who We Want
Natural Language Processing Specialist is academically inclined, native English-speaking collegiate students. Natural Language Processing Specialists must be responsible and possess a strong work ethic and a flexible schedule willing to accept a fixed working schedule based on their availability. 

Candidates are expected to be in good academic standing and actively enrolled in collegiate studies.

What you will be doing
- Evaluate AI performance and redirect AI output
- Interpret data for accuracy
- Research and cite information in academic formats based on a given topic
- Draft responses to improve AI model function
- Generate topics for AI training 
- Review past output and provide evaluations
 
Candidates must possess the following:

* Access to a personal computer
* Strong internet connection
* Advanced analytical skills
* Advanced writing skills

Other details :

* You should have the ability to work under deadline pressure and manage multiple projects
* You must organize all projects in folders for easy searching
* Ability to grow and earn more responsibility and salary

Job Type: Contract, 20-40 hours per week dependent on volume.

Required language: English
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Accounting Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/invisible/21821ac7-d915-41d1-97fc-5c466f115d3c</link><description>We are currently looking to fill this position ASAP.

What is Invisible?

Website 
Blog 
Strategy Blog 
Overview / Sales Deck
Recorded Demo
Meet Invisible

Who are we
We are Invisible’s Finance Team. We solve problems at scale so they never happen again. At our best, we solve problems before they happen. 

We Believe That
- Invisible is a world-changing company 
- Consistent feedback is key - we are addicted to learning and getting better
- What one of us knows, all of us should know
- Every new mistake is a learning opportunity

Because of these beliefs, we’ve built a team where
- Distributed approaches and centralized intelligence merge. Each teammate is constantly innovating and trying something new. Every mistake is prevented by all. Every success is learned by all
- Each of us contains the sum of the knowledge, intelligence, and creativity of our entire team
- We evolve and mutate constantly like an organism, identifying successful and problematic tactics and incorporating ideas from any source

The right person already called me and told me these words: I know numbers. I love them and they love me.  I live for finding the lines that aren’t exactly lining up in the financial statements.  I find problems, I fix them and feel very satisfied with a tremendously valuable, perhaps a little tedious,  job well done. I can respond to emails in my sleep and take little joy in perfectly aligned reports. I am detail oriented, contentious, and trustworthy.  I’m a team player but don’t mind working independently.  I am reliable and will make my supervisor breathe a huge sigh of relief when they see an email from me stating, “don’t worry. I’ve got this one.”  

I know the value of steadfastness and kindness, standing by your teammates, and providing excellent service to my customers. My work is flawless and I’m very proud of that fact.  At the end of the day, I’ll know that Invisible will be dramatically improved by my modest, but essential, contribution.  I will take great pride in the work we do at Invisible. I’ll know, without my efforts, the company couldn’t function and continue to grow into an unstoppable, paradigm-altering force.  

</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 18:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>