<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Canva Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/canva?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Canva from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Senior Product Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/10359940-4672-4fbe-beaa-6e52f6ba2a41</link><description>We’re looking for a Senior Product Manager to lead Marble’s Data Partnerships, responsible for being the driving force on our health data supply partnerships team and supporting integration development of Marble APIs for new generation of businesses and apps using digital health data.  This role will work closely with our founders and executive leadership to accelerate our growth, deliver on our value proposition for critical Supply Partners, and play a key role in the development of our growing Product Management team. This position is remote with an opportunity to work in our Toronto office whenever you want. 

About Marble  
 
Marble is building the world’s most comprehensive marketplace of patient-owned health data, delivering unparalleled access to a comprehensive view of patient information. We are rapidly evolving our patient-centric, explicit consent-driven platform with unique capabilities to empower patients and their agents with new, actionable health insights.
 
The size of the market we are going after is in the trillions of dollars and we have a LOT of traction:
·       $10’s of millions raised to date and preparing for our Series-B
·       Millions of dollars in revenue with 400% revenue growth YoY
·       Key metrics growing exponentially
·       “Best Places to Work” winner
·       Top investors including Crosslink Capital, Golden Ventures, iGan Partners, Nas, and Stanford University, among others
 
We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Marketing Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/347dc0a8-cdc5-4cc3-aed2-43107742b988</link><description>We’re looking for a Product Marketing Manager to join Marble that will play a key role in crafting the positioning and determining the way to communicate the product vision.  Our Product Marketing Manager will report directly to the CEO as a core member of our Product team. This position is remote, with an opportunity to work out of our Toronto office whenever you want. 

About Marble  
 
Marble is building the world’s most comprehensive marketplace of patient-owned health data, delivering unparalleled access to a comprehensive view of patient information. We are rapidly evolving our patient-centric, explicit consent-driven platform with unique capabilities to empower patients and their agents with new, actionable health insights.
 
The size of the market we are going after is in the trillions of dollars and we have a LOT of traction:
·       $10’s of millions raised to date and preparing for our Series-B
·       Millions of dollars in revenue with 400% revenue growth YoY
·       Key metrics growing exponentially
·       “Best Places to Work” winner
·       Top investors including Crosslink Capital, Golden Ventures, iGan Partners, Nas, and Stanford University, among others
 
We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 14:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/3d190603-3477-4506-be1e-7d1d26886a2c</link><description>About Medchart
We are on a mission to impact millions of people by unlocking secure access to their health data and making it accessible to the apps they use in their daily lives. We want to help thousands of entrepreneurs build their unicorns on top of our APIs – think “Stripe” for health data.

We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that.

About the Role
Medchart is rapidly expanding its team to grow adoption of our new health data API, Marble. This role will be responsible for ensuring the Marble solutions is usable, including service design, interaction design, and visual design. This role would also encompass all responsibilities typically related to user experience, customer experience and user interface. Additionally, the product designer plays a key role in crafting the experience and to best determine the way to communicate the product vision.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Head of Business Development</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/5d882346-9ffe-4a3d-92e0-20627435db92</link><description>Marble is looking for a Head of Sales to join our Leadership team in Toronto! Reporting to the CEO you will build, scale, and develop a team of high performing business development reps, account executives, and customer success.  From strategy to execution, you own the monthly revenue target and other sales productivity metrics.  We are looking for someone who is passionate about sales and someone who takes full responsibility for their success.

About Marble  
 
Marble is building the world’s most comprehensive marketplace of patient-owned health data, delivering unparalleled access to a comprehensive view of patient information. We are rapidly evolving our patient-centric, explicit consent-driven platform with unique capabilities to empower patients and their agents with new, actionable health insights.
 
The size of the market we are going after is in the trillions of dollars and we have a LOT of traction:
·       $10’s of millions raised to date and preparing for our Series-B
·       Millions of dollars in revenue with 400% revenue growth YoY
·       Key metrics growing exponentially
·       “Best Places to Work” winner
·       Top investors including Crosslink Capital, Golden Ventures, iGan Partners, Nas, and Stanford University, among others
 
We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 12:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Sales</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/a3118a70-11ef-4493-a3f3-a41ce7c61896</link><description>We’re looking for a Director of Sales to lead our Legal vertical. In this role you will own our strategy to execution, along with monthly revenue target and other sales productivity metrics.  We are looking for someone who is passionate about sales and someone who takes full responsibility for their success.

About Marble  
 
Marble is building the world’s most comprehensive marketplace of patient-owned health data, delivering unparalleled access to a comprehensive view of patient information. We are rapidly evolving our patient-centric, explicit consent-driven platform with unique capabilities to empower patients and their agents with new, actionable health insights.
 
The size of the market we are going after is in the trillions of dollars and we have a LOT of traction:
·       $10’s of millions raised to date and preparing for our Series-B
·       Millions of dollars in revenue with 400% revenue growth YoY
·       Key metrics growing exponentially
·       “Best Places to Work” winner
·       Top investors including Crosslink Capital, Golden Ventures, iGan Partners, Nas, and Stanford University, among others
 
We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 16:03:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>API Business Development Lead, New Products</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/7ddb255f-6007-4b12-8ab0-e79b2c5434b4</link><description>About Medchart 
We are on a mission to impact millions of people by unlocking secure access to their health data and making it accessible to the apps they use in their daily lives. We want to help thousands of entrepreneurs build their unicorns on top of our APIs – think “Stripe” for health data.
We believe we have a huge opportunity to build something meaningful. Everyone has a friend or family member who has been impacted due to a lack of access to health data and insights, and we are working to change that.

About the Role
Medchart is rapidly expanding its team to grow adoption of our new health data API. We’re looking for an entrepreneurial Business Development Lead to drive go-to-market activities, expanding adoption by app developers in telehealth, consumer fitness, consumer health, clinical research, and insurance, among others.
 
The right candidate for this role will have a mix of entrepreneurial, sales and technical acumen, as well as a great track record helping application developer clients capture growth by integrating Medchart API offerings. The BD Lead for Medchart APIs will report to MedChart’s VP Product and play a critical team leadership role by developing the playbook for expansion into new verticals and regions.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/Medchart/e9c0b75b-7fec-4758-9e1e-b1af53e1bdac</link><description>About Medchart 

Medchart is building the world’s most comprehensive marketplace of patient-owned health data, delivering unparalleled access to a comprehensive view of patient health. We are rapidly evolving our patient-centric, explicit consent-driven platform with unique artificial intelligence and machine learning capabilities to empower patients and their agents – including law firms, insurance companies across North America - with new, actionable health insights.  Medchart has over 140 employees with offices in Toronto and Dallas-Fort Worth.
We’re looking for an Account Executive to join Medchart to become part of our Sales team.  In this role you will be challenged to grow, be a team player and contribute to building our health data marketplace. As an Account Executive, you will report to the Director of Sales, and play a critical role driving topline revenue growth and expanding our customer base across North America in the Legal sector.  

As an Enterprise Account Executive, you will:

• Target and open high-value law firm accounts; build and execute account plans to accelerate adoption of the Medchart platform.

• Sell across law firm partners, operations and office managers, paralegals and other stakeholders, by demonstrating how Medchart drives process and profitability efficiencies.  

• Challenge customers’ status quo by understanding customer needs presenting Medchart’s solution with a value-first sales approach.

• Handle full sales cycle which includes cold calling, closing the account, account management and working with Customer Experience team to ensure successful implementation.

• Pragmatically build, manage and report on a pipeline leading to revenue overachievement, communicate ongoing status, and provide progress and visibility with management.

• Lead online presentations and demos to better qualify and create interest around benefits of Medchart platform.

• Tell stories helping law firm customers understand how Medchart solves medical record retrieval and review challenges through cloud-based technology, data connections and AI/ML

• Represent the voice of the customer and engage meaningfully with clients to provide feedback to inform the product roadmap.  

• Keep a high level of energy and positive attitude contributing to overall sales team experience and aggressive top-line growth in a scale-up corporate environment.

What are we looking for?

• Customer Lifetime Value, Customer Obsession: No Compromises. You are obsessed with customer success and wear customer satisfaction as a badge of honour

• Experience: You are high performing Sales professional with 5+ years account management/account executive experience in a full-cycle sales environment. Legal, Health, Insurance or SaaS Sales experience preferred. 

• Overachievement: You get an adrenaline rush every time you close a deal and live to exceed your quota. You create highly satisfied clients who trust your expertise.

• Growth Mindset: You’re seeking to improve and develop your skill set on a continuous basis. You wake up hungry to learn, read, and study your craft to become your best self. 

• Sales Methodology, Innovation: You believe in following a process because it works, and changing it up when it doesn’t. You build and execute successful, repeatable Sales strategies.

• Creativity, Analytical Thinking: You have the proven ability to analyze situations and to think beyond traditional approaches to solve problems.

• Communication, Listening: You have exceptional interpersonal skills.  Your communication is second to none, and you naturally identify the solution to a client’s unique issues. 

• Sense of Urgency, Hands On, Agile: You want the challenge of working at a high-growth, post-Series A company.  You are responsive to customer needs and revenue growth imperatives.

• Passion: You get up in the morning with a fire in your belly.  You are customer-focused to the core and passionate about cloud-based and AI/ML technology.

• Culture Orientated, Team Player: You want to contribute to an amazing culture and be part of a collaborative team that believes in Medchart’s core values: Hunger Humility, and Care. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 18:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>