<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Geotab Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/geotab?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Geotab from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Software Engineer - Full Stack</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/f0c03ba3-28d0-4809-8b1d-4718d1617a7a</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Engineering Team:

We aim to meaningfully improve the lives of small business owners, who are traditionally under-served and often struggle because of this. At Wave, you won’t just write code—you’ll build high-quality systems at scale. This means being involved in the research, design, and organizational and maintenance practices behind our wide range of applications, which are relied upon by tens of thousands of small business owners. You won’t find many hardcore specialists here. Most Wave engineers are willing and able to dive into different technologies to get the job done. This requires curiosity, openness to new ideas and perspectives, and a genuine interest in what makes software products tick.

Looking to join this team? You’ll work alongside some technical heavyweights such as:

Jason Colburne: Staff Engineer at Wave, ex-Amazon, and talented enough to build his own guitar effect pedals (which he uses in live performances).

Felix Crux: Engineering Director at Wave; ex-Google, ex-Amazon. Three passports, four languages, and licensed to safely operate a bicycle.

As an engineering team, we deeply care about being the best in our craft - System Design, Code Quality, Test Coverage, and Observability. As a part of this team, you will help maintain the current bar we have but will hopefully go on to raise it to the next level.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 17:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Full Stack</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/1ef07d89-be25-4d2a-81a3-ef82eed33e39</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Engineering Team:

We aim to meaningfully improve the lives of small business owners, who are traditionally under-served and often struggle because of this. At Wave, you won’t just write code—you’ll build high-quality systems at scale. This means being involved in the research, design, and organizational and maintenance practices behind our wide range of applications, which are relied upon by tens of thousands of small business owners. You won’t find many hardcore specialists here. Most Wave engineers are willing and able to dive into different technologies to get the job done. This requires curiosity, openness to new ideas and perspectives, and a genuine interest in what makes software products tick.

About The Role:

As a Senior Software Engineer, you will join one of the many cross-functional engineering team to work alongside Product, Design and other developers to bring your engineering skill to bear on exciting business challenges. You will work with some fantastic engineers to solve tough problems in delivering world-class financial products to our customers at scale. You will  work with a wide variety of technologies and help investigate new ones as we are constantly striving for to keep our technology choices up to date. As an engineering team, we deeply care about being the best in our craft - Performance, Reliability, Reusability, Code Quality, Test Coverage, and Observability. You will help maintain the current bar we have but will hopefully go on to raise it to the next level.

Interested in the role? You’ll work alongside some technical heavyweights such as:

Jason Colburne: Staff Engineer at Wave, ex-Amazon, and talented enough to build his own guitar effect pedals (which he uses in live performances).

Tina Goyal: Senior Engineering Director at Wave. Tina is passionate about building software teams and products, leadership, coaching and creating a culture of trust, excellence and collaboration.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 16:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Front End</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/c4506732-2cf0-420e-ab2f-fc79bfd27f35</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Engineering Team:

We aim to meaningfully improve the lives of small business owners, who are traditionally under-served and often struggle because of this. At Wave, you won’t just write code—you’ll build high-quality systems at scale. This means being involved in the research, design, and organizational and maintenance practices behind our wide range of applications, which are relied upon by tens of thousands of small business owners. You won’t find many hardcore specialists here. Most Wave engineers are willing and able to dive into different technologies to get the job done. This requires curiosity, openness to new ideas and perspectives, and a genuine interest in what makes software products tick.

About The Role:

As a Senior Software Engineer in the Front-end domain, you will join one of the many cross-functional engineering team to work alongside Product, Design and other developers to build software to solve exciting business challenges. You will work with some fantastic engineers to solve tough problems in delivering world-class financial products to our customers at scale. You will bring your front-end skills to bear on making our React and ReactNative apps scale better and stay ahead of these quickly evolving ecosystem, helping the teams around also contribute better code by laying good React/ReactNative standards and building solid interfaces and reusable utilities and libraries that make everyone's lives better. You will be exposed to a wide variety of technologies and help investigate new ones as we are constantly striving for to keep our technology choices up to date. As an engineering team, we deeply care about being the best in our craft - Performance, Reliability, Reusability, Code Quality, Test Coverage, and Observability. You will help maintain the current bar we have but will hopefully go on to raise it to the next level.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 16:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager, Data Platform and Operations</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/95e655c2-98ab-4487-a93c-3c7ee1ef0fc1</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

We are a team of data scientists - analysts and analytics engineers - who work with Wave stakeholders across Product, Marketing, Customer Experience and Risk to craft experiments and build data products that deliver actionable insights and create measurable value.

The data that our work depends on moves through pipelines and infrastructure operated by our colleagues in DataOps, and also feeds the models trained by our Machine Learning team. 

Our collective strength as a Data and Analytics Team comes from our relationships and close collaboration, enabling us to drive strategic and operational decision-making at Wave. We are looking for a Manager who will be a coach and a mentor to the team, who will empower us to execute autonomously, who will be an advocate and effective communicator for Analytics, and who will nurture our growth and resilience.


About the Role: 

Wave is looking for an experienced leader for our Data Platform and Operations team. The ideal candidate is an experienced people leader who possesses a robust knowledge of data platforms, a passion for moving and serving data reliably and efficiently, and who is comfortable being hands-on when required.

The Data Platform and Operations team builds, optimises, and maintains Wave’s data infrastructure. This includes the pipelines, tooling and data warehouse through which our data is moved, transformed and consumed, as well as the overall data architecture. You will be managing a team of Data Engineers and a Data Architect who split their time between advancing data projects, monitoring data pipeline operations, servicing Wave stakeholder requests, and supporting the Analytics and ML teams.

You will report to the Director of Data, and will work closely with fellow managers, contributing to wider management duties across the Data and Analytics Team. You will play a role in augmenting data literacy at Wave, deepening business engagement with the Data team, and have the opportunity to shape the data-driven culture at Wave.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 13:05:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager, Data Analytics</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/78ca9c05-34c3-435b-b8ff-2ab0b6a8fb67</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the team: 

We are a team of data scientists - analysts and analytics engineers - who work with Wave stakeholders across Product, Marketing, Customer Experience and Risk to craft experiments and build data products that deliver actionable insights and create measurable value.

The data that our work depends on moves through pipelines and infrastructure operated by our colleagues in DataOps, and also feeds the models trained by our Machine Learning team.
 
Our collective strength as a Data and Analytics Team comes from our relationships and close collaboration, enabling us to drive strategic and operational decision-making at Wave. We are looking for a Manager who will be a coach and a mentor to the team, who will empower us to execute autonomously, who will be an advocate and effective communicator for Analytics, and who will nurture our growth and resilience.

About the Role:

Wave is seeking out a dedicated leader for our growing Analytics team. The ideal candidate is an experienced people leader with a strong background of thought-leadership in analytics and data product management, who is comfortable being hands-on when required.

The Analytics team leverages data – and the interpretation of data – to answer business questions, solve business problems, glean insights, and offer a better understanding of our products and customers. You will be managing a group of analysts who each have a primary area of focus (a product or functional group), and who also collaborate to support one another’s work.

You will report to the Director of Data, and will work closely with fellow managers, contributing to wider management duties across the Data and Analytics Team. You will play a role in augmenting data literacy at Wave, deepening business engagement with the Data team, and have the opportunity to shape the data-driven culture at Wave.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 13:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Payroll Risk Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/e3e85414-661d-4a69-9c81-44ad6b056fad</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Team:

The Risk Team is responsible for protecting Wave and our customers from fraud, credit and compliance losses across all financial services including our proprietary payments, payroll and debit card products. 

About the Role:

Reporting to the Manager, Payroll Risk the Payroll Risk Analyst will have an important role at Wave. You will be responsible for ensuring the onboarding of customers onto our payroll platform by assessing the credit risk of new businesses and entrepreneurs. This role requires strength in both fraud and credit analysis to protect Wave and our customers as we grow our business.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Payments Risk Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/aa32a2df-f74e-4105-988e-6fb1ba8b13ec</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About Risk:

The Risk team is responsible for assessing the credit risk of new businesses, detecting and preventing fraud, optimizing our transaction processes, assisting with enhancements of risk prevention strategies and liaising with our small business owners to develop and implement the best possible solutions. 

About the Risk Analyst: 

Reporting to the Lead Payments Risk Analyst, the Risk Analyst plays a critical role at Wave. This position isn’t for the faint of heart: you must be a highly motivated individual with strong communication skills, carry a sense of tact and empathy under pressure, and have a sixth sense for identifying problems while implementing and communicating solutions.

Looking to join this team? You’ll work alongside some top notch Wavers such as:

Raf Diana: Senior Manager, Risk Operations. Raf leads and supports a rapidly growing team, who together crush fraudsters and find complex patterns of fraud all before lunch. Raf herself has been taking down all types of financial fraud for over 20 years, but doesn’t look a day over 39. Raf has even executed face-to-face interviews with offenders who thought they were getting away with it! Raf’s leadership approach is collaborative, empowering, and strength based. In Raf’s spare time she’s raising her 10 year old son, throwing pizza doughs, playing the Godfather theme song on the mandolin, and sticking up for the little guys/girls.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 20:02:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobile Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/dabf6370-0912-4032-b4aa-30fe3b4c7e6b</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without. 

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take one-minute and forty-eight seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Mobile Platform Team: 
We enable other Wave teams to develop and deploy functionality for our mobile apps, and these apps make life easier for Wave users.  We build on a combination of native iOS and Android, as well as React Native, and we use continuous integration to run test suites on every commit. This means that we welcome anyone with iOS, Android, or React Native (or other!) mobile development experience, and we expect that you’ll be comfortable learning how to build for more than one platform when you get here. You will work with other Wave teams that will translate their Python, Go and Ruby services into graphQL APIs for mobile consumption as you all work together towards common goals.

We face exciting, out of the box challenges everyday: whether it is improving performance for our mobile apps, developing new shared React Native components, or determining how to deliver over-the-air updates for our applications, we never run out of difficult problems to solve. This is a workplace that is fun and informal. As part of this team, you will be exposed to a wide range of technologies and challenges and amazing teams that you will collaborate with to deliver mobile solutions that empower the small business owners that rely on our platform.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 22:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Growth Marketing Manager, Mobile</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/1ae73a9c-624c-4ce4-8f6f-6f3fc2b21654</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the role
As a Growth Marketing Manager for our Wave Mobile App, you’ll work closely with both our mobile product team and cross-functional product teams to drive activation and revenue within our mobile channel. You’ll be working with product managers, designers, and data scientists to go deep into the mobile product to understand what’s working, what isn’t, and how we can improve experiences that will drive value for both our business owners and for Wave
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Executive Assistant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/6dd0420f-1b5e-4ea9-b69c-82b74042f493</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the role:

In this role, you will be the Executive Assistant to the CEO of Wave.  You will be responsible for leading and coordinating all of the day-to-day management, communication and operational functions of the CEO. The Executive Assistant will strategically organize meetings, events, and tasks to optimize the CEO’s time and keep productivity on track. 

This is a part-time role, we are looking for someone who can work roughly 20/hours per week. Working hours are not set in stone as the role requires on-call availability. This role can be done remotely or from the Wave office in Toronto. 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 18:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chargeback Dispute Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/9a769d5b-23a6-49cd-a6ce-70a5de83376a</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Financial Services Operations team: 

Do you love interacting directly with customers and providing amazing experiences? Have a passion for helping small business owners and entrepreneurs deal with issues with their customers? Have a knack for explaining the complex in a simple, easy to understand way?  Comfortable in a fast paced, technology driven environment? Got a competitive streak in you and love to win?  Well then, have we got a role for you!

As a member of our mighty Financial Services Operations team, you will have the unique opportunity to showcase your amazing investigative, communication and customer service skills as part of the elite chargebacks team to help win chargeback disputes on behalf of our Entrepreneurs. Reporting to the Manager, Recovery Operations we are looking for aDisputes &amp; Chargeback Analyst to help fight for our business owners and Wave throughout the chargeback dispute resolution cycle. This position isn't for the faint of heart; you must be ready to take on both the excitement and responsibility of being a Disputes &amp; Chargeback Analyst and be able to guide small business owners through the entire dispute cycle to resolution. 

No direct chargeback experience?  While it is helpful and considered a huge plus, we also pride ourselves in terms of being able to help Wavers learn and grow new skills in their career.  As long as you’re curious, tenacious, a quick study and have a passion for the customer, we will teach you the rest!  Empowered with a solid understanding of the different types of chargebacks, experience gathering evidence for cases and investigations and working in a cross-functional and collaborative team across Wave, this opportunity isn’t one you should pass up!

Looking to join this team? You'll work alongside some top notch Wavers such as Krista Cappadocia:

I’ve been with Wave now for 6 years. I originally started in customer support, worked my way to the chargebacks team, started the loss mitigations team here at Wave and now managing the Dispute Resolutions team. It has been an amazing opportunity for growth and leadership. Each day offers new challenges and opportunities to grow. In my spare time, I like hanging out with my son, dancing and watching movies!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 14:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bookkeeping Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/waveapps/3cf7c537-f6c2-44be-b219-b2db5136ca6d</link><description>We believe small businesses are at the heart of our communities, and championing them is worth fighting for. We empower small business owners to manage their finances fearlessly, by offering the simplest, all-in-one financial management solution they can't live without.

Wavers are a special breed. We could write a novel on our award-winning culture and what makes us, us. However, we’d rather just show you. Take 1 minute and 48 seconds out of your day to get a quick glimpse on why you should join us.

About the Wave Advisors team:

The Wave Advisors team partners with small business owners in managing their books and making more time for them to focus on what matters most - their business! The team acts as a trusted advisor by providing coaching, bookkeeping and tax services to small business owners to help them manage their finances. 

About the Bookkeeping Associate:

Reporting to the Lead Accounting Associate, you will have a portfolio of companies whose bookkeeping you own. As an Bookkeeping Associate, you will be an integral piece of the Wave Advisors bookkeeping team that’s helping great customers get an even better experience. As a team, we care deeply about being the best in our craft— as a part of this team, you will help maintain the current bar we have but will hopefully go on to raise it to the next level. Please note, this position does not follow the traditional CPA route.

Looking to join this team? You’ll work alongside some top notch Wavers such as:

Teresa Yeung: Sr. Manager of Accounting Services, Teresa is passionate about inspiring and empowering others. At Wave, she manages a team of bookkeeping associates and loves to see her team grow and develop professionally.
Lawrence Levinson: Director of Wave Advisors, Lawrence is an accomplished business leader with 20 years of multinational experience across B2B/B2C cultures and industries. He has driven top-line growth &amp; ROI through Business &amp; Strategic Development, Customer Experience, Sales, Loyalty and Marketing in Startup, Fortune 100 &amp; Forbes Global 2000 companies. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 16:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>