<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Koho Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/koho?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Koho from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:13:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Staff Developer, Payments - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/0425f251-c32f-478a-9710-9adaea935247</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role:
As a Staff Software Developer, Backend on KOHO’s Tech team, you will be a technical leader in the KOHO payment ecosystem. You will help define the vision for payments at KOHO while improving the overall technology platform. Even though your main focus is the Payments ecosystem, the impact you will have will be felt and seen across the entire Tech team. 

Our teams have a significant degree of autonomy and ownership, and we’re looking for someone with a high level of initiative. This is a fast-paced outcome-oriented environment! We are looking for collaborative developers like you who are eager to help other developers grow, never afraid to voice concerns, and always pushing for best practices. We are looking for you to own and help us improve our coding standards, testing practices, metric definitions, monitoring and alerting our system, and documentation guidelines.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 21:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Developer, Frontend - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/0a74bc2f-2570-4440-85d7-fa6418fea82f</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

As a Senior Software Developer, Frontend, you will be a technical leader within your team. You will evangelize our technology, own our system, mentor team members, challenge our processes, and influence others.

Our teams have a large degree of autonomy and ownership and we’re looking for someone with a high level of initiative. This is a fast-paced outcome-oriented environment! We are looking for team players like you who are always eager to learn and help other developers grow. Excited yet?
</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Developer, Back End - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/243fefb6-d3e9-4051-87f2-70c911e5f2a4</link><description>About the Role 
As a Senior Software Developer, Backend on KOHO’s Tech and Engineering team, you will be a strong contributor in the KOHO ecosystem and work with other developers to help define and implement processes. You will be working as part of a cross-functional team and driving our core features from start to finish. 

Our teams have a large degree of autonomy and ownership and we’re looking for someone with a high level of initiative. This is a fast-paced outcome-oriented environment! We are looking for collaborative-oriented developers like you who are always eager to learn and help other developers grow. Excited yet?

Please Note: This is a remote position based in Canada that is available to those who are legally entitled to work in Canada.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 15:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Security Architect - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/cf570ae7-2471-46eb-a7d6-c3e4900f0261</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

Reporting to the Director, IT &amp; Security, you will be responsible for our cloud security projects ensuring we secure our infrastructure hosts and containers.  You will be working closely with DevOps and Tech/Engineering teams to discover, remediate, and secure vulnerabilities to reduce risks to our backend infrastructure. 

You’ll be a foundational security team member and have significant responsibilities that make an impact on KOHO’s security posture. 

</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 16:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Marketing Lead, SEO &amp; Content - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/71e39b25-3b97-4c40-9551-6949d6646182</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is looking for our next Senior Marketing Lead to own all things SEO and Content. There are three main pillars to this role: content, SEO and ASO. If this sounds like you already, keep reading!

</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 19:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Legal Counsel, Commercial - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/a3f6f3a8-9517-4ee8-baf0-da660124bb3e</link><description>We're seeking a smart, motivated attorney to help our company grow and scale as we continue to deliver financial products and services that improve the lives of consumers across Canada. You will lead the commercial legal work; and may provide support for product development and regulatory matters also. This role reports to the Chief Legal Officer and can be located anywhere in Canada (as we are a fully remote company!)
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 12:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Analytics Engineer - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/fad43ed6-71e0-4510-bdbb-2c8969c7537a</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is looking for a Senior Analytics Engineer to work with our data analytics, engineering, data science, and machine learning teams. This role is for you if you are passionate about modeling data in a way that empowers end users to answer their own questions. Successful applicants will spend their time transforming, testing, deploying, and documenting data leveraging dbt while applying software engineering best practices across the analytics code base. This role will also include the ownership of dbt across the organization and collaboration with data leadership related to all aspects of analytics engineering for the firm.

Please Note: This is a remote position and is available to those who are legally entitled to work in Canada.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Engineer - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/646ef82e-8830-4d27-a580-278a34c4e230</link><description>About the Role

As a Sales Engineer at KOHO, you will be a core part of the team responsible for selling our unique solutions to partners across Canada. You will lead consultative, technical-focused discussions with both internal and external stakeholders in support of new partnerships, implementations and integrations. The role will require you to collaborate with a wide range of cross-functional teams to gain a holistic understanding of KOHOs technical capabilities to successfully support your day-to-day responsibilities.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Responsable de la Sécurité des Produits - À Distance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/4d5e66a5-cb09-42c8-abbb-97f903393a92</link><description>À Propos de KOHO

L'objectif de KOHO est de donner aux Canadiens les moyens d’établir des fondations financières solides grâce à des produits totalement transparents et faciles à gérer. Notre parcours a débuté en 2014 et nous avons depuis créé une communauté de plus de 600 000 utilisateurs. Des investisseurs de premier plan du monde entier croient en notre vision et nous avons réussi à amasser plus de 320 M$ pour la concrétiser. 

Le collectif KOHO compte plus de 300 employés à ce jour. Pour en savoir plus sur notre culture, cliquez ici et pour connaître les dernières nouvelles de notre équipe, cliquez ici!

À Propos du Poste

Relevant du directeur, TI et sécurité, nous sommes à la recherche d’un gestionnaire qui veillera à ce que les produits de KOHO répondent aux exigences en matière de sécurité, de confidentialité et de résilience. Le titulaire de ce poste dirigera la sécurité des produits et collaborera avec les équipes suivantes : Tech/Ingénierie, Produit, Risque et Juridique. 

Vous travaillerez en étroite collaboration avec les équipes de produits pour comprendre les feuilles de route et la stratégie des produits de KOHO. Vous dirigerez et développerez la stratégie de confidentialité et de sécurité des produits de KOHO pour toutes les gammes de produits. Vous comprendrez les fonctionnalités qui ont un impact sur la confidentialité et la sécurité de nos utilisateurs pour l'ensemble des produits.

Vous serez un membre essentiel de l’équipe de sécurité et aurez des responsabilités importantes qui auront une incidence sur la stratégie de sécurité de KOHO.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Security Manager - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/a48421c0-f138-4308-b372-ba2b45d0f161</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

Reporting to the Director, IT and Security,  we are looking for a manager to ensure KOHO products meet security, privacy, and resiliency requirements.  This position will lead product security and collaborates with Tech/Engineering, Product, Risk, and Legal teams. 

You will work closely with Product teams to understand KOHO product roadmaps and strategy. Lead and develop KOHO’s product privacy and security strategy across all product lines. Understand product features that impact the privacy and security for our users across all products.  

You’ll be a foundational security team member and have significant responsibilities that make an impact on KOHO’s security posture. 

</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 21:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Manager, Credit - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/665cd3a2-31da-4cdf-b3b7-1bf20ee36cb6</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

We’re looking for a Product Manager to join our team for a role to work remotely based in Canada or USA. Reporting to the Director of Product Management, you’re going to be part of a team that owns the core product.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal Counsel - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/249642b3-b229-461d-b15e-3847e6dbf9b3</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

We're a leading Canadian fintech and we're seeking a smart, motivated Legal Counsel to help our company grow and scale as we continue to deliver financial products and services that improve the lives of consumers across Canada. You will provide legal guidance on commercial contracts, product development, and regulatory matters. This role reports to the Chief Legal Officer and can be located anywhere in Canada (as we are a fully remote company!)
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 16:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Join the KOHO Talent Community!</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/21b6594e-8556-4a55-b0af-28dd2ed9d41b</link><description>We Have Something for Everyone!

Didn't find a role matching your profile and experience?

Feel free to submit an application and keep in touch with us for future opportunities! We are always seeking talented individuals who want to make an impact and join us on our mission.

When submitting your application, please identify which department(s) you’d be most interested in joining, and one of our Talent Partners will reach out if a suitable position opens up. We’ll also stay connected with you about potential opportunities and you’ll receive alerts about any new roles that match your experience! We hope to connect with you in the near future!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Joignez-vous à la Communauté des Talents de KOHO!</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/037f3175-ef5f-4eab-b281-0eb20057badf</link><description>Nous Avons Quelque Chose Pour Tout le Monde!

Vous n’avez pas trouvé de poste correspondant à votre profil et à votre expérience de travail?

N'hésitez pas à soumettre votre candidature et restez en contact avec nous pour connaître les opportunités futures! Nous sommes toujours à la recherche de personnes talentueuses qui souhaitent apporter leur contribution et se joindre à nous dans notre mission.

Lors de l'envoi de votre candidature, veuillez indiquer le ou les départements qui vous intéressent le plus et l'un de nos Partenaires en acquisition de talents communiquera avec vous si un poste correspondant à vos qualifications se libère. Nous resterons également en contact avec vous pour vous informer des opportunités potentielles et vous recevrez des alertes au sujet des nouveaux postes correspondant à votre expérience! Nous espérons communiquer avec vous prochainement!

</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingénieur Principal En Analytique - À Distance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/55257b74-7ac7-4296-8475-289102806572</link><description>À propos de KOHO

L'objectif de KOHO est de donner aux Canadiens les moyens d’établir des fondations financières solides grâce à des produits totalement transparents et faciles à gérer. Notre parcours a débuté en 2014 et nous avons depuis créé une communauté de plus de 600 000 utilisateurs. Des investisseurs de premier plan du monde entier croient en notre vision et nous avons réussi à amasser plus de 320 M$ pour la concrétiser. 
Le collectif KOHO compte plus de 300 employés à ce jour. Pour en savoir plus sur notre culture, cliquez ici et pour connaître les dernières nouvelles de notre équipe, cliquez ici!

À Propos De Ce Poste

KOHO est à la recherche d'un ingénieur principal en analytique pour travailler avec nos équipes d'analyse des données, d'ingénierie, de science des données et d'apprentissage automatique. Ce poste est pour vous si vous êtes passionné par la modélisation des données d'une manière permettant aux utilisateurs finaux de répondre à leurs propres questions. Les candidats retenus consacreront leur temps à transformer, tester, déployer et documenter les données en utilisant DBT (outil de création de données) tout en appliquant les meilleures pratiques d'ingénierie logicielle à l'ensemble de la base du code analytique. Ce poste prévoit également la prise en charge de DBT dans l'ensemble de l'organisation et la collaboration avec la direction des données pour tous les aspects de l'ingénierie analytique de l'entreprise.

Prenez note : Il s’agit d’un poste à distance offert aux personnes légalement autorisées à travailler au Canada.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingénieur En Analytique - À Distance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/9f493ea3-9a88-4eb3-9146-94cef8ba778e</link><description>À Propos De KOHO

L'objectif de KOHO est de donner aux Canadiens les moyens d’établir des fondations financières solides grâce à des produits totalement transparents et faciles à gérer. Notre parcours a débuté en 2014 et nous avons depuis créé une communauté de plus de 600 000 utilisateurs. Des investisseurs de premier plan du monde entier croient en notre vision et nous avons réussi à amasser plus de 320 M$ pour la concrétiser. 

Le collectif KOHO compte plus de 300 employés à ce jour. Pour en savoir plus sur notre culture, cliquez ici et pour connaître les dernières nouvelles de notre équipe, cliquez ici!

À Propos De Ce Poste

KOHO est à la recherche d'un ingénieur en analytique pour travailler avec nos équipes d'analyse des données, d'ingénierie, de science des données et d'apprentissage automatique. Ce poste est pour vous si vous êtes passionné par la modélisation des données d'une manière permettant aux utilisateurs finaux de répondre à leurs propres questions. Les candidats retenus consacreront leur temps à transformer, tester, déployer et documenter les données en utilisant DBT (outil de création de données) tout en appliquant les meilleures pratiques d'ingénierie logicielle à l'ensemble de la base du code analytique. Ce poste prévoit également la prise en charge de DBT dans l'ensemble de l'organisation et la collaboration avec la direction des données pour tous les aspects de l'ingénierie analytique de l'entreprise.

Prenez note : Il s’agit d’un poste à distance offert aux personnes légalement autorisées à travailler au Canada.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Enterprise Account Executive - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/5b3be4ee-83a7-4406-b867-ad6e92c27c3d</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is looking for an Enterprise Account Executive sales professional to spearhead our Instant Pay sales in the Canadian market. We've been actively selling into this market over the last 12 months and have developed features and the necessary regulatory compliance required to penetrate this market. We've already landed many noteworthy Canadian clients to prove our product-market fit.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 19:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director, Product Management (Growth) - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/b16f1e9e-6eb4-4d16-9874-28e926828632</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

At KOHO, we're building the ultimate savings tool for all Canadians. As a Director, Growth, you will be involved in every aspect of the product development process, from defining the product strategy and roadmap to driving release milestones with the engineering team.

This role reports into our Chief Product Officer. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director, Product Management (Growth) - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/1506bd0a-c6d4-4ad9-a9c1-7aeef5a9dfeb</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

At KOHO, we're building the ultimate savings tool for all Canadians. As a Director, Growth, you will be involved in every aspect of the product development process, from defining the product strategy and roadmap to driving release milestones with the engineering team.

This role reports into our Chief Product Officer. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director, Performance Marketing - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/aee52756-28a3-40f8-88f7-246ba9f5a2b0</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is seeking a passionate, growth-oriented, and analytical Director of Performance Marketing to lead the growth team that manages all paid online and offline advertising. The role will be responsible for the strategy and execution to drive growth at a key inflection point for the company, working closely with other functional leaders to scale our business units in an efficient and ROI-positive way.

This person will lead a team that manages paid digital channels (paid social, SEM, display, etc.), experimentation across new channels, marketing analytics, and testing and optimization. This position reports directly to our CMO.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 20:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director, Performance Marketing - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/86a48f76-7301-4463-aef3-d45713581bcb</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is seeking a passionate, growth-oriented, and analytical Director of Performance Marketing to lead the growth team that manages all paid online and offline advertising. The role will be responsible for the strategy and execution to drive growth at a key inflection point for the company, working closely with other functional leaders to scale our business units in an efficient and ROI-positive way.

This person will lead a team that manages paid digital channels (paid social, SEM, display, etc.), experimentation across new channels, marketing analytics, and testing and optimization. This position reports directly to our CMO.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 14:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Développeur Principal de Logiciels, Interface Utilisateur - À Distance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/ebf6ae3a-82d9-424f-919e-570cefcad0da</link><description>À Propos de KOHO

L'objectif de KOHO est de donner aux Canadiens les moyens d’établir des fondations financières solides grâce à des produits totalement transparents et faciles à gérer. Notre parcours a débuté en 2014 et nous avons depuis créé une communauté de plus de 600 000 utilisateurs. Des investisseurs de premier plan du monde entier croient en notre vision et nous avons réussi à amasser plus de 320 M$ pour la concrétiser. 

Le collectif KOHO compte plus de 300 employés à ce jour. Pour en savoir plus sur notre culture, cliquez ici et pour connaître les dernières nouvelles de notre équipe, cliquez ici!

En tant que développeur principal de logiciels, Interface utilisateur, vous serez un leader technique au sein de votre équipe. Vous allez évangéliser notre technologie, prendre en charge notre système, encadrer les membres de l'équipe, remettre en question nos processus et influencer les autres.
 
Nos équipes disposent de beaucoup d'autonomie et de responsabilité et nous sommes à la recherche d'un candidat doté d'un haut niveau d'initiative. Il s'agit d'un environnement au rythme rapide et axé sur les résultats! Nous sommes à la recherche de joueurs d'équipe comme vous qui sont animés par la volonté d'apprendre et d'aider les autres développeurs à se perfectionner. Ça vous intéresse?
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Bureau Reporting Lead (Contract)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/19969992-8986-4597-83a6-ea52f1ba6fe1</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

In this position, you will be the key SME and owner of the credit reporting function to the credit bureaus. You will report to the Director of Credit Risk and work closely with Product, Risk &amp; Compliance, and User Success teams. This is a critical role for KOHO - here’s your chance to make a huge impact!

Please note: this is a contract position on a per project basis.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 14:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Copywriter (Instant Pay) - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/bf38d1a2-8db0-4c86-b100-987ce7ade961</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO’s Marketing team is looking for a stellar copywriter to join our growing company. This individual — a top-notch writer and clever maker of puns— is ready to roll up their sleeves and support wherever copy is needed, be it in-app, on social, for landing pages, and in emails. 

Do you live for a clever turn of phrase and a well articulated thought? Are you curious about how to make the financial system easier to understand? Do you love all things brand? Perfect. This role is all about walking the tightrope between brand tone, time management, and prioritization.  

We need a creative communicator who goes above and beyond to bring energy to every post, thread, and communiqué! Who are we? A loveable team of results-oriented, data-driven creative thinkers on a mission to change financial services in Canada. If the fintech space lights you up, and copywriting is your passion, then please apply for this role. We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity and uniqueness at our company.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Content Strategist (Instant Pay) - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/e79f90d1-a3e5-4dc9-95d2-8a0bb27963aa</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO’s Marketing team is looking for a stellar content strategist to join our growing company. This person —a top-notch writer and strategic thinker— is ready to roll up their sleeves to lead the content strategy for one of our newest products, Instant Pay.

As our content strategist, you’re motivated by working in startup cultures where responsibilities entail leading your function both in strategy and execution. You have a strong understanding of the technical aspects of content creation and a passion for crafting campaigns that drive business outcomes forward. A grammar nerd to your core, you’ll ensure all communications are up to our brand standards and tone of voice.

Who are we? A loveable team of results-oriented, data-driven creative thinkers on a mission to change financial services in Canada. If the fintech space lights you up, and copywriting is your passion, then please apply for this role. We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity and uniqueness at our company.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 21:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Development Representative - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/4f19ff1a-9593-4c7d-8b88-570faeccfa3c</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

As our Business Development Representative, you'll be playing a crucial role of breaking into new accounts and fostering relationships with multiple contacts within all levels of our target customer segments. You understand the impact that you'll create to the bottom line, playing one of the most vital roles in the company. The day-to-day role includes collaboration with the wider sales team, market research to identify new potential customers and leads, and qualification of these leads by learning about their approach to onboarding.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Architecte de Sécurité Principal - à Distance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/0f6df41d-6e85-443d-89bd-4f31633888ad</link><description>À Propos de KOHO

L'objectif de KOHO est de donner aux Canadiens les moyens d’établir des fondations financières solides grâce à des produits totalement transparents et faciles à gérer. Notre parcours a débuté en 2014 et nous avons depuis créé une communauté de plus de 600 000 utilisateurs. Des investisseurs de premier plan du monde entier croient en notre vision et nous avons réussi à amasser plus de 320 M$ pour la concrétiser. 

Le collectif KOHO compte plus de 300 employés à ce jour. Pour en savoir plus sur notre culture, cliquez ici et pour connaître les dernières nouvelles de notre équipe, cliquez ici!

À Propos du Poste

Relevant du directeur, TI et sécurité, vous serez responsable de nos projets de sécurité infonuagique en veillant à ce que nous sécurisions nos hôtes d’infrastructure et de conteneurs. Vous travaillerez en étroite collaboration avec les équipes DevOps et Tech/Ingénierie pour identifier, corriger et sécuriser les vulnérabilités afin de réduire les risques pour notre infrastructure dorsale (back-end).  

Vous serez un membre essentiel de l’équipe de sécurité et aurez des responsabilités importantes qui auront une incidence sur la stratégie de sécurité de KOHO.  
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Analytics Engineer - Remote</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/koho/21fecebb-e583-414e-b9b6-136800ac0984</link><description>About KOHO

KOHO’s purpose is to empower Canadians to build a great financial foundation with products that are radically transparent and easy to manage. Our journey began in 2014, and we have since built a community of over 600,000 users. Leading investors around the globe believe in our vision, and we’ve successfully raised over $320M to make our vision a reality.

The KOHO collective has grown to 300+ employees to date. Discover our culture here and get the inside scoop from our team here!

About the Role

KOHO is looking for an Intermediate-level Analytics Engineer to work with our data analytics, engineering, data science, and machine learning teams. This role is for you if you are passionate about modeling data in a way that empowers end users to answer their own questions. Successful applicants will spend their time transforming, testing, deploying, and documenting data leveraging dbt while applying software engineering best practices across the analytics code base. This role will also include the ownership of dbt across the organization and collaboration with data leadership related to all aspects of analytics engineering for the firm.

Please Note: This is a remote position and is available to those who are legally entitled to work in Canada.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 08:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>