<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Palantir Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/palantir?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Palantir from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:13:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Staff Product Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/349bf557-2321-4454-9ed7-be506285defb</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

User Experience at Wealthsimple:
We're a close-knit UX team made up of broadly skilled Product Designers. We're embedded on product teams so that we can be involved with projects from the get-go and work really closely with other disciplines at every stage of the process. We work purposefully and think big when it comes to our growth as a team and individuals. It's important to us that we have a collaborative and supportive environment to work in every day. Our empathy for our users sets the bar really high for the products and experiences we create.

We’re looking for multiple Staff Product Designers to join our R&amp;D UX Team!
Never heard of a Staff Designer? The role of Staff Designer is a level above Senior Designer in our Job Levels and equivalent to a Manager. Staff Designers do not typically have direct reports, though they may have formal 1:1 mentorship roles with others within their discipline. They are the standard-bearers for quality and consistency within their domain, and work with UX Managers to raise the bar for what we create. Every day looks different for our Staff Product Designers: You might be focused on executing high-priority, high-stakes project work as an individual contributor this week, pairing with Product Designers the next to help them take their work to the next level, and then partner with Product and Engineering Leaders to shape user-centric product strategy after.

We are hiring for multiple positions across our team to help lead design efforts.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 19:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineering Internship (Winter 2023)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/15d31ef8-81dc-419c-b6b4-230d48e18f1c</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. As our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money, Wealthsimple interns are able to be at the forefront of Canada's leading digital financial products and work with smart, high-performing team members who will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for people who love a fast-paced environment and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.  

Internships @ Wealthsimple
At Wealthsimple, we offer 4 to 12-month internships that are open to co-op and non-co-op students, recent grads, and career changers. During your remote-first internship, you will be able to contribute to projects that are changing the landscape of financial services for Canadians. You will be on a team that supports your growth and provides mentorship while also connecting to the broader Wealthsimple community! 

Engineering @ Wealthsimple
Wealthsimple has several engineering teams ranging from product-focused to back-office and our teams build and manage the software that powers our services. We do this using microservice architecture and an agile approach, focused on short iterations and rigorous automated testing, deploying our code over 100 times a day. We maximize our productivity by building high-performing teams and giving them autonomy to deliver results, working very closely with product management, design and operations to make sure that our work delivers maximum benefit for our clients. 

What you can expect from the interview process 👀
First Interview: 30-minute Technical Interview (in your language of choice) with one interviewer
Second Interview: 1-hour Interview with a Hiring Manager where you will be walking through a project review
Last Stage: Offer! 🎉  

Interns @ Wealthsimple are completely integrated into the teams they join and get to work on meaningful projects during their time with us! For Winter 2023, we're looking to add Frontend, Full Stack, and Backend Engineers to our growing teams! Throughout the interview process, we’ll learn more about your skills and interests to match you with the right team at Wealthsimple. 🙌

Applications are due September 19th, 5pm.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior UX Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/b7c3894e-0acf-4887-be1c-b12adc01c42d</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

User Experience at Wealthsimple:
UX at Wealthsimple is a close-knit team of broadly skilled Product Designers. We're embedded in cross-functional product teams to ensure design has input from the start. It's important to us that we foster a collaborative and supportive environment to work in every day. Our empathy for our users sets the bar really high for the products and experiences we create.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Front-End Operations</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/aa60ba9b-62ef-454d-b813-6efeed6a04b5</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! 

Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

At Wealthsimple, we are building products for a diverse world and we need a diverse team to do that successfully. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status. Wealthsimple provides an accessible candidate experience. If you need any accommodations or adjustments throughout the interview process and beyond, please let us know.

The Team

The Front-End Operations team enables all front-end engineers across Wealthsimple to ship high-quality features, faster. We build world-class internal tools that power the engineering experience at Wealthsimple. We also provide architectural guidance (e.g. micro front-end), external tools (e.g. Sentry), testing frameworks (e.g. Cypress), release processes and education materials to all Wealthsimple engineers working on our web (React) and mobile (React Native) products.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Security Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/254f2572-9c1d-46f7-a920-cc986aea2b1f</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas. 

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us!  Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

At Wealthsimple, we are building products for a diverse world and we need a diverse team to do that successfully. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status. Wealthsimple provides an accessible candidate experience. If you need any accommodations or adjustments throughout the interview process and beyond, please let us know.

About the Team: The Product Security Team works to proactively build security into every product and feature that Wealthsimple releases, ensuring that clients accounts and funds are secure this is done through education, review and testing.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 21:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/4463e25b-d15b-4905-b320-8fe9f00b6b35</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

At Wealthsimple, we are building products for a diverse world and we need a diverse team to do that successfully. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status. Wealthsimple provides an accessible candidate experience. If you need any accommodations or adjustments throughout the interview process and beyond, please let us know.

We’re looking for a Senior Product Designer to join our Team!
We're a close-knit UX team made up of Product Designers, Content Designers, and UX Researchers. We're embedded on product teams so that we can be involved with projects from the get-go and work really closely with other disciplines at every stage of the process. We work purposefully and think big when it comes to our growth as a team and individuals. It's important to us that we have a collaborative and supportive environment to work in every day. Our empathy for our users sets the bar really high for the products and experiences we create. 

Note, there are multiple opportunities available throughout the year and we are looking to hire senior designers to focus on different products including but not limited to Cash, Investing, Crypto and more! 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior HRIS Analyst - Workday</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/9ea7b5e1-f440-411e-9b2a-cd495c1b8f45</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.
 
Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.
 
We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than facetime, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us!
 
Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.
 
About the People Team:
Our People Operations team is growing our team to help operationalize and scale the People function at Wealthsimple! Together, we will work to advance multiple exciting projects while providing functional support across the business. The HR Technology team has brought the organization to new heights with the implementation of Workday! We are just getting started in our Workday journey and are looking for you to make a big impact on this team!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Registered Investment Agent</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/421eb822-d87a-4cee-be4d-528478055361</link><description>Our team is working together to build one of the most innovative fintech companies in the world. We're looking for talented people who want to help us move fast, ship often, and make a huge impact. Join us on our mission to make financial services simple and affordable for everyone.

Read our Culture Manual to learn more about us and how we work.

As part of the Client Experience team, you will be responsible for handling client questions and overseeing risk and meeting compliance requirements. We manage hundreds of millions of dollars, so the stakes are high. We want to deliver extraordinary experiences that meet our client's on-demand expectations while being a compliance leader. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Engineer, Crypto</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/d23daf31-b00c-48bc-91fc-e34f8de3420b</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

Crypto @ Wealthsimple
Our vision is to enable all Canadians to participate in and benefit from the Crypto ecosystem no matter who they are. We aspire to build a simple, safe and trusted platform that emphasizes education and provides access to all the benefits and opportunities that crypto has to offer.

We have ambitious plans for Wealthsimple Crypto, that go much further beyond our current trading platform, and are looking for ambitious individuals that can help us shape and execute that vision.

The Crypto space is constantly evolving and can be hard to keep up with. To help keep our team at the forefront of the space, the Crypto team reserves 20% of our time to prototype and dabble with new Crypto technologies in a self-directed environment.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Principal Security Engineer, Crypto</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/3bb469ce-1970-44f3-bef3-baed304fc1dc</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

At Wealthsimple, we are building products for a diverse world and we need a diverse team to do that successfully. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status. Wealthsimple provides an accessible candidate experience. If you need any accommodations or adjustments throughout the interview process and beyond, please let us know.

Throughout the interview process, we’ll learn more about your skills and interests to match you with the right team at Wealthsimple.

About the role:

The Wealthsimple Security organization champions the mandate of protecting our clients, products and business. We believe that security should be built into the fabric of everything we do, across all domains, products and teams. The team protects the systems that help hundred of thousands of users manage billions of dollars in assets. We use a micro service architecture and an agile approach, focused on short iterations and rigorous automated testing, deploying our code over 100 times a day.

The roles of Staff and Principal Engineer at Wealthsimple share a number of similarities. In particular, both are technical IC roles with impact beyond individual teams. Our Staff Engineers are domain experts that drive the technical direction and impact Product or foundational domain; Principal Engineers are deep subject matter experts that work across all of engineering.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 22:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Copywriting</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/89245ae3-4f5f-4062-89fb-578ce62b97cf</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas. Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead, Credit Strategy and Policy</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/ce2c0325-767c-41eb-b684-1cf5e028366c</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.


About the team:

Credit policy is part of a new retail lending group at Wealthsimple and we want to build a team of exceptional lending professionals with diverse educational backgrounds. 

We are taking on green-field lending: starting with small data and growing through iteration and experimentation. The team is responsible for managing a suite of inclusive retail lending products in a way that optimizes risk &amp; return and delights our customers. 

The credit team is staffed with seasoned engineers, product managers, and data scientists and we need a credit policy leader who can collaborate with these teams to deliver strategies for approval, line management, pricing, limits, and authorization. 

This team is a great place to learn about the interplay of product, technology and risk and a great place to see your work deliver a big impact to the business.

As credit policy &amp; strategy lead you will play a pivotal role in managing the risk of Wealthsimple’s retail lending products.

Together our work will accelerate Wealthsimple’s goal to be the primary financial service provider to millions of Canadians.

You should have domain knowledge in retail lending, strong analytical skills, strong communication skills, and experience with cross-functional collaboration. You should be comfortable managing a small team and experienced enough to step in and get your hands dirty sometimes. 

We are building inclusive financial products and we want someone who is willing to challenge the status quo of what it means to be credit-worthy.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 19:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Content Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/264bba26-d7ad-4ca2-9840-fdc79252fc80</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

User Experience at Wealthsimple:
We're a close-knit UX team made up of Product and Content Designers. Product Designers are embedded on product teams so that we can be involved with projects from the get-go and work really closely with other disciplines at every stage of the process. Content Designers are critical enablers and the champions for our product content standards, ensuring we communicate simply across our product portfolio. We work purposefully and think big when it comes to our growth as a team and individuals. It's important to us that we have a collaborative and supportive environment to work in every day. Our empathy for our users sets the bar really high for the products and experiences we create.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Infrastructure Security Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/0c72323b-bd4f-423f-af97-aa5d2d1efbfa</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost. We're the company behind some of Canada's leading digital financial products, and are growing faster than ever.

Our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money. Smart, high-performing team members will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for talented people who love a fast-paced environment, and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas.

We’re a remote-first team and output is more important than face time, so where you choose to work is up to you — as long as you have internet access, you can work from anywhere in Canada. Be a part of our Canadian success story and help shape the financial future of millions — join us! Read our Culture Manual and learn more about how we work.

At Wealthsimple, we are building products for a diverse world and we need a diverse team to do that successfully. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status. Wealthsimple provides an accessible candidate experience. If you need any accommodations or adjustments throughout the interview process and beyond, please let us know.

The Infrastructure Security Team protects Wealthsimple's environment and works to ensure infrastructure security gaps are addressed with adequate and well maintained security controls.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Science Internship (Winter 2023)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/wealthsimple/0c68b968-c96f-40ca-8d61-b356ea25c8fe</link><description>Wealthsimple is on a mission to help everyone achieve financial freedom, no matter who they are or how much they have. Using smart technology, Wealthsimple takes financial services that are often confusing, opaque and expensive and makes them simple, transparent, and low-cost.

As our team is reimagining what it means to manage your money, Wealthsimple interns are able to be at the forefront of Canada's leading digital financial products and work with smart, high-performing team members who will challenge you to learn and grow every day. We value great work and great ideas — not ego. We're looking for people who love a fast-paced environment and want to ship often and make an impact with groundbreaking ideas. 

Internships @ Wealthsimple
At Wealthsimple, we offer 4 to 12-month internships that are open to co-op and non-co-op students, recent grads, and career changers. During your remote-first internship, you will be able to contribute to projects that are changing the landscape of financial services for Canadians. You will be on a team that supports your growth and provides mentorship while also connecting to the broader Wealthsimple community!

Data Science @ Wealthsimple
The Data Science &amp; Engineering (DSE) team consists of data scientists and software engineers with diverse educational backgrounds such as math, operations research, economics, computer science, engineering and business. The team is responsible for enabling data-driven decision-making and building data products at Wealthsimple. We achieve these goals by:
- Building a high quality and scalable state-of-the-art data warehouse that powers all decision making
- Leveraging machine learning and algorithms to help Wealthsimple build smarter financial products
- Using decision science to understand the cause and effect of our business decisions

What you can expect from the interview process:
First Interview: 30-minute technical interview (in your language of choice) with two interviewers. 
Second Interview: 45-minute Interview with a Hiring Manager where you will be walking through a project review and also find out more about your potential team.
Last Stage: Offer! 🎉

Interns @ Wealthsimple are completely integrated into the teams they join and get to work on meaningful projects during their time with us! For Winter 2023, we're looking to add Data scientists across our times! Throughout the interview process, we’ll learn more about your skills and interests to match you with the right team at Wealthsimple 🙌

Applications are due September 19th, 5pm.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>