<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Paytm Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/paytm?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Paytm from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Workforce Planning Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b00d1b9c-bd9f-4331-a4a2-17c72dae40fd</link><description>Buckle up if you’re ready to be our Workforce Planning Specialist. In this role, you shall be responsible for providing HC data for budgeting, monitoring headcount planning vs actual, and analyzing the effectiveness of the manpower in the organization. 

Working closely with the PBP and Business Leaders you shall be responsible for a headcount of over 2,500 employees. The folks in the GTF People Business Partner, HR Data Analytics, Finance, and Payroll will be your companions on this ride. Your efforts will band together to enhance the company's operational excellence.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vendor Management Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5d21d554-030b-45df-83f2-b48ecff1a15e</link><description>About the Role

Vendor Management Team is a centralized function based in Jakarta. It handles Vendor Onboarding and Maintenance process throughout GoTo.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 04:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UX Writer - Merchant Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/433b31b7-df2f-40ab-bb4e-2408fbf8af88</link><description>About the Role

It is said that good design is good business. As our UX Writer for the Payments Product Design team, you'll dive deep into projects surrounding user experience, translating business goals, technical problems, and research points into impactful words/copy. With your stellar design-thinking, research, and data-driven capabilities, you’ll write for a range of audiences, produce multiple design point-of-views and solutions, conduct small to large research projects, and collaborate with a talented troop of writers and designers within the company.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 08:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UX Writer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0c277d1f-973a-4abf-b01e-b01da26b187c</link><description>About the Role

It is said that good design is good business. As our UX Writer for the Payments Product Design team, you'll dive deep into projects surrounding user experience, translating business goals, technical problems, and research points into impactful words/copy. With your stellar design-thinking, research, and data-driven capabilities, you’ll write for a range of audiences, produce multiple design point-of-views and solutions, conduct small to large research projects, and collaborate with a talented troop of writers and designers within the company.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 08:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UX Writer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/fb9dd137-11af-49f7-8d6a-c4122099acb6</link><description>About the Role

It is said that good design is good business. As our UX Writer for the Commerce Enablement Product Design team, you'll dive deep into projects surrounding user experience, translating business goals, technical problems, and research points into impactful words/copy. With your stellar design-thinking, research, and data-driven capabilities, you’ll write for a range of audiences, produce multiple design point-of-views and solutions, conduct small to large research projects, and collaborate with a talented troop of writers and designers within the company.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>User Spend Pod Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3eca0616-621c-4b6c-9595-778375010875</link><description>About the Role 
As our GoPay User Spend Business Lead, you’ll take the wheel in managing the company’s strategy-to-execution - from consumer research, OKRs, to strategy planning. Working closely with GoTroops from various professional backgrounds, you’ll spearhead GoPay’s development within various industry vertical in Indonesia, bolstering Indonesia’s cashless society while driving user and transaction growth with full P&amp;L ownership. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 09:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Total Rewards Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d14640e7-bb37-40f0-a102-2bffe353e2ea</link><description>About the Role 

We are looking for Bachelor's and Master's students who can join us for a 5/6 months internship starting from Aug 2022 to Jan 2023. This internship would provide a great opportunity to shadow and learn the ropes from global C&amp;B subject matter experts with deep functional expertise.  Depending on which team you are assigned to, you would get exposure to Compensation Market Benchmarking, Compensation Analytics, Employment Tax, Compensation Operations, Compensation Process Engineering, or Benefits Program design among other varied and interesting C&amp;B topics. 
</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TechOps Engineer (GoFinance)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/065cd0fa-5278-4052-b9e6-ae6b3decc7f7</link><description>About the role

As a part of TechDevOPs, you’ll play an important role in setting up the newly established Infrastructure Platform within Gojek’s Financial Services team. Together with several Engineering streams and our third-party partners’ engineers, you’ll deploy and administer cloud-based infrastructure, perform troubleshooting and root cause analysis, and contribute your expertise to the platform’s technical direction and strategic decisions for its infrastructure &amp; architecture. Also there will be extra responsibility of achieving SLA’s in Response time and Resolution time. You have to always keep checking all logged tickets and respond to customers. Reach SLA’s also follow the JSM lifecycle.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tax Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ce118275-cd23-436b-9988-9c22627b01bb</link><description>About the Role 

Tax specialist is a centralized function unit for Gojek based in Jakarta that handles any tax related to compliance, day-to-day operation, and audit process. 


</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 06:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tax Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6c2d98bb-6e4a-4c67-88d0-039e530ff67c</link><description>About the Role 

The tax manager will lead ia centralized function unit for Gojek based in Jakarta that handle any tax related to compliance, day to day operation with some automation and audit process.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 06:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Talent &amp; Leadership Development Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8594484e-c837-4403-9235-315c8bb13b0a</link><description>Jump to our rocket ship and fasten your seatbelt now if you’re ready to be a part of an adventurous journey in building the future of the digital economy as Talent &amp; Leadership Development Lead. In this role, you will be an integral player within the Learning &amp; Development Team. Your main mission is to enable talent development in this rocket ship to upgrade and grow their capability at its best! Pretty much you will be playing the Yoda role, you will be responsible to oversee the development of all “Jedi Masters” in our GTF Galaxy. Together with our L&amp;D team, your efforts will band together to boost our rocket ship closer to vision!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff Product Security Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/77556f94-d731-4d44-9c6e-c4950c5a801d</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our next Staff Product Security Engineer. You will be part of a journey making path-breaking outcomes that will influence not only your aspirations to lead a career within Information Security but also make an impact on the mission of Gojek. As a part of our Product Security team, you will be independently responsible for the entire lifecycle of security projects or features including security design &amp; development, deployment, implementation, and operations. We at Gojek, believe that Security is EVERYONE's responsibility and you will be holding the reigns to promote and lead "Security by Design" principles at Gojek.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. QA Engineer - Merchant Experience</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/69e96be9-463a-4f1c-b86a-73b1939f196b</link><description>Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Senior QA Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay team based in Bangalore, India, that directly oversees Gojek's payment experiences. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current user preferences and trends, and emerging technologies in the mobile engineering field, you'll drive end-to-end testing efforts and take the wheel in the development and success of the product within your team. You'll get ample opportunity to flex your automation testing skills, getting us even closer to our goal of creating a seamless app that will transport Gojek to all corners of the globe.

Test Engineers would need to be able to lead and implement the test strategy for manual as well as automation by working closely with the product and engineering group. You would also work on the latest cutting-edge technologies and focusing on Merchant Payments – Experience team. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. Product Marketing Lead - Selly - 7869</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/88deef6d-4de3-449b-86be-ff5f5c2a4465</link><description>About the Role

As a Sr. Product Marketing Lead for the Commerce Enablement team, we are looking for a passionate and impact-driven person that can lead a team and develop a strong marketing strategy that can contribute to a significant impact on the business.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. Product Manager - Consumer Experience</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c672433b-a4a7-4467-b3a0-d8abb73181b3</link><description>About the Role

As our Sr. Product Manager for the Payments group, you'll manage the Experience &amp; Growth stream. This stream will be part of the Consumer Experience team. As a part of this team, you will need to closely collaborate with research, design, and marketing teams to understand more about users &amp; their spending behaviors. GoPay is competing against payment companies, financial services, and surely cash. It’s important to be on tows to understand changing user behaviors and their needs from their payment providers. 

As a Sr. Product Manager, you will identify these needs and will influence teams to work towards solving problems to make GoPay an emerging market leader. Areas that you will be owning are user behavior,  analytics, discoverability, growth, and adoption of features all across payments, experimentation and segmentation, and building and governing all our communications channels with our customers.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 10:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. Data Engineer (Streaming &amp; Batching)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b4375b0f-f936-4a0a-b5b1-241ad816e88a</link><description>About the Role

As GoPay is undergoing exponential growth, our data has followed the same growth curve. Thus, as an integral member of the Data Engineering team, you'll be at the epicenter of one of Southeast Asia's most coveted companies, and get to witness and solve the challenges that come with rapid scaling.

As our Data Engineer, you'll work closely with the business team and other data teams to improve the accessibility &amp; reliability of data while leveraging the largest-scale data processing technologies in the world. With your strong product-oriented vision and "Do It Yourself" mindset, you'll build data products that will deliver, model, and curate data for the entire Gojek Payments platform.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 15:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr Content Creator Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3f7e6e5c-3a28-411b-9b83-74ddcdfb97f8</link><description>About the Role 

As a Content Creator Specialist for Creative Labs creative team, you’ll take the wheel in ideation and executing creative campaigns for Gojek’s Social Media channel. Reporting to Creative Labs Creative Director, you’ll lead the discussion and development of creative ideations amongst various internal stakeholders, and oversee the production process from end-to-end - from its inception, design, development, to execution. You’ll get a front row seat (and get your hands dirty) in running impactful marketing campaigns through marrying business objectives and current trends, driving our beloved products to more corners of the world.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 06:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer, Infrastructure Engineering - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/464e09ca-f43c-4b2f-970f-4dceb9a68e05</link><description>About the Role

As our Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering Payments platform, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, contributing in critical projects, and participating in designing microservices to further evolve our platforms. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer Lead (BE) - Merchant Payments - 3872</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/dc6e5c16-0a17-46bf-8408-31b06c8c5134</link><description>About the Role

Merchant Payment is looking for passionate, entrepreneurial technical leaders with a drive of building scalable applications and teams. In this role you will be responsible for the overall delivery of your team and will interface very closely with business stakeholders and product stakeholders to deliver a cutting edge product aimed at improving customer experience on Payment. A strong sense of prioritization, deep technical expertise along with taking care of growth and development of the team, are essential in this role

</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 02:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer in Test - Mapan</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/af4160d0-3d9d-449c-8930-878f8645c9ef</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Software Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Mapan Product Development team based in Jakarta, Indonesia - a team whose efforts are especially catered to aid lower-income users attain additional income through our platform. You'll maintain product quality pre and post release, and employ TestNG, Selenium, and Appium  to bolster and enhance the team's products and deliver best-in-class products. You'll have ample opportunity to employ your technical expertise and clean coding skills to deliver tangible solutions that'll bring a positive socioeconomic impact to all who use our app.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer [iOS] - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e58b7fe9-f35e-4ba6-bd98-4667edbe0345</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Software Engineer [iOS]. In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay tech team based in Bangalore, India. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current users trends and preferences, and emerging technologies within the mobile engineering field, you will work alongside the product management team and cross-functional teams (Product Engineer, DevOps, Data, UX, QA) to improve overall code structure, and develop clear and sustainable iOS software components, and develop robust, well-designed software systems. Most importantly, your efforts will directly ensure our users get quality care and a seamless experience with our products &amp; services.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (Webdev) - KYC - Payment</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9678c95e-cca9-44bd-93ef-75e5cbc00a3c</link><description>About the Role

If you're looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team who enjoys building creative solutions for users, look no further. As a Full Stack Engineer for the Payments team, you'll design and implement highly-scalable, fault-tolerant products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses to process and manage their payment transactions. Your efforts will ensure that our family of Indonesian and Southeast Asian merchant-partners using GoFood and GoPay have seamless and enjoyable transactions, and are better positioned to grow their business, revenue, and profitability. After all, our merchant-partners are the heart of what we do. 


</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 09:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (IOS) - Payments - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/54f0e20c-3b7d-487c-8e42-a0e57e0c7af9</link><description>About the Role

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Software Engineer (iOS). In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay tech team based in Bangalore, India. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current users preferences, and emerging technologies, you will work alongside the product management team and cross-functional teams (Product Engineer, DevOps, Data, UX, QA) to improve overall code structure, and develop clear and sustainable iOS software components, and develop robust, well-designed software systems.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (Backend) - GoFood</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1e7087c6-1705-4d7d-880b-705911204e1c</link><description>About the Role

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you're ready to be our next Fullstack Engineer. This role will posit you to be an integral player in the Gojek’s Adtech team based in India &amp; Indonesia. With the knowledge of building scalable applications, current user preferences, and emerging technologies, you will be responsible for designing and managing applications, evolving and boosting productivity for the Ads &amp; Promo Platform team, and delivering a cutting edge product aimed at scaling the volume and vision of Gojek’s ads businesses. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (Backend) - Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c6e59467-c79b-4a64-ad6f-be2e7099d3e0</link><description>About the role: 

We are a data driven company - we take pride in being hypothesis driven; we measure the number of concurrent experiments we run and use experimental results to make product and business decisions. Our experimentation platform, Litmus, has made it possible to run targeted experiments on-demand to guide our super app, driver app product experience and business decisions.  We are now in the process of evolving it to the next level through automation at scale, statistical sophistication, reducing experiment rollout time by enabling new methods like A/A Tests, CUPED and building decision ready analytics systems. In this role as our Software Engineer for the Experimentation Team, you will be handed the reins to build A/B tests analytical metric intelligent experimentation platform for Gojek. You will be in charge of automating scalable &amp; intelligent business metric attribution systems, evolving architecture to ingest, pre-aggregate billions of clickstream events, provide real time querying capabilities scanning billions of rows. Working closely with backend engineers, data engineers and data scientists, you will get to contribute to the system that runs meaningful experiments for Gojek. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide APIs for Gojek millions of users and driver partners to use.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (Android) - Payments - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a7d3215f-a1df-414e-ba37-6db788dd20b5</link><description>About the Role:

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Android Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay team based in Bangalore, India. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current user preferences and trends, and emerging technologies in the mobile engineering field, you will work alongside the product management team and cross-functional teams (Product Engineer, DevOps, Data, UX, QA) to improve overall application performance, code structure, and develop robust, well-designed software systems. Your work will directly ensure our users get quality care and a seamless experience with our services.



</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer (Android) - Driver Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a06d22b8-4b91-4b27-8ead-80822a3ed755</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Driver Platform team, you take the wheel in overseeing Android Engineering at Gojek. Along with owning the entire life cycle of these projects, you will establish and evangelize the best engineering practices for your team to follow. Working closely with product managers, QA engineers, and designers, you will get to build world-class products and meet the technological needs of the Gojek's driver partners, ensuring they get the quality care and service that they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 06:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer - Infrastructure Engineering - Gopay - Bandung</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d98f8c83-ab9a-4fec-a721-1ab0ccd26de9</link><description>About the Role

As our Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering Payments platform, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, contributing in critical projects, and participating in designing microservices to further evolve our platforms. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e53ab3f8-fb81-4bba-b57a-7a4a3a4ed7e9</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 



</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 09:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c83605f5-f5b1-4769-80cd-b39a1e3658cf</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 07:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Social Media Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8d84d328-6fb1-402d-9c99-480c3b212c90</link><description>About the role: 
This role reports directly to the Head of Social Media &amp; Digital Content and works closely with the Brand team &amp; other pods to grow various social media channels and manage content production for GoPay marketing activities, leading a team of social media specialists.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SM, National Merchant Activation</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d178f58e-c7f7-43d8-bcec-ae477f94dafa</link><description>About The Role

National Merchant Activation Manager is responsible for planning and managing the overall Merchant Activation Activities with the primary goal of building targeted merchants to have sustainable transactions in the GoPay ecosystem.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 11:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior/Lead Golang Developer, Data Management</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2a6af775-c112-448a-aa71-f1eb0368da1d</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Lead/ Senior Software Engineer - Golang for the Data Engineering team. As Gojek is undergoing exponential growth, our data has followed the same growth curve. Thus, as an integral member of the Data Engineering team, you'll be at the epicenter of one of Southeast Asia's most coveted companies, and get to witness and solve the challenges that come with rapid scaling. 

In this role, you'll focus heavily on building and scaling a data platform that enables and delivers reliable, trustworthy, and approachable data to our users, as well as designing, developing, deploying frontend applications with a high sense of ownership. Additionally, you'll devise and manage our entire web infrastructure, and produce innovative solutions that our users will enjoy. Your software will deliver, model, and curate data that powers core data platforms throughout Gojek.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior UI Engineer - Customer Platforms</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/65868b95-f858-44e9-a029-de08d91565e4</link><description>About the Role 

Are you interested in building next gen collaboration tools alongside a world class engineering team? Or defining the best platform with a talented troop of engineers? Then, this may be the role for you. As a senior engineer in for the Ticketing Platform team, you’ll drive the internal platform customer experience vision alongside our design and product management team. The product vision is to build tools, processes and products that would integrate gojek’s immensely complex products with customers for support. You would be leading a team that would work with customer support operations to identify the strategy to improve and automate customer support.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 07:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Infrastructure Engineering - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/aa38638f-d4f3-4f6e-9220-f0ce31cc0bfe</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering Payments platform, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, enhancing the platform’s engineering strategy, mentoring a talented troop of engineers, driving critical projects, and designing microservices to further evolve our payments system. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 08:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Infrastructure Engineering - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a5816bb4-17dc-463a-8c49-9c3f01da75d6</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering Payments platform, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, enhancing the platform’s engineering strategy, mentoring a talented troop of engineers, driving critical projects, and designing microservices to further evolve our payments system. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 07:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Infrastructure - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/caef882c-a51b-4d0e-8868-30e1c66afdb3</link><description>About the Role

In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing heavily on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance and output to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Infrastructure - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b85f8091-a00d-4ee1-845d-a8a3ee88b14c</link><description>About the Role

In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing heavily on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance and output to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 09:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Developer Tooling - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/34a7e090-c338-4198-b285-45fbfa5b5908</link><description>About the Role

At GoToFinancial, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering team, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. 

You will take the wheel in building, operating, and maintaining our developer &amp; infrastructure platforms and tools - such as: developer portal, developer tools and common libraries to mention a few - empowering our entire engineering team with scale and extensibility in mind. With this team, you will be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 08:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Data Science Infrastructure</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d0ade463-d62d-4b7e-bd37-01f85f771e9a</link><description>About the role

As Nasi Goreng is to the people of Indonesia, engineers are to GoTo Financial: sustaining and nourishing the longevity of our business from the inside out. As our Data Science Engineer, you'll be an integral player within the Data Science Engineering team. You'll ensure our Data Scientists in the various GoToFinancial sub-teams have all the resources they require to achieve their goals. You’ll employ your stellar software engineering skills and expertise in the infrastructure operations field in efforts to productionize their processes. Your work will directly influence the performance of our Machine Learning and Data Science models throughout the company, and help in taking data oriented decisions in different interests of business growth, risk etc.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 08:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6157f291-bb10-4483-8a31-ad5f5a0ebe07</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Data Engineering team, you’ll take the wheel in overseeing Back-end Engineering at Gojek - designing and developing highly scalable, reliable, maintainable and fault tolerant systems for our Data Engineering team. Along with owning the entire life cycle of these projects, you will establish and evangelize the best engineering practices for your team to follow. Working closely with the data catalog team, data engineers and data scientists, you will get to contribute to the system that runs meaningful experiments for GoJEK. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide APIs for GoJEK’s millions of users and driver partners to use.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 10:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer (iOS) - Gopay KYC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/afdcee5b-8ce5-4ce2-af20-7a0fa1b9a585</link><description>About the Role

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Senior Software Engineer (iOS). In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay KYC tech team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current users preferences, and emerging technologies, you will work alongside the product management team and cross-functional teams (Product Engineer, DevOps, Data, UX, QA) to improve overall code structure, and develop clear and sustainable iOS software components, and develop robust, well-designed software systems.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer (Frontend), Infrastructure Engineering - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6d8c6e04-25d4-4df9-a921-196ce11a3cb6</link><description>About the Role

At GoToFinancial, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As Senior Frontend Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering team, you'll play an integral part in creating the best developer experience for our product engineers. 

You will take the wheel in building, operating, and maintaining our developer platform called GoPay.sh - empowering our entire engineering team with scale and extensibility in mind. With this team, you will be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 04:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer (Backend) - Payments - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/61ed9b5c-17c2-4649-a8b6-b5033e12478e</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly analytical team that enjoys building creative solutions for users, look no further. As our Software Engineer for the Payments Engineering group, you'll take the wheel in overseeing the design, development, and delivery of back-end products within your technical focus area. You'll work closely with a wide spectrum of engineering teams at Gojek, including the Payments, Transport, and Food streams. With a talented troop of fellow engineers and product managers, you'll build groundbreaking features and systems that scale millions of transactions and handle multiple terabytes of storage. The cherry on top: your efforts will contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 06:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer (Android) - Driver Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4e249806-8925-4a68-bacf-1be03185db13</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Driver Platform team, you take the wheel in overseeing Android Engineering at Gojek. Along with owning the entire life cycle of these projects, you will establish and evangelize the best engineering practices for your team to follow. Working closely with product managers, QA engineers, and designers, you will get to build world-class products and meet the technological needs of the Gojek's driver partners, ensuring they get the quality care and service that they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 09:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Infrastructure Engineering - GoPay - Bandung</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8fd037e4-b6f0-4559-a96f-f5b53faddab2</link><description>About the role

As our Senior Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering Payments platform, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, enhancing the platform’s engineering strategy, mentoring a talented troop of engineers, driving critical projects, and designing microservices to further evolve our payments system. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 11:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b00ad4da-f999-4d4d-a7bf-46ce48925f8f</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ab65ea06-3760-4510-9b1a-656a3219d664</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5e3bd3b1-576f-4dd3-8443-6fc778da2419</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer  - Developer tooling - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2cc318cc-976f-48d3-a9f6-7a6b19ad2d58</link><description>About the Role

At GoToFinancial, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As Software Engineer for the Infrastructure Engineering team, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for Indonesia’s leading digital payments platform. 

You will take the wheel in building, operating, and maintaining our developer &amp; infrastructure platforms and tools - such as: developer portal, developer tools and common libraries to mention a few - empowering our entire engineering team with scale and extensibility in mind. With this team, you will be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers, and contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Risk Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a5cc9a7a-fc2a-4694-8b9c-687e2b15255d</link><description>As our Senior Risk Analyst for the Merchant Platform team, you’ll take the wheel in identifying potential fraud risks that may pose a threat to the company, and developing risk mitigation strategies in our fast-expanding business. You’ll analyze, validate and optimize risk rules in order to deliver on target risk metrics. You’ll also act as a key fraud analyst in conducting deep and thorough analysis to address risk related issues. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our platform integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust and perception of Gojek, ensuring a safe platform our users can count on and love to come back to.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Researcher - Market Research (Quantitative)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3ec6ddb4-99b2-4862-b292-5a48e46c654c</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly analytical team, and an opportunity to ensure user insights are at the heart of Gojek driver’s experience, look no further. Fasten your helmet and climb onboard as a Senior Researcher - Market Research Lead for the Driver Platform team. You will be our go-to expert in quantitative research methodology to ensure driver insights are at the heart of our products. You’ll take the wheel in providing key insights to aid the development and execution of product design and overall business strategy. The folks in the product, design, data, and business team will be your companions on this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your quantitative, qualitative, and analytical research skills, getting us even closer to build the best platform for our driver partners.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 02:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Operations Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6a9dfad1-2df0-4b05-b3e8-e5f68fbde47c</link><description>About the role:

We are looking for someone with first-hand experience in defining and scaling complex strategic and operational initiatives to bolster our growth and product development in the Vietnam market. This person should have impeccable communication and interpersonal skills, and a passion for bringing order to chaos through methodical cross-functional alignment and rigorous execution. In this role, you will partner with leadership across the company to refine the needs of our Vietnamese customer base and bridge to our product teams. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 02:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Operations Consultant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f5619a6c-1982-4cfa-8d63-0f60e24f7721</link><description>About the Role

Take on specific challenges a Gojek business like Transport, Food or Logistics has, conduct a thorough analysis, and make recommendations. This is a high-ownership role where you are also expected to drive these recommendations to get it done. This role is perfect for someone who enjoys solving strategic problems, building consensus among different groups, and is comfortable with data analysis.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 09:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Manager, Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/823ee172-a754-436b-abba-857c15320c93</link><description>About the Role
As a Senior Product Manager for Data Platform involves you to have a pivotal role in enabling internal as well as external use cases on the platform, to ensure that we stay true to our goal of being the most preferred SuperApp for our customers. You will collaborate with leadership and cross-functional partners in driving the conceptual and technical development of data products.

As a key member of the Data Platform Product Management team, you'll collaborate closely with a talented troop of Product Engineers and Design folks, along with various Business, Product, and Analytics stakeholders within Gojek. Your efforts will directly enhance the overall velocity of Gojek's Product and Engineering teams, and shape the strategic direction of Gojek's Data Engineering function.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 15:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Manager, Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2080dd93-b702-4e0d-a305-f0c292049589</link><description>About the Role

As a Senior Product Manager for Data Platform involves you to have a pivotal role in enabling internal as well as external use cases on the platform, to ensure that we stay true to our goal of being the most preferred SuperApp for our customers. You will collaborate with leadership and cross-functional partners in driving the conceptual and technical development of data products.

As a key member of the Data Platform Product Management team, you'll collaborate closely with a talented troop of Product Engineers and Design folks, along with various Business, Product, and Analytics stakeholders within Gojek. Your efforts will directly enhance the overall velocity of Gojek's Product and Engineering teams, and shape the strategic direction of Gojek's Data Engineering function. We are open for both Jakarta and Bengaluru locations.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 04:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Manager- GoMart</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/59200a22-1a9e-410b-9c5e-921de8343eef</link><description>About the role: 

Gojek is looking for an entrepreneurial product leader to drive the vision, strategy and execution of the next stage in our Convenience &amp; Grocery products. We have built and grown GoMart to be the convenience delivery market leader in Indonesia but competition, the opportunity to innovate and - most important - doing more for our users is driving us to push our product further, faster.

As the Senior Product Manager for GoMart, you will take on a “founder” style role where an obsession for great user experience, thinking big while being hands-on and entrepreneurial spirit guide our path forward. Working together with a set of cross functional leads from Engineering, Design, Marketing, and Business you will craft a product strategy and roadmap that will quickly get a wholly reimagined grocery experience to MVP and beyond. 

</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Manager - Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/de247a53-50fc-4bb3-bc39-fc68fa27fe0b</link><description>About the Role

As a Senior Product Manager for Data Platform involves you to have a pivotal role in enabling internal as well as external use cases on the platform, to ensure that we stay true to our goal of being the most preferred SuperApp for our customers. You will collaborate with leadership and cross-functional partners in driving the conceptual and technical development of data products.

As a key member of the Data Platform Product Management team, you'll collaborate closely with a talented troop of Product Engineers and Design folks, along with various Business, Product, and Analytics stakeholders within Gojek. Your efforts will directly enhance the overall velocity of Gojek's Product and Engineering teams, and shape the strategic direction of Gojek's Data Engineering function. We are open for both Jakarta and Bengaluru locations.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 13:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Engineer - Bills and Pulsa</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f5e2c079-4224-4a41-adcc-1de342e1263a</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Product Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Digital Inclusion team based in Jakarta, Indonesia - a team behind GoTagihan product in Gojek app.  
You’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive group of users, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our products, and help millions users by making bill payments effortless. 


</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Designer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7aa30684-8f95-4291-98e9-f258801d3b25</link><description>About the Role

Product designers provide the user's point of view to the discussions and collaborate with the rest of the product team to ensure that users will end up with the best solution to the issue at hand. With a deep knowledge of how the technology works and interest in how users behave, the best product designers can answer any problem with a combination of well-defined flow, wireframes, information architecture, user journey, and/or storyboard.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Analytics - Merchant Lending (Jakarta Placement)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/56b54b49-2c99-4b90-b7ce-ffdfb9cccee7</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team with an opportunity to dive deep into product development/improvement, look no further. As our Product Analyst for Merchant Lending, you will be key in identifying opportunities by digging deeper into the data while understanding the goals &amp; metrics of the business. You will have a range of products that you would support in establishing the data funnels, visualizing them and a key insight provider to enhance them. Working closely with the product, engineering and the growth teams, you’ll shape the nature of our lending products to ensure our merchant partners are able to meet their short-term and long-term financial needs responsibly.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Analytics - Merchant Lending</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/81f2f572-9a33-4050-8e0b-93bb3a845619</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team with an opportunity to dive deep into product development/improvement, look no further. As our Product Analyst for Merchant Lending, you will be key in identifying opportunities by digging deeper into the data while understanding the goals &amp; metrics of the business. You will have a range of products that you would support in establishing the data funnels, visualizing them and a key insight provider to enhance them. Working closely with the product, engineering and the growth teams, you’ll shape the nature of our lending products to ensure our merchant partners are able to meet their short-term and long-term financial needs responsibly.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 09:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Analyst - Mapan</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f76c28e9-f669-409b-a185-20f908d80ae9</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Product Analyst, you will play a substantial role in the Product Development Group (PDG) team for the core Mapan products. In this role, you'll get to buy and sell online/offline experiences, knowledge distributions, and community practices via the products you oversee. You'll dive deep into the various metrics &amp; data available across the company, generate insights, run experiments, and create recommendations for the product &amp; business. As one of the few Senior Product talents in the company, your efforts will have a direct influence over our customer's product habits and values, and will roll out products that remove the friction from our users' daily lives.  


</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 14:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Platform Engineer - Containerization</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/91cf9913-514f-4337-9e6c-75481dcc4f50</link><description>At the Engineering Platform, Gojek; we are looking for passionate engineers responsible for building scalable PaaS offerings aimed at improving engineering experience for various product groups at Gojek. You will also be developing services, tools and platforms that provide distributed systems abstractions.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 09:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager, Merchant Engagement Strategy</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/09f121e1-d179-4275-863f-83ef04b4d32a</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Senior Manager, Merchant Engagement Strategy. As a Senior Manager Merchant Engagement - Strategy, you will take the wheel in defining the segmentation, planning as well as the execution program for millions of unmanaged merchants. You'll be working closely with Region and HQ team to create and improve the engagement strategies for our merchants.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager of Risk Data Science</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c08b60df-c549-4e70-8b3e-fccf0a3dcef8</link><description>About the Role

As a Sr. Manager of Risk Data Science, you will lead a team of data scientists responsible for risk models which protect GoPay and its customers. You will have the opportunity to work with rich data to derive new intelligence and use various data science techniques. 
You will drive strategic directions in your data science area and solve some of the most impactful and stimulating business problems in the payments space by partnering with leaders from Risk, product, and engineering. You will work in a fast-paced environment with direct impacts to the business.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager of Investor Relations</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/43b8ff01-4a88-4d4b-af5c-74cf9fb0bd9c</link><description>About the Role 

Join an expanding dynamic investor relations team to be our next Manager/Senior Manager, either based in Singapore or Jakarta. The role requires strong research and analytical skills to carry out deep-dive industry/business intelligence screening, fundamental analysis, and benchmarking disclosure with peers. It also requires strong communication skills to passionately engage with the sell-side and buy-side to build trust with capital markets. The new team member will be expected to lead quarterly/annual earnings preparation cycles to assist with smooth execution.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 06:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Lead Internal Communications</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/431648a2-e53b-492a-a3ee-291399fb4491</link><description>About the Role

Supporting Head of Internal Comms in actualizing Gojek’s objective of becoming a powerful global brand and world-class workplace through excellent internal communications practices and programs and interdepartmental collaboration that inform and engage employees at all levels. 

What success looks like: 
- Increased employee satisfaction toward Gojek internal communications practices and transparent culture
- Improved information intake and engagement
- Measurement tools: eNPS score, HR/PAC employee survey, townhall surveys, and focus group discussion results


</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 05:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior iOS Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/62fc54be-ab3b-4e2b-9169-08ac1977b00c</link><description>About the Team

As our Senior iOS Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable iOS software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 05:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior iOS Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3fbc61ac-2665-4e6e-bdb2-2c95c8c3d223</link><description>About the Team

As our Senior iOS Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable iOS software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 11:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Information Security Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/02d922a3-72e9-429d-af64-21a78e5232d1</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and a chance to hone in on your InfoSec skills, look no further. As our Information Security Engineer, you will be an instrumental player in the Product Security team. In this role, you will frequently utilize your coding and engineering expertise as a second-line engineer. Along with independently handling product security reviews, you will also perform manual and automated code reviews, conduct software security tests, oversee vulnerability assessments for cloud-based tech stack, and assist in technical documentation and scripting for automating DevSecOps. In our humble opinion, the coolest part of this role is knowing that your work will directly ensure the safety of our Gojek family.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 08:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Fullstack Engineer - Financial Services - Consumer Lending</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/501e7b21-1976-4b4f-9f3b-336856c190e4</link><description>About the Role

If you're looking to hone in on your engineering abilities and work on mission-critical high scalability distributed systems, this may be the job for you. As a Senior Software Engineer, your contributions will be crucial for development of financial products. You will help shape the future of our Consumer Lending products, and more importantly, help millions of users meet their financial needs responsibly.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 04:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Frontend Engineer - Merchant Platform - 7856</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/380bae9a-0d78-45eb-9286-c7978f0aac11</link><description>About the role: 

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Senior Frontend Engineer. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 08:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Frontend Engineer - Merchant Platform - 7855</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8662400d-64bc-473c-8fe5-04ee7c922fe1</link><description>About the role: 

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Senior Frontend Engineer. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 06:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Frontend Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8e15ce13-9a4e-4b0a-b0c5-8f310b3fa46b</link><description>About the Team

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Transport</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6267bf3a-0313-489b-a1d5-5349c573b0f4</link><description>About the Role

The Transport Engineering team at Gojek is responsible for providing the best-in-class experience to the customers of our ride and car businesses. A stellar team of cross-functional individuals is responsible for delivering top-of-the-line experiences across ordering, payments, navigation, and customer support. This team’s ownership spans technology products catering to millions of our customers across all our operating countries and is responsible for running the show for Gojek’s biggest business lines.     
We are looking for engineering leaders who have hands-on experience in building highly reliable distributed systems. As a Senior Technical Leader, you will create the vision for and build technical capabilities across backend systems, android, and ios apps. The successful candidate will have influence over the vision, features, and design of the critical systems and data used to drive the business. 


</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/bfd01910-cbb2-4141-b7f0-c9a171c49ad5</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our senior engineering manager. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 

</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/56ff8bad-6e65-4c81-81d9-9d2af579ed5e</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our senior engineering manager. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 

</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3ece0232-9ba1-4794-ba36-178955a5c264</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our senior engineering manager. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior DevOps Engineer - Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/00fd1ef0-de49-4bf0-b0dc-82eb427dddbe</link><description>About the Role:

Gone are the days of colourless tasks and idle work routines. As a Senior DevOps Engineer, you will play a critical role in the Gojek Data Engineering team. With the knowledge of managing and operating highly scalable distributed systems in the cloud, you will be responsible for designing and developing infrastructure as code, standardising operational tools, and evolving the data infrastructure to be more secure, scalable, and resilient. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of the engineers, and bring observability and reliability to the system. At Gojek, we’re bonded not only by our desire to make people’s lives easier but our shared enthusiasm for technology and the drive to make a social impact.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Warehouse Engineer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c1a68ce4-2ed5-4b83-b0a4-72c472d189cd</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Data Warehouse Upstream Developer, you’ll be an instrumental cog in GoPay’s Data &amp; BI wheel at Gojek that impacts the company’s analytical data infrastructure. You’ll take the reins in designing, developing, setting up, and managing our data infrastructure - one that needs to operate reliably at scale using a high degree of automation. 

You’ll also play an active role in ensuring the data governance policies and tools are implemented and adhered to. Product managers, engineers, BI/analytics, and data scientists will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have ample opportunity to flex your data/software engineering and communication skills, helping the team build a large, scalable data engineering platform that'll be utilize company-wide.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 09:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - Risk - Gopay -7898</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f91d388a-bc69-421f-9032-e26b8506abf7</link><description>About the Role 

As a data scientist in our Risk Data team, you will create data science models which protect GoPay and its customers. You will have the opportunity to work with rich data to derive new intelligence and use various data science techniques. You will partner with Risk, product and engineering stakeholders to identify and solve some of the most impactful and stimulating business problems in the payments space. You will work in a fast-paced environment with direct impacts to the business.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - Marketplace</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b41164ad-146f-4a0c-b96e-1facee838d17</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Data Scientist, you'll be an integral player in the Marketplace Data Science team based in Bengaluru. With the latest cutting-edge data science tech at your disposal, you'll focus your efforts on bringing our Marketplace systems (i.e. supply, demand, and pricing) to the next level, employing various quantitative techniques such as Machine Learning, Optimization, Simulation, Bayesian Techniques to drive asymmetric values for our businesses at Gojek. You'll be heavily involved in ideation, research, and building prototypes, and the folks in the Data Science Platform will bring your models to production. Your efforts will directly influence the stability and scalability of Gojek's Marketplace stream, and thus to company's top and bottom line as a whole.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - Marketplace</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2a8e43ea-6328-492a-be09-8903865312f4</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Data Scientist, you'll be an integral player in the Marketplace Data Science team based in Jakarta. With the latest cutting-edge data science tech at your disposal, you'll focus your efforts on bringing our Marketplace systems (i.e. supply, demand, and pricing) to the next level, employing various quantitative techniques such as Machine Learning, Optimization, Simulation, Bayesian Techniques to drive asymmetric values for our businesses at Gojek. You'll be heavily involved in ideation, research, and building prototypes, and the folks in the Data Science Platform will bring your models to production. Your efforts will directly influence the stability and scalability of Gojek's Marketplace stream, and thus to company's top and bottom line as a whole.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 06:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - KYC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9a36476b-cc70-43fe-a59e-430e2a901d67</link><description>About the Role

As a Data Scientist specializing in Computer Vision, you will be solving a variety of practical deep learning and computer vision tasks arising from different businesses in GoTo financial. You should be able to bring a new level of Deep Learning/Computer vision capabilities to the GoPay data science cloud and mobile platform.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - KYC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3db002c0-0502-434b-a439-07963419141b</link><description>About the Role

We are looking for an experienced data scientist who can lead a team of multi-displinary data scientists to create models which helps build a trusted KYC system. You will be working as part of the Data Science team at GoPay and will work closely with the business, product, and engineering stakeholders to identify and solve some of the most challenging business problems in the KYC space. You will have the opportunity to work in a fast-paced environment in a highly cross-functional team with business and product stakeholders and leverage our robust data infrastructure.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/825d3005-6396-41a3-b1d9-2530ea8fc229</link><description>About The Role 

We are looking for a data scientist to join our Data Science team at GoPay - you will create models which help grow the customer base and transactions in GoPay. You will work closely with the business, product and engineering stakeholders to identify and solve some of the most challenging business problems in the payments space. You will have the opportunity to work in a fast-paced environment in a highly cross-functional team and leverage our robust data infrastructure 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 10:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7a32e526-801d-494c-9d08-91de18f53506</link><description>About The Role 

We are looking for a data scientist to join our Data Science team at GoPay - you will create models which help grow the customer base and transactions in GoPay. You will work closely with the business, product and engineering stakeholders to identify and solve some of the most challenging business problems in the payments space. You will have the opportunity to work in a fast-paced environment in a highly cross-functional team and leverage our robust data infrastructure 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 07:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Engineer (Enterprise BI)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/dc0c261a-0cd5-4941-9782-7be784d82fb1</link><description>About the Role

As our Senior Data Engineer, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the Enterprise BI wheel of Gojek that directly supports the Finance, Accounting, and Tax (FAT) team in automating various processes and providing data required for finance reporting. You’ll focus a bulk of your time on developing and maintaining data automation for financial processes. The Data Warehouse, respective back-end and product, and ITBP finance support teams will be your companions on this ride. You’ll have ample opportunity to flex your SQL and Python programming skills, streamlining and automating various financial operations for the wider team to utilize.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 02:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Analyst - Cartography</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/14fd7920-4cb2-4e01-865e-e2ed3b8b5544</link><description>About the role

If you’re a Data Analyst at heart, this role is for you! You will be mining insights from the sea of data, building data products, and designing experiments with the ability to see the real-time impact of your contribution. The work will be focused on solving our map data management, map operations, and map SDK problems across Gojek, diving deep into some of the most challenging analytical problems in Cartography - The Map Experiences team. We have Product Managers, Engineers, Data Scientists and Map Operations teams that are eager to assist you through this journey.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Data Analyst - Cartography</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0b05871b-5ccd-43d5-9232-0f73763955e4</link><description>About the role

If you’re a Data Analyst at heart, this role is for you! You will be mining insights from the sea of data, building data products, and designing experiments with the ability to see the real-time impact of your contribution. The work will be focused on solving our map data management, map operations, and map SDK problems across Gojek, diving deep into some of the most challenging analytical problems in Cartography - The Map Experiences team. We have Product Managers, Engineers, Data Scientists and Map Operations teams that are eager to assist you through this journey.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 03:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Copywriter</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8486153a-65de-44ab-a346-df7a3d1dd981</link><description>About the Role 

As the Copywriter for Creative Labs, you’ll take the wheel to communicate ideas that inspire, inform, and captivate consumers. And you will execute creative copywriting for any campaign executing creative campaigns for Gojek’s vast array of products. Reporting to the Group Head of the Creative stream, You’ll get your hands dirty in executing marketing creatives, marrying insights from user behaviors and trends, and relatable content. However, showing the ability to identify and check in with the managers on the viability of approach options.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 09:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Cloud Infra Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/84f10ecf-9e8d-4903-98b5-446e6aa0c889</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Cloud Infrastructure Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing your efforts on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view. Your infrastructure and standardization designs will not only be implemented for the CE group alone, but throughout the Gojek ecosystem as a whole.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Cloud Infra Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/80146772-3f23-4796-b0c0-8be9d208e6ca</link><description>About the Role

In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing heavily on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance and output to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Business Intelligence - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6985e718-5a2d-413f-bfb6-b4d2fac07647</link><description>About the Role

As a Business Intelligence Analyst, you will be working with the Business and product team on supporting analytics and data products (automated dashboards, reports, alerts, and simulation tools) which will create business impact at scale! You would be helping GoPay at a level of detail that enables the stakeholders to identify and address critical issues and align deliverables according to the Team’s priorities and requirements.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior BI Analyst (Enterprise BI)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/193db481-b7fc-4cdb-8b33-11063cf259a2</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Senior Business Intelligence (BI) Analyst in our Enterprise BI practice. Based in Jakarta, Indonesia, you'll be an integral player within Gojek’s IT Enterprise Systems team under the CIO Organization. 
 
As our Senior BI Analyst, you’ll be instrumental in the Enterprise BI IT Business Partner (ITBP) wheel of Gojek that directly supports the all Enterprise Functions of Gojek which includes Finance, Accounting, and Tax (FAT), HR, Corporate Planning, MM, Procurement etc. team in automating various processes and providing data required for corporate and financial reporting. You’ll focus a bulk of your time on developing and maintaining data automation for corporate and financial processes. The Data Warehouse, respective back-end and product, and ITBP finance support teams will be your companions on this ride. You’ll have ample opportunity to flex your SQL and Python programming skills, streamlining and automating various corporate planning and financial operations for the wider team to utilize. 


</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Android Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/97efbd1f-5561-4744-bd0e-40b0134b04e2</link><description>About the Role

At Goto, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Android Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable Android software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Android Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/809db1ce-e08d-46a1-b443-b18b7ec9fadd</link><description>About the Role

At Goto, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Android Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable Android software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 10:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Account Payable Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f0016816-fe72-4a02-8c2b-19e40bdfc620</link><description>About the Role 

As our Senior Account Payable Specialist you will be a part of the team that is responsible for the day-to-day operational matters while dedicated to improving and implementing the organizational system, procedures and processes within the GoTo Group and its regional subsidiaries. You will be reporting to Gojek Account Payable Manager and collaborating closely with GoTo Group Finance &amp; Accounting and Treasury functions.

</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 08:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Account Manager (Merchant Payment - Offline)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/68914be9-2457-4bfa-b781-c3928670cf66</link><description>About the Role

You will be part of the business &amp; operations team accountable for delivering special projects across Offline Payment products (Gopay &amp; Card). Partnering with Device Management team, Marketing team and Product and Development Teams to execute strategies for highest priority products and solutions, for different segments of the merchant.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Account Manager - Online Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/96d9cf47-7f66-44df-be31-51802c2a58c4</link><description>About the Role

Sales in Midtrans plays an important role to acquire, execute, and maintain partnerships with the most strategic startup and offline-to-online (O2O) businesses in the company’s portfolio. You will assist the Commercial Department in sales functions, including end-to-end management and executing all partnerships' contractual assets that help drive the company's key business goals.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 08:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Engineer-Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8e0c3bfb-b68e-4398-ba78-c9ebbcf29c96</link><description>About the Role 

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding Cyber Security Engineer, look no further. As our Security Engineer for GoTo Financial, you’ll take the wheel in building and maintaining our security engineering program and. Along with conducting security engineering, you will be in charge of ensuring security best practices implementation within GoTo Financial's products and infrastructure. Working closely with data and engineering, you will get to provide a secure platform for our merchants, partners, and consumers. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide the best protection by having a high standard of information security!


</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Support Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5875caba-b679-404d-8c39-077073734eea</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your seatbelt and climb aboard if you are ready to be our Sales Support Manager. Based in Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam, you will be responsible to support our sales team to cater to Gojek merchants’ onboarding/ offboarding,  needs, as well as problem-solve their daily issues. You will work closely with other teams both within the region &amp; in HQ to problem solve onboarding issues (i.e: product teams, HQ sales team, VN Legal team, VN KYB team, etc).

</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 03:03:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Strategy Manager - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0f9bf2f0-d6e9-4328-941c-e3a97753a820</link><description>About the role 

Your main objective will be to provide the Nationwide GoPay Sales team with strategy, knowledge, &amp; sales tools that they need, so that they can know how well they are doing in achieving the company targets and how to close the gap. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Strategy Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b5422c76-3058-4a0c-bf50-6908d62b4d4d</link><description>As a Sales Strategy Manager, you will contribute to building strategic plans for the Midtrans Sales Team to support growth objectives while strengthening the business core to develop and maintain a competitive advantage.The role will also serve as the proxy for Ops, Marketing, and other functions in Midtrans and GoTo Financial to support better communication, planning, and execution moving forward.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 02:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Strategy and Excellence Head</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/01ee1713-2af1-4341-a38c-1d054af29858</link><description>About the Role

As our Sales Strategy &amp; Excellence Head, you will be the north-star of GoPay Sales Team, providing the guidance on where they stand, where they should go, and how to reach their destination. Your main objective will be to provide the Nationwide GoPay Sales team with strategy, knowledge &amp; sales tools that they need, so that they can know how well they are doing in achieving the company targets and how to close the gap. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Planning Manager - GoPay - #7061</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5db8b5bd-9c5c-44a0-aa6c-23189d47d513</link><description>About the Role 

As our Sales Planning Manager, you will be the key person to provide guidance for the sales team on where they stand and where they should go. Your main objective is to provide the nationwide sales team with the performance data that they need, so that they can know how well they are doing in achieving the company targets and so that they can devise the best strategy to win the market based on the data you provide. You will also be responsible to ensure that there is clear accountability between our merchants and their respective salesperson.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 08:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Excellence Senior Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6ba81750-3e88-4e3b-9aaa-0622a8b398fb</link><description>About the Role

Sales Excellence functions play a vital role in overseeing and improving the sales support process and implementing sales excellence to provide a wholesome, excellent experience for the merchants and partners in the Online Payments - Sales Department in Midtrans. Your role as the Sales Excellence Senior Manager will be to support the Sales Excellence team, with a primary focus on business process improvement to ensure the best fit with the company, standardizing processes to improve operations capabilities, and reviewing/evaluating and maintaining existing documentation (policies, procedures, process maps) that are consistent, updated and inline with the overall business direction. The function is intended to identify and evaluate gaps and execute improvements towards establishing more efficient day-to-day sales support processes and business processes under the Online Payments - Sales Department. If hired, you will do the document processes (SOPs making) and recommend improvements and evaluate the efficiency of changes made to our business processes. You will also help with socialization and training to ensure policy awareness and implementation across functions in the sales team and related departments or stakeholders. You will directly report to the Head of Sales Excellence in a dynamic, fast-paced environment within a rapidly growing organization.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales &amp; Marketing Head (Medan)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/834a1da8-02ec-42de-b54c-ed47487d145e</link><description>About the Role

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Sales &amp; Marketing Head (District Head) for Medan. As our District Head, you will play a pivotal role in curating and deploying strategies as well as doing analytics at the District and finding local insights. You will work closely with the sales, marketing, operations, and business analyst teams in your day-to-day tasks, and also develop and maintain strong relationships with the government, merchants, associations and various communities. On top of that, you will work collaboratively with all troops in the district as well as collaboration with the Region team to oversee overall operations and ensure strategic implementation including product changes and ensuring that everything that transpires is aligned with Gojek's goals &amp;values.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3a2e3473-1add-48fd-a7e1-40e0205ba4d2</link><description>About the Role

As our Risk Manager for the Merchant Platform team, you’ll take the wheel in identifying potential risks that may pose a threat to the company, and developing risk mitigation strategies in our fast-expanding business. You’ll analyze, validate, and optimize risk-related data to design and implement policies that will deliver target risk metrics while heightening the level of risk awareness within the company. You’ll also act as an advisor for risk-related matters, influencing functional stakeholders to implement other broad risk control strategies in their respective domains. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our platform integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust and perception of Gojek, ensuring a safe platform our users can count on and love to come back to. 


</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 08:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Manager - Account,Identity &amp; Abuse - 4994</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/20e3b175-99b3-4c1f-95ed-15caa0377f52</link><description>About the Role 

We are looking for exceptional fraud risk managers to identify potential fraud risk, develop mitigating strategies in our expanding business especially focused on account identity and verification, account takeover prevention and anti incentive abuse .  The role holder will be responsible for delivering on target risk metrics - by analyzing data and implementing risk rules - as well as influencing functional stakeholders to implement other broad risk control strategies. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 17:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Lead - Anti-Scam</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b2e867d4-9cc0-40e7-87c5-9a955ccf4702</link><description>About the Role 

A great opportunity awaits our Consumer Risk Lead who will take the wheel in identifying potential risk breaches and developing risk mitigation strategies in our fast-expanding business. Reporting directly to the Group Head of Risk, you’ll act as the stream's key analyst within the Trust &amp; Anti-scam domains, monitoring risk metrics and rules and developing a holistic approach in implementing risk management strategies. You’ll cultivate an effective risk culture within the organization, influencing functional stakeholders to implement other broad risk control strategies within their domains. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our platform integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust and perception of Gojek, ensuring a safe platform our users can count on and love to come back to.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 02:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Analyst - Policy and Process</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/bbec28d1-1718-46ac-8795-b55e2e6723fb</link><description>As our Risk Analyst for the Merchant Platform team, you’ll take the wheel in identifying potential fraud risks that may pose a threat to the company, and developing risk mitigation strategies in our fast-expanding business. You’ll analyze, validate and optimize risk rules in order to deliver on target risk metrics. You’ll also act as a key fraud analyst in conducting deep and thorough analysis to address risk related issues. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our platform integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust and perception of Gojek, ensuring a safe platform our users can count on and love to come back to.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Analyst - Acct, Identity &amp; Abuse - 4992</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/31dd60f9-a364-495e-a9cd-e2c02b6ac3be</link><description>About the Role

A great opportunity awaits our Consumer Risk Analyst who will take the wheel in identifying potential risk breaches and developing risk mitigation strategies in our fast-expanding business. Reporting directly to the Group Head of Risk, you’ll act as the stream's key analyst, monitoring risk metrics and rules and developing a holistic approach in implementing risk management strategies. You’ll cultivate an effective risk culture within the organization, influencing functional stakeholders to implement other broad risk control strategies within their domains. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our platform integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust and perception of Gojek, ensuring a safe platform our users can count on and love to come back to.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 02:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0d9d1bce-59ae-45fc-8b15-3a9cab5a1f9e</link><description>If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, data-driven team and an opportunity to hone your analytical skills, look no further. As our Risk Analyst, you will analyze data to identify and validate high risk users in the GoTo Financial ecosystem such as GoPay, GoPaylater, GoBiz, Midtrans and Moka, and etc. Armed with data analytics skills in SQL, Python, you will be in charge of investigation of fraud and complaint cases and build analytical tools such as dashboards and SOP to improve the process. Working within the Risk function, you will get to learn about risk analytics and fraud detection and management.  The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to make Trust and Safety a top priority at GoTo Financial.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Researcher Lead-Merchant Lending</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0c8b7c12-c99c-4450-8447-47e501ad4f00</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Researcher Lead. In this role, you will be an integral player within the Merchant Lending based in Indonesia. Focusing heavily on driving all research related task, you will communicate your findings to stakeholder , planning and evaluating research project. The folks in the product team will be your companions on this ride. Your efforts will directly influence to build customer centric product development.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Researcher</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d2ca564f-2f1b-464f-86d2-373518dc73a5</link><description>About the Role

If you are passionate about creating real business impact with the power of insights, you are in for a treat! As our Researcher in the Research &amp; Insights team in Gojek Vietnam, you’ll be the go-to person for market insights, and the voice of our users and driver partners, helping to solve a multitude of business problems. Your main objective is to ensure that good insights get to the right audience, are interpreted the intended way, and are maximizing return on investments for the business. On this ride with us, you can expect the folks from Marketing, Corporate Strategy, Operations, Product Development teams to be your companions on a daily basis. You’ll get ample opportunity to hone your craft in qualitative, quantitative, and analytical research by managing multiple research projects end-to-end.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Regional Sales Support Manager (Non Java) - GoPay - #7872</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/59d8088b-30d6-42b0-9110-172d424f9325</link><description>About the Role - One paragraph between 80 - 100 wordsAs our Regional Sales Support Manager, you will be responsible to support our SMB sales team to cater to GTF Merchants’ onboarding/offboarding needs, support them with analytics &amp; insights, as well as problem solve their daily issues. On top of that, you will act as the functional support to the District Sales Support Admins to help them find solutions to the problems they’re facing, and when required escalate to GTF SM, Sales Support in HQ to close the issues.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Regional Sales Support Manager (Java) - GoPay - #7871</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a1f8b79b-78ed-4f4e-844e-c80486f07ba0</link><description>About the Role - One paragraph between 80 - 100 wordsAs our Regional Sales Support Manager, you will be responsible to support our SMB sales team to cater to GTF Merchants’ onboarding/offboarding needs, support them with analytics &amp; insights, as well as problem solve their daily issues. On top of that, you will act as the functional support to the District Sales Support Admins to help them find solutions to the problems they’re facing, and when required escalate to GTF SM, Sales Support in HQ to close the issues.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Regional Sales Support Manager (Jakarta) - GoPay - #7870</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ececc0a9-30e3-49c4-8f40-85978465a8c1</link><description>About the Role - One paragraph between 80 - 100 wordsAs our Regional Sales Support Manager, you will be responsible to support our SMB sales team to cater to GTF Merchants’ onboarding/offboarding needs, support them with analytics &amp; insights, as well as problem solve their daily issues. On top of that, you will act as the functional support to the District Sales Support Admins to help them find solutions to the problems they’re facing, and when required escalate to GTF SM, Sales Support in HQ to close the issues.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 11:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Regional Consumer Engagement Associate - Bandung</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4ce93bc2-1eba-450d-839d-a7d85738a44a</link><description>About the Role

Gojek Central West Java offers an excellent experience for a talented leader to join our Gojek team based at Bandung office. You will be responsible for developing Gojek products by creating and implementing strategic marketing plans across various touch points namely visibility, partnership, and digital to name a few. You will also be responsible for the marketing funnel of Gojek products across the CWJ region aligned with the headquarter initiatives. You will work closely with the CE and cross functional team.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Teamer-Team6 Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/82d12dc8-5219-4dd8-a10e-b805d3574a79</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding information security, look no further. As our Red Team Specialist for GoTo Financial, you’ll take the wheel in ensure product security for GoTo Financial. Along with Perform a thorough documentation on how vulnerabilities were exploited, you will be in charge of assist in identifying, tracing and neutralizing the active threats. Working closely with Blue Team, you will get to manage unique security incidents. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to create project with higher degree security assessments.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Teamer-Team6 Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/641e22ba-1d05-4088-a135-c7dd6b460532</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding information security, look no further. As our Red Team Specialist for GoTo Financial, you’ll take the wheel in ensure product security for GoTo Financial. Along with Perform a thorough documentation on how vulnerabilities were exploited, you will be in charge of assist in identifying, tracing and neutralizing the active threats. Working closely with Blue Team, you will get to manage unique security incidents. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to create project with higher degree security assessments.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>QA Engineer - Payments- Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4385126d-3bbb-4a53-90b0-1d838c05ab3f</link><description>About the Role 

As our Senior QA Engineer for our GoPay team based in Bangalore, India, you'll take the wheel in overseeing Gojek's payment experiences. With deep knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current user preferences and trends, and emerging technologies in the mobile engineering field, you'll drive end-to-end testing efforts, design new test suites, and execute test cases to enhance the development and success of the product within your team. You'll be part of a fluid, fast-paced, and agile team, where the latest cutting-edge internet and software technologies are at your disposal. Your efforts will enhance the durability and efficiency of automation tests done by the wider Engineering team, getting us even closer to our ultimate goal of creating a seamless app that will transport Gojek to all corners of the globe.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>QA Engineer - Money Management</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b65bf62b-82d1-443f-a546-802081117f3b</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our QA Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Bills and Pulsa team based in Jakarta, Indonesia - a team behind GoTagihan product in Gojek app. 
Your main objective will be to ​drive​ end-to-end testing efforts and be responsible for​ the​ product within your team. Best yet, you will have the opportunity to flex your automation testing skills, getting us even closer to our ultimate goal of creating a seamless app that will transport Gojek to all corners of the globe.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 05:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Management Specialist (Go-Mart)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7e71d650-a975-4c6e-9306-79fa382c5b4d</link><description>About the Role

They say no man is an island - a notion that holds particularly true for this role. As our Project Management Specialist, you’ll manage multiple exciting projects &amp; business initiatives across GoMart. From creating overall planning, execution, and monitoring. Your efforts will help us improve GoMart’s service performance and ultimately allow us to provide great services because of the delightful experiences to our customers, merchants and driver-partners.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 04:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Security Engineer - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6fc10e72-bba2-4584-bee4-9d1dc9d07129</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding Product Security, look no further.As our Product Security Engineer for Merchant Platform, you’ll take the wheel in building and maintaining our product security program and. Along with conducting product security, you will be in charge of ensuring security best practices implementation within the Merchant Platform product and infrastructure. 

Working closely with data and engineering, you will get to provide a secure platform for our merchants, partners, and consumers. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide the best protection by having a high standard of information security.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 11:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Security - Internship</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e2fae0d4-b21d-4f33-a358-04e2ef698617</link><description>About the Role

Gojek is looking for talented, highly motivated university students for our Product Security team to help increase the security posture across Gojek. Our future talent will be interns as Information Security. You will wear many hats as you jump into a fast-paced environment and produce results. We value an open culture, like-mindedness &amp; appreciate people from varied security backgrounds and hence we are most willing to work with growth mindset people. You can be part of the journey making path-breaking outcomes that will influence not only your aspirations to lead a career within Information Security but also impact the achievement of Gojek’s mission. 


</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 07:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Security - Internship</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/92d6809b-a3f7-485a-83ee-318118516b18</link><description>About the Role

Gojek is looking for talented, highly motivated university students for our Product Security team to help increase the security posture across Gojek. Our future talent will be interns as Information Security. You will wear many hats as you jump into a fast-paced environment and produce results. We value an open culture, like-mindedness &amp; appreciate people from varied security backgrounds and hence we are most willing to work with growth mindset people. You can be part of the journey making path-breaking outcomes that will influence not only your aspirations to lead a career within Information Security but also impact the achievement of Gojek’s mission. 


</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 07:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Researcher-Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3fec0d27-4354-4b08-a20e-a3bd377f7e38</link><description>About the Role

"If I have seen further, it is by standing on the shoulders of giants." – Isaac Newton. To innovate, you need to collaborate and build ideas from one another in order to progress. If you are passionate about learning, collaboration and utilizing knowledge and insights to drive innovation, the role of Merchants Product Research at GoTo Financial may be for you. As a product researcher in GoTo Financial, you will play an instrumental role in building merchant products that inspire growth for its users: entrepreneurs and business operators. Your main objectives will be to plan and execute research projects and present them to stakeholders. Your manager will work with you to develop your skills and knowledge and to ensure the quality of the research. Product managers and designers will be your main companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your hybrid of quantitative and qualitative research skills, and drive impact on product decisions as a thinking partner for our stakeholders


</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Marketing Manager - Money Management (#7481)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d83ef92c-c7db-48f1-b789-b15cb88bee24</link><description>About the role

This role reports directly to the GoPay Head of PMM Money Management with the goals to build a strong foundation of overall GoPay penetration through liquidity, money transfer, bill payment, investment and digital banking initiatives. This role works closely with Money management cross functional team (business strategy, product, growth, research, analyst, corporate affair, brand, etc) to manage end to end marketing initiatives with the aim of building GoPay to become the hub of users’ money management.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 07:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Marketing Manager - GoKasir - 7830</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ada4ce97-7f4f-4491-9506-2c1f10b9441f</link><description>About the Role

As a Product Marketing Manager - GoKasir for the Commerce Enablement team, we are looking for a passionate and impact-driven person that can lead a team and develop a strong marketing strategy that can contribute to a significant impact on the business.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 03:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Manager 2 - Communication Systems</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/284b7c32-32dd-4bd1-8ca6-5c4cda555218</link><description>About the Role

When it comes to our customers, communication is the only touchpoint that wins or loses them. Whether it is a notification on the app or a nudge outside of it, the way we communicate orchestrates the action of our users, drivers, and merchant partners. This is where you come in.

As a Product Manager in the Marketing &amp; System Communications Product team, your capabilities will feed into the way we interact with end users across different touchpoints (within the app as well as outside). You will partner with our marketing, CRM, and other core product teams (Transport, Food, Logistics, Groceries) to help solve for customer acquisition, onboarding, engagement, retention, and monetization. But wait! This is not a job for the light-hearted. You will need to be strategic and creative in the way you build platforms and have a high bias for action for landing solutions—and, most importantly, put customers first.

To succeed in this role, you will be helping to shape the overall direction for the team as well as roll up your sleeves to execute key deliverables. You would ensure that product judgments are based on strong sound rigor and in-depth investigation and value data over opinions. You should also know to look beyond the surface level when it comes to data/research and separate wheat from the chaff. You need to have exceptional communication and stakeholder management skills as this role need you to collaborate with, manage expectations of, and align stakeholders across functions.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 12:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Manager - Merchant Experience (Internal Tooling)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5bacda9a-ba99-4d60-bd36-d1a72bda3b11</link><description>About the Role

In the GoPay ecosystem we deal with 3 primary stakeholders, Customers, Merchants and Payment Providers. In this role you will be working on the internal tooling aspect for Merchants. Which will be working closely with the Ops, Product and Technology teams as well as other stakeholders.

We are looking for a quick-learning, self-driven, and motivated Product Manager who obsesses over merchant problems to define the product vision and build products to scale. You look at every problem with the user’s lens and come up with the most effective and elegant solutions. Working alongside other Product Managers, BI Analysts and Product Engineers we are focused on building newer product flows to help provide the smoothest experience to our Merchants and our internal teams.

 As an incumbent of the role, you would be responsible for automating SOPs for critical use cases such as onboarding, dispute management/refunds, settlements and merchant communications. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 11:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Designer - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/49cc77e2-db57-4638-a360-ee11efe7c572</link><description>About The Role 

Are you someone who's looking to solve problems that matter? Are you someone who thrives on the balance of business goals and users' needs? Are you looking to work with people who see failures as growth opportunities? This opportunity might be for you! 

The Merchant Platform team is looking for a Product Designer to join us in our efforts to build the next generation merchant platform. The Merchant Platform team is responsible for the core user experience across the different merchant products like GoBiz app and the GoBiz Dashboard. Product designers provide the user's point of view to the discussions and collaborate with the rest of the product &amp; business team to ensure that users will end up with the best solution to the issue at hand.

You will be part of a team of designers working to simplify and design for  complex problem areas of payouts, reporting, merchant onboarding, account &amp; user management. For your assigned problem area you will be responsible for product design and collaborating with others on the team for creating a seamless merchant experience.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Designer - Merchant Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1dce1b55-d161-419f-9c7c-31116222cf96</link><description>About the Role 

We are looking for a product designer with solid front-end engineering background in your previous role and is familiar with technical documentation to help us on building a centralized documentation center for developers. The ultimate goal of this project is to accelerate partners and the devs community to integrate and seamlessly build payment products on top of our payment platform, which will strategically strengthen our position as a leader in the industry.

You will also be able to take care of more than one product/project to ensure you’re always challenged and developed. As a leader in the payment industry, we are constantly revitalizing our product lineup and innovating. 

As an independent product designer, you’ll work closely with the product manager, engineers, writer, researcher, and business team with minimum guidance from the design lead/manager. You’ll provide the user’s point of view to the discussions and collaborate with the rest of the product team to ensure that users will have the best solution to the issue at hand. 

</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Producer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d392ada0-99b4-4bdc-8071-b0586e0cfbe7</link><description>About the Role 

It's the role for you who's creative as well as detail-oriented. In this role, you will coordinate and manages many aspects of a video production process from start to finish. In a nutshell, a producer may help with creative direction, setting a budget, writing scripts, organizing logistics, deadlines, and communicating with the team each step of the way.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 07:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Procurement System Support Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9b59a2bb-5a90-4c12-9e7b-09ab6a878ca6</link><description>About the Role

As our Procurement System Support Analyst, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the IT Business Partner (ITBP) wheel of Gojek that directly supports the Procurement and Finance Accounting and Tax (FAT) team in performing their daily activities, providing them with accurate and timely support. You’ll also collaborate with technical support, data analysts, and other stakeholders in handling day-to-day inquiries, providing consultation support, and helping to resolve their respective issues. The support your team provides in the Procurement and FAT platform will guide their decision-making process and steer the trajectory of the company’s business and financial endeavors.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Procurement Specialist - Offline Marketing</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/38b161a5-41f7-4d75-8d05-8771cdd951b7</link><description>About the Role

As our Procurement Specialist in the Marketing Sourcing Category, you’ll be an integral player within the Procurement team based in Jakarta. We oversee all Procurement things related to Marketing and Sourcing Category. Specifically, we do sourcing activities that relates to goods/ services in several categories with nature of procuring Marketing related i.e Above the line and Below the line, knowing about the details of marketing area Online, Offline, Digital Platform, Research and working with cross business units who require the such product/ services nature.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 03:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Principal Technical Architect - Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/56fdc06d-92ed-4e6d-8554-7c06525b1724</link><description>About the Role 

You will play an essential role in developing products and executing business strategies. You will be working very closely with the business development manager, product manager, and engineers to evaluate 3rd party vendors, available technology choices, conversion of product roadmap into engineering execution plan, selection of technology infrastructure, frameworks and libraries, architect and design technology solutions and work with engineers and quality assurance team for timely quality deliverables. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 05:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Principal Technical Architect - Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/472e75d2-2f95-4c95-8075-99a39559deb8</link><description>About the Role 

You will play an essential role in developing products and executing business strategies. You will be working very closely with the business development manager, product manager, and engineers to evaluate 3rd party vendors, available technology choices, conversion of product roadmap into engineering execution plan, selection of technology infrastructure, frameworks and libraries, architect and design technology solutions and work with engineers and quality assurance team for timely quality deliverables. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 09:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pricing &amp; Supply Business Analyst, GoFood</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3888f0ed-8188-48bc-807d-d632cfd438a1</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Pricing &amp; Supply Business Analyst. In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoFood Strategy &amp; Planning team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. You'll take full ownership of various pricing and supply levers, including customer pricing, driver pricing, incentives, and allocation, devising and implementing pricing &amp; supply enhancements with cross-functional teams along the way. You'll have a direct impact on the trajectory of GoFood's growth and profitability, ensuring the business maintains its market leadership in Indonesia and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PPGR Transport Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/941fe72a-83c3-4e46-a393-59d219f429e7</link><description>About the Role

This position will lead the advocacy for transport and logistics products to the key stakeholders and policymakers from various ministries. The role also serves as an internal advocate that ensures that the Transport and Logistic team can mitigate regulatory and policy risk. On top of that, the role will drive Gojek to expand networks through collaboration and partnerships. Your efforts will ensure that Gojek maintains its commitment towards the government, driver-partners, and industry associations. 


</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PPGR Corporate Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e8e8ed28-e7f1-49d0-8025-8b09afb7255e</link><description>About the Role

As a  PPGR Corporate Manager, you will help shape public policies that affect GoTo and its group of companies through engagement with the government and relevant stakeholders. Your understanding of how business operates combined with your experience in navigating and managing policy issues and ability to build and nurture government relations will support the PPRG team in addressing challenges that include business competition, merger and acquisitions and taxation. To this end, you will have to work with various government agencies, non-profit groups and other institutions while coordinating with internal business teams to ensure alignment. Your work will impact GoTo’s growth through greater public policy awareness among its important stakeholders. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 10:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Performance Executive - People and Culture</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9c0d94d2-5bac-4778-b48e-4c2a0e2024b7</link><description>About the Role

If you’re located at Jakarta or India, and looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding planning, design and delivery of the performance and promotion program across Gojek, look no further. As our Performance Executive, you’ll take the wheel in turning the data output from the program into insight to enable us to grow and develop the performance of all our people. This role is pivotal to the smooth running and success of this team and work on a broad variety of areas within the small team including communication, data analysis and basic project coordination.  

Along with design and deliver communications from the PAC Performance team to employees at all levels and across/within PAC, you will ensure Gojek employees &amp; cross-functional PAC stakeholders are familiar with the overall  mission and vision of the P&amp;A team and receive timely updates about the format, process, timelines, and policies related to a performance review cycle. Working closely with PAC Data team, you will get to you will be in charge of help support the team to analyze performance data and transform data into readable, goal-driven reports for continued innovation and growth and to enhance the impact of performance review cycles. The cherry on top: you’ll be project coordinator for the program and play a key role in the execution of the Performance Cycle plans, and will help keep performance plans on schedule working toward high efficiencies and flawless execution.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 11:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Operations Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ec07ae7f-a6d4-4a17-8f95-9b7431eb6f15</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and come aboard if you’re ready to be our People Operations Lead. In this role, you will be an integral player within the People Operations team based in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. We are looking for an individual who excels working in a dynamic and fast-paced environment, is result-oriented, is eager to develop themself, eager to champion various HR initiatives for GoTroops in Vietnam and global markets, and passionate about providing delight to employee experience. This role handles the end-to-end People Operations activities and streamlines HR processes to optimize workflow efficiency, effectiveness, and productivity.

</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 06:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Business Partner (Commercial &amp; Regional)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c21612f4-b7d7-4456-874a-ad3e7851ade3</link><description>About the Role

As our People Business Partner in the Commercial and Regional teams, you'll partner with various business leads within the company to gather insights about and devise effective strategies to resolve people-related issues, achieve business objectives with maximum productivity, and design integrated, meaningful, and enjoyable people experiences in the region. You’ll dive deep into understanding our ecosystem of driver-partners, merchant-partners, and users in Indonesia, and you will drive strategic problem-solving in numerous people areas.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Business Partner - India Based</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/fbc59c3b-f333-47a7-9a81-e2eb8036f0e9</link><description>About the Role 

As our People Business Partner, you'll be a seasoned and strategic People and Culture (PAC) thought partner to our Gojek Engineering team. Like a superhero, you'll trade between business imperatives and the needs of our GoTroops, contributing hands-on efforts at the strategic level in partnership with relevant client groups, mostly at the executive rank and above. This is an individual contributor role. You'll get ample opportunity to work on a variety of global projects, acting as a thought-leader by sharing your knowledge, experience, and people-related best practices among the broader PAC team across the Gojek ecosystem.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>People Business Partner</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0c0218c4-992d-41a3-84d5-8d8c50a0b9ff</link><description>About the Role 

As our People Business Partner, you'll be a seasoned and strategic People and Culture (PAC) thought partner to our Financial Services team. Like a superhero, you'll trade between business imperatives and the needs of our GoTroops, contributing hands-on efforts at the strategic level in partnership with relevant client groups, mostly at the executive rank and above. Starting as an individual contributor, your role may evolve into leading a team of one or more People Business Partners down the road. You'll get ample opportunity to work on a variety of global projects, acting as a thought-leader by sharing your knowledge, experience, and people-related best practices among the broader PAC team across the Gojek ecosystem.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 12:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Payroll Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/19de0831-d0cf-48ee-b1ee-b7b3464e766a</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and come aboard if you’re ready to be our Payroll Specialist. In this role, you will be an integral player within the People Operations team based in Bangalore, India. We are looking for an individual who excels working in a dynamic and fast-paced environment, is result-oriented, is eager to develop him/herself, eager to champion various HR initiatives for GoTroops in India and global markets, and passionate in providing delight to employee experience. This role handles the end-to-end payroll activities and involves streamlining of HR processes to optimize workflow efficiency, effectiveness, and productivity.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Merchant Event &amp; Community Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e4a5202b-4b80-42d6-9172-01c96fe00be6</link><description>Gone are the days of colorless tasks and idle work routines. As Merchant Event and Community Intern, you will be a remarkable player in our hyper growing solutions for SME’s, GoKasir. Focusing heavily on the education and engagement roles, you will operate offline/online events, moderate contents through community channels, and reporting the impact in efforts to empowering our Mitra Usaha.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 03:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Merchant Engagement Specialist - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/06759703-09a8-4c44-82de-d9f5026feea3</link><description>About the Role

As part of the Merchant Engagement team, you will be focusing on providing the best customer experience to all non-AM Merchants during their journey in Moka POS and GoStore. To strive and succeed, you are expected to support &amp; provide the best solution for merchants if they face any issues. Thus, you need to have extremely strong product knowledge, communication, sales &amp; negotiation skills, and the ability to help merchants to solve issues are imperative to becoming a successful Merchant Engagement Specialist.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Merchant Engagement Lead - 7492</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c480af32-4a53-4266-824a-f01939a74e62</link><description>About the Role

As part of the Merchant Engagement team, you will be a crucial figure of the merchant lifecycle in driving engagement strategies &amp; execution initiatives throughout our Non-AM merchants journey. As the Merchant Engagement (ME) Lead, you will work with a passionate team of agents to innovatively improve merchants’ engagement &amp; assist them towards achieving business growth.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 11:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Product Management, Sanctions Platform-Payment Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/25c678e8-5d50-4315-85c6-5a11c1dbfbbf</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to hone your product management skills, look no further. As a PM for Sanctions platform you will be responsible for building state of the art products/platforms that allows Gopay to fight fraud and make our products safe and trustworthy for our customers. You will be working with seasoned risk leaders, data scientists, and business stakeholders in driving the Ml driven new age risk mitigation solutions for payments business. Your efforts will help position Gopay as the most trusted payment method for customers and merchant partners.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 11:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Product Management, KYC platform - Payments Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/03469aef-1fca-45bd-a3bb-edec14b04e3e</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to create massive impact, look no further. In this role you will be responsible for creating OneKYC platform in GoTo that allows us to verify real identities of our customers and help us build trust with them and give them seamless access to vast use cases related to payments and financial services. OneKYC platform will not be limited to Payments &amp; GTF but also wider use-cases in GoTo across customers and merchants. You will be working with teams in Indonesia, India &amp; Singapore including Data, Compliance and Regulations, Business and other Product units in GoTo that leverage the capabilities of the platform and help shape the future roadmap. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Product Management - Consumer Lending</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d5022fa6-273a-4229-920c-304165ce579b</link><description>About the role

You’ll take the wheel in building lending products for consumers across the GoTo ecosystem. Along with overseeing product development processes that are used by Own personal OKRs and understand the team, you will be in charge of delivering scoped features with guidance from Head of Product. Working closely with the engineering and design team, you’ll shape the nature of our lending products to ensure our customers are able to meet their short-term and long-term financial needs responsibly.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 08:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Product Management - Consumer Lending</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5692b158-2e5e-4839-8a0e-c25593efa463</link><description>About the role

You’ll take the wheel in building lending products for consumers across the GoTo ecosystem. Along with overseeing product development processes that are used by Own personal OKRs and understand the team, you will be in charge of delivering scoped features with guidance from Head of Product. Working closely with the engineering and design team, you’ll shape the nature of our lending products to ensure our customers are able to meet their short-term and long-term financial needs responsibly.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 09:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal Supervisor</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/023e3396-98d2-47e0-9bf8-e1a6ed0a298d</link><description>About the Role

A great opportunity awaits our Legal Supervisor who will represent Gojek and the Legal Team for a majority of its legal and business advisory. Together with the Product Legal Stream, you’ll run points for all legal matters that are related to all Gojek’s on demand business streams, primarily Food, Transport, Commercial and Merchants.

You will also manage other pivotal streams, international projects and other initiatives that are demanded by Gojek’s business. In view of our recent merger with Tokopedia, this position will play a pivotal role in the integration and product development and other commercial initiatives as well. As part of the award-winning legal team, you will be involved in various legal tech related works such as drafting commercial contracts and providing legal advice on various product development by the business team.  


</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 09:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer, Machine Learning Operations - GoFood</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6766139d-e93e-405d-832d-ca95f8d7d430</link><description>About the Role

Don your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Machine Learning Engineer. In this role, you will get to design and build Gojek's machine learning infrastructure and platform. Your efforts will be critical in ensuring rapid and reliable Machine Learning products and functionality for our consumer app and behind-the-scenes efficiency. In our humble opinion, the coolest part of this role is that your work will directly influence the production quality systems at all stages of the Machine Learning lifecycle for Gojek.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer (Fullstack) - Data Engineering</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cc09484e-ca56-4707-9935-57d74b5a43a5</link><description>About the role: 

You will be the part of the Data Engineering Frontend team responsible for building the next-gen self-serve console portal, since most of Gojek internally relies on it, hence the responsibility increases to provide high-quality products.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 04:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer - Data Engineering</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6cc72ce8-754f-4b55-ac3d-34330d20fb6c</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Software Engineer for the Data Engineering team, you’ll take the wheel in overseeing Back-end Engineering at Gojek - designing and developing highly scalable, reliable, maintainable and fault tolerant systems for our Data Engineering team. Along with owning the entire life cycle of these projects, you will establish and evangelize the best engineering practices for your team to follow. Working closely with the data catalog team, data engineers and data scientists, you will get to contribute to the system that runs meaningful experiments for GoJEK. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide APIs for GoJEK’s millions of users and driver partners to use.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 10:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1da5286e-73dc-4e71-b978-0e42a91587d6</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 08:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/181a830a-77ea-405f-8628-db4b396e81e5</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/10d74458-7a04-4c01-901c-d4d2e8dc8c92</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Product Manager, Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/68d2ac74-4c1f-40b2-8c4f-c31e2bd32a0e</link><description>About the Role

Every business revolves around money, as it is one of the most important parts in business. As our PM on Financials based in Jakarta, you’ll manage products that facilitate all payment transactions that are to be settled to merchants. The scale will be upwards of a million transactions on a daily basis and the key products that you will be managing would include the merchant wallet, calculation and deduction engines. These products form the backbone of the Merchant Platform and are critical for Gojek's ability to monetize from merchants. You will be responsible for building the roadmap and vision around how to scale the work of our merchant finance team that enables us to grow. The folks in the engineering, business, design, and research team(s) will be your companions on this ride. Your efforts will directly influence the happiness, stickiness and trust of merchants on our platform and for other product groups in Gojek, these products will be invaluable to drive their monetization and revenue realization efforts.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 02:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Product Manager - Merchant Experience</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/bc1d0538-6b5d-4d7d-9836-4e02db431b3a</link><description>About the Role

In the GoPay ecosystem we deal with 3 primary stakeholders, Customers, Merchants and Payment Providers. In this role you will be working on the Merchant Experience charter, which is part of the Merchant Payments vertical in the company. 

We are looking for a quick-learning, self-driven, and motivated Product Manager who obsesses over merchant problems to define the product vision and build products to scale. You look at every problem with the user’s lens and come up with the most effective and elegant solutions. Working alongside other Product Managers, Designers, Researchers, BI Analysts and Engineers we are focused on building newer product flows to help provide the smoothest experience to our Merchants. 

As an incumbent of the role, you would be responsible for leading with a close sense of the merchant’s voice and crafting solutions which aim to solve their pain-points.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 11:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead of Savings - Money Management #6560</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f95a62e3-db34-4809-866f-570c669f972a</link><description>About This Role :
As part of Money Management POD focusing on Savings, you will play an important role in setting the strategy &amp; growth plan of the POD. You’ll take the wheel in managing the POD’s strategy-to-execution - from consumer research, OKRs, to strategy planning to create the most impactful business solutions for our users and strategic partners, steer the strategy and delivery of growth targets for the team responsible for allowing a customer to manage their money and linked sources of money. This would include the linked accounts, balances, digital account openings, history, categorisation of expenses, insights and actionable recommendations, default in/out channels for payments.
Throughout this exciting experience, you’ll build relationships with internal and external stakeholders, from product, marketing, research, and operation team among others to meet the fast-paced nature of the financial technology industry.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead IT Auditor</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b70e8aa2-6a57-429f-8397-3d2c689e510c</link><description>About the Role 

In GoTo, the growth of our business is continuously challenged by the fast pace of technology development and regulatory changes.  As the IT Audit Lead, you will be a valued member of the Internal Audit Function with broad discretion in developing a strong foundational technology assurance framework.  You will grow both technically and professionally through interaction with one of the most dynamic and driven management teams, exposure to the latest technologies, and observe firsthand on tech-enabled business strategy.  
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 05:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead iOS Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f665a797-9494-4f64-866c-46a4ea14ce51</link><description>About the Role 

As our Lead iOS Individual Contributor, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable iOS software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead iOS Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/dd9f8b5f-763a-499f-9647-32d6beb6f440</link><description>About the Role 

As our Lead iOS Individual Contributor, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable iOS software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Growth Analyst - Financial Services</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/892f78a6-d649-4f35-8733-736f5b8f8d6e</link><description>As a Lead Growth Analyst on the Financial Services Platform, you will be responsible to utilize our voluminous data to improve acquisition, activation, retention, and loyalty for our Financial Services products. You will be driving the analytics projects of the Growth team across different products, ultimately enabling the Financial Services team to make data-driven decisions. You will have ample opportunity to flex your analytics and project management skills, getting us even closer to the financial inclusion of all Indonesian. You will be based in the Jakarta office.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Frontend Engineer - Merchant Platform - 7854</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/da4b6b28-c4fa-4f40-a192-0df841d376c0</link><description>About the role: 
Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Lead Frontend Engineer. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Frontend Engineer - Merchant Platform - 7846</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6dd39e70-bbdc-4016-aea7-95a2fe9417f2</link><description>About the role: 
Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Lead Frontend Engineer. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Frontend Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/73282012-2bc2-4be9-a777-59142a3b80cf</link><description>About the Role

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Senior Software Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 05:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Front-end Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cba44b28-af19-4bee-b2b8-d0309fc30fcd</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Front-end Engineer for the Commerce Enablement group, you’ll be part of the team building some of the most critical products for Gojek’s merchant-partners. Working alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry across design, product, and engineering, you’ll focus your efforts on designing and implementing products for a massive network of small, medium and large businesses, improving overall application performance, code structure, and developing robust, well-designed software systems. Your ownership, drive, and passion will help provide for a world-class user experience and heightened stability of our CE products, and directly augment the growth of millions of Southeast Asian merchant-partners.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Governance - GoFinance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f9ff2d6a-a041-497b-91a8-a8e30fb26358</link><description>About the Role

In this role, you will act as a bridge between the business intelligence team, software engineering team, product team, compliance team, and legal team to help enable the stakeholders to accurately make data-driven decisions while implementing proper data security and protection principles. Through this role you will be able to flex your data analytical skills, communication and leadership skills, and greatly contribute to securing data within the Gojek ecosystem. Along the way, you will have the opportunity to collaborate with multiple people with different backgrounds, so you will be exposed to different perspectives.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Engineer-Streaming</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7e58bcc0-1534-4fbd-b0dc-4045b3b1d395</link><description>About the Role

As Gojek is undergoing exponential growth, our data has followed the same growth curve. Thus, as an integral member of the Data Engineering team, you'll be at the epicenter of one of Southeast Asia's most coveted companies, and get to witness and solve the challenges that come with rapid scaling.

As our Lead Data Engineer, you'll work closely with the business team and other data teams to improve the accessibility &amp; reliability of data while leveraging the largest-scale data processing technologies in the world. With your strong product-oriented vision and "Do It Yourself" mindset, you'll build data products that will deliver, model, and curate data for the entire Gojek ecosystem.

</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Engineer - Infrastructure</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4902cf55-f4d1-4925-9004-be3120a0d713</link><description>About the Role - 
As GoPay is undergoing exponential growth, our data has followed the same growth curve. Thus, as an integral member of the Data Engineering team, you'll be at the epicenter of one of Southeast Asia's most coveted companies, and get to witness and solve the challenges that come with rapid scaling.

As our Data Engineer- Infrastructure for our Payments team, you'll focus heavily on building and scaling a data platform that enables and delivers reliable, trustworthy, and approachable data to our users. You'll also get to design, develop, and deploy applications with a high sense of ownership. The core data platforms you’ll build will deliver, model, and curate data for the entire Gojek Payments platform.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 11:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0f8f8e36-4225-47fd-bbd0-d4c917ddf7a3</link><description>About the Role
As our Lead Data Engineer, you’ll be a crucial member of the Financial Services Platform at Gojek. In this role, you’ll take the wheel in building and scaling our Data Warehouse foundation that enables and delivers reliable and trustworthy data that affects our internal users, driver-partners, and merchant-partners alike. You’ll design, develop, and maintain the services for our data ingestion pipeline, ensuring the data is understandable, usable, and adheres to data governance policies. The folks in the Engineering, Business, Operations, and Data Science teams will be your companions on this ride; they’ll provide the data you’ll utilize in your daily tasks, while you act as a bridge between them and third parties.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 10:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Analyst - Financial Services</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8d03e634-4729-4906-b797-546ad56b8d8f</link><description>About the Role

As a Lead Data Analyst on the Financial Services Platform, you will be responsible to utilize our voluminous data to improve acquisition, activation, retention, and loyalty for our product. You will be driving the analytics projects of the Growth team across different products, ultimately enabling the Financial Services team to make data-driven decisions.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Cloud Infra Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/94c55b8e-5940-432b-b332-c764f05cb522</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Cloud Infrastructure Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing heavily on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance and output to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view. Your infrastructure and standardization designs will not only be implemented for the CE group alone, but throughout the Gojek ecosystem as a whole.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead BI Analyst (Enterprise BI)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b7663508-1b35-4132-a664-c15ade7347c0</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Lead Business Intelligence (BI) Analyst in our Enterprise BI practice. Based in Jakarta, Indonesia, you'll be an integral player within Gojek’s IT Enterprise Systems team under the CIO Organization. 
 
As our Lead BI Analyst, you’ll be instrumental in the Enterprise BI IT Business Partner (ITBP) wheel of Gojek that directly supports the all Enterprise Functions of Gojek which includes Finance, Accounting, and Tax (FAT), HR, Corporate Planning, MM, Procurement etc. team in automating various processes and providing data required for corporate and financial reporting. You’ll focus a bulk of your time on developing and maintaining data automation for corporate and financial processes. The Data Warehouse, respective back-end and product, and ITBP finance support teams will be your companions on this ride. You’ll have ample opportunity to flex your SQL and Python programming skills, streamlining and automating various corporate planning and financial operations for the wider team to utilize. 


</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 02:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Android Engineer - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5181d137-b706-4b11-af9f-470f9b089aeb</link><description>About the Role

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Lead Android Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the GoPay team based in Bangalore, India. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current user preferences and trends, and emerging technologies in the mobile engineering field, you will work alongside the product management team and cross-functional teams (Product Engineer, DevOps, Data, UX, QA) to improve overall application performance, code structure, and develop robust, well-designed software systems. Most importantly, your efforts will directly ensure our users get quality care and a seamless experience with our products &amp; services.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 05:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Android Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/dbdafe70-f6e3-4a5a-9e60-356070af6fa1</link><description>About the Role

At Goto, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Android Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable Android software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Android Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/64d8c192-9870-4638-bbe6-1fa5124ec5e1</link><description>About the Role

At Goto, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Lead Android Engineer, you’ll be an integral player on our Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. With a talented team of Product Managers, UI/UX Designers, Testers, Program Managers, and various Engineers, you’ll dive deep into building a POS system for both online and offline functions. By improving the overall code structure, developing clear and sustainable Android software components, and ensuring robust, well-designed software systems, you’ll ensure our customers are given the most streamlined transaction flows and a reliable centralized payment platform.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 10:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KYCC SME #6552</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0692757f-7bde-43b4-a40f-3b75682b4c17</link><description>About the Role -
In this role you would provide advisory support to the teams so that KYC is performed in an efficient, accurate and professional manner, and in accordance with relevant policies. You also would analyze customer complaints and identify actions to improve service. To promulgate good complaint handling techniques across the business, you will play a critical role through the delivery of skilled technical and analytical support, enabling the business to maintain customer satisfaction and meet regulatory policy standards.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 13:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KYC Special Project - GoPay - #7510</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1d01f5f0-9b84-4e97-b9bc-093adfcb182d</link><description>About the Role

As our KYC Project Manager, you’ll be part of the greater KYC verifications team that directly impacts Gojek’s partners. Your main objective will be to lead projects that further enhance KYC processes contributing to measurable benefits for the team's operations. You’ll help identify gaps in our current operational processes, come up with automated solutions to resolve these issues, and review their subsequent results. The main KYC streams, as well as the Product and QC teams, will be your companions on this ride. Your efforts will directly ensure the KYC team operates with great efficiency, reducing manual processes across all KYC functions and facilitating seamless new product deployment.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 09:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KYC Project Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/856f146e-2a1c-4cbb-b11e-017e8b916208</link><description>They say no man is an island, and this notion holds particularly true for this role. As our KYC Project Manager, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the verifications wheel of GoJek that directly impacts the company’s ability to ensure its adherence to implementing a robust Enhanced Due Diligence (EDD) and Customer Due Diligence (CDD) in compliance to regulation. You will be in the driver seat to translate company goals into initiatives with tangible result by doing cost and benefit analysis 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KYC Ops Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6f1dfa44-e8cc-41a9-b8bf-c99d0c0e91e2</link><description>They say no man is an island, and this notion holds particularly true for this role. As our KYC Ops Manager, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the verifications wheel of Gojek that directly impacts the company’s ability to ensure its adherence to implementing a robust Enhanced Due Diligence (EDD) and Customer Due Diligence (CDD) in compliance to regulation. Your main objective will be to ensure that existing processes meet the standard requirements such as targeted SLA and KYC quality as well as identify ways to better streamline current processes. The greater KYC, Product, and Compliance teams will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your leadership and team management skills, getting us even closer to a seamless KYC Ops process 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 03:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KYB Ops Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/857e0964-aefe-427c-8325-de6064587b6b</link><description>They say no man is an island, and this notion holds particularly true for this role. As our KYC Ops Manager, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the verifications wheel of Gojek that directly impacts the company’s ability to ensure its adherence to implementing a robust Enhanced Due Diligence (EDD) and Customer Due Diligence (CDD) in compliance to regulation. Your main objective will be to ensure that existing processes meet the standard requirements such as targeted SLA and KYC quality as well as identify ways to better streamline current processes. The greater KYC, Product, and Compliance teams will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your leadership and team management skills, getting us even closer to a seamless KYC Ops process 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 04:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IT Procurement Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7f774991-2176-47df-bda3-b804a77475ca</link><description>About the Role

Vendor Management Team is centralized function unit based in Jakarta that handle Vendor Onboarding and Vendor Maintenance process throughout Gojek entities.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 05:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IT GRC Specialist-Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/95393a6e-1744-44d1-85d8-4a7e4ce16fa2</link><description>About the Role

As our IT GRC Specialist (Governance, Risk &amp; Compliance), you'll be a crucial cog within the Financial Platform wheel at GoTo Financial. You'll be the key person who'll build and maintain our IT GRC program, as well as oversee the implementation of its controls. You'll dive deep into conducting IT GRC assessments, including legislative and regulatory proposals surrounding personal information, and constantly scout for any gaps in our system to prevent system &amp; data leaks. Your efforts will ensure the privacy and safety of our users and partners are protected and upheld, providing anyone who utilizes our financial platform the best protection through world-class IT GRC programs and processes.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 06:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IT GRC Lead-Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f0dbe871-71e8-446f-8be8-ee5ad076c438</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding Information Security, look no further.As our IT GRC Lead for Merchant Platform, you’ll take the wheel in leading the team of a high performing team of IT GRC Specialists in developing and maintaining Information and security management policies for Goto Financial. Along with conducting security risk, you will be in charge of monitoring, evaluating, and enforcing the implementation of information security controls throughout the company. Working closely with data and engineering, you will get to provide a secure platform for our merchants, partners, and consumers. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide the best protection by having a high standard of information security


</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 03:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IT Enterprise Risk Management Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1f7c2b9b-5c21-4497-bbc6-3a70409a46d3</link><description>About the Role 

As our IT ERM Lead, you'll be responsible for overseeing the overall IT Risk Management process including monitoring internal and external reporting procedures of risk metrics and creating actionable insights for various Risk teams. You’ll develop a rigorous IT risk management reporting program for the Risk Management Committee and Audit Committee. 

Working closely with Operating company ERM teams and IT GRC Teams on key material risks and mitigations specifically for IT and Cyber Risks, you'll also manage the aggregation of the Risk at the GoTo level, and cultivate risk management culture centered around trust and confidence amongst external stakeholders. This role is exciting as you will be interfacing with dynamic, ambitious, and result-driven individuals that are focused on improvements. Join us in a race to provide a safe and trusted platform that our customers count on and love to come back to. 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 08:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internal Controls &amp; Compliance Manager  - 5484</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c9a96b12-b276-4490-a4e5-df4dac1292fe</link><description>About the Role 

As Internal Controls &amp; Compliance manager, you are responsible for the operationalisation of corporate compliance programs for GoTo Financial. You will focus on performing regular corporate compliance risk assessment, implementing group compliance policies and standards, ensuring the establishment of relevant standard operating procedures, and building the ethics &amp; compliance culture through effective communication program/strategy and compliance testing/monitoring activities. 

Essentially, you will be part of the team who protect the company, manage risk related to the GoTo Financial ecosystem by ensuring rigorous processes and policy is in place to meet regulatory and shareholders expectations, align the business activities with the company code of conduct, group policies and international standards of good practices.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internal Communications Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5e396ce6-f2b2-4f58-ac7f-ea407481b24e</link><description>About the Role
Supporting Senior Manager of Internal Comms in actualizing Gojek’s objective of being a great place to work through excellent internal communications practices and programs and interdepartmental collaboration that create trust and inform and engage employees at all levelsWhat success looks like:Increased employee trust and satisfaction toward Gojek internal communications practices and transparent cultureImproved information intake and engagementMeasurement tools: HR/PAC employee survey, townhall surveys, and focus group discussion results, others
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 03:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Interaction Designer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d9631a1b-204c-41f8-a302-904e8f6bef18</link><description>About the role

As an Interaction Designer, you will craft user-centric products and experiences, into - functional - intuitive and beautiful interfaces as well as micro-interactions. You will collaborate with Developers, Product Designers, UX writers, Researchers, &amp; Creatives in an agile team environment. You will deliberate design decisions and translate any given user-experience journey into a smooth and intuitive interaction. 

We are looking for Interaction Designers who have a deep understanding of how computers and humans interact, master the design fundamentals such as color, space, typography, hierarchy, and paddings and grids like the back of your hands. You have to be familiar with the platform that you are building (iOS, Android, Web, etc.) — sticklers for details, understanding design systems and how it works at scale, and expertise over their tools.  

You will be a part of the key players who help us build the best and biggest payment platform in Indonesia.  

</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 07:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Insurance - Software Engineer - SE2</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/104a2bf4-4458-4e5c-987a-d9591770dda8</link><description>About the Role

If you're looking to hone in on your engineering abilities and work on mission-critical high scalability distributed systems, this may be the job for you. As a Software Engineer, you will help shape the future of our Consumer Lending products, and more importantly, help millions of users meet their financial needs responsibly. 

Be a part of feature development from end-to-end, constantly pairing with Senior Engineers.
Write code that's clear, concise, performant, tested, and easy to understand by other teams and engineers.
Contribute to the design and development of highly scalable, available, reliable, secure, and fault-tolerant services.
Try questioning engineering standards, tooling, and processes after understanding our needs and communicate what works and what does not work for you and why.
Deep dive and debug production issues across services and levels of the stack when needed.
Coordinate and communicate with different internal/external teams daily—stay in close communication with product manager, team lead and senior engineers to execute the feature roadmap efficiently.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 09:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Insights Assistant Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/414901c8-9f91-4859-a71c-5d42604b99f5</link><description>About the Role 

As Insights Assistant Manager, you will help Insights Manager to provide actionable insights and strategies to reach target acquisitions and monthly transacting users. Working closely with the Marketing, Business Analyst, Strategy, and Demand team, as well as the greater GoFood Product team, you’ll help to drive an effective and strategic decision-making process by providing a holistic view of the market and competitive insights. Collectively, by devising and navigating strategic and data-driven initiatives for the team, your efforts will further position GoFood as the most preferred food delivery platform in Indonesia and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Information Security Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7d4bfcac-8827-40dc-b5b3-413887c9a494</link><description>About the Role

The Information Security Manager will play a crucial role in the implementation of the Information Security programs. You will work closely with the Information Security Chief of Staff and collaborate with leadership and technical teams on the continued evolution of Information Security programs across the cybersecurity, and company functions. We are looking for someone who has good knowledge of information security domains, a passion to execute the long-term strategy, and a strong aim to empower others. Self-starter mentality, analytical thinking, good communication, collaboration skills, and attention to detail are key.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 07:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In-App Copywriter</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/06b40251-67b9-4683-a65f-f785cd152844</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding in-app campaigns that lead to user engagement and conversion, look no further. As an In-app Copywriter, you’ll execute a successful in-app marketing campaign by combining user behavior and creative content. The role is about executing and analyzing in-app marketing creatives.
As an In-app Copywriter, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the Marketing wheel of Gojek. Based in Jakarta, Indonesia, you’ll execute our in-app creative copywriting that directly influence user engagement and conversion rates. You’ll get a front-row seat (and get your hands dirty) in executing in-app marketing creatives, marrying insights from user behaviors and trends with creative, relatable content. You’ll prioritize marketing creatives based on team objectives, and follow the team’s KPI that has been set.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Head of Risk Experience</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a13a3fab-8b60-4001-9a38-67dd7fbc4269</link><description>About the Role

Our company depends on the Risk function to provide solutions for several challenges impacting the Trust &amp; Safety of our platform. These can range from verifying the identity of users to identifying errant behavior patterns, preventing fraudsters from misusing our platform, and keeping our users safe whilst using our services. You will define, design, and develop products and services that are comprehensive and easily accessible to other businesses and platforms. You will also coordinate their integration in various platforms and services, ensuring that the fraud and resilience concerns are mitigated and that the required defenses are in place across all products.

You will optimize our communication and processes to make them clear, efficient, fast, and effective to serve our users better and improve customer satisfaction. You will also be the champion of user-centricity in all of our Risk treatments.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Head of Risk Analytics - Tokopedia</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9f931b19-f1e8-4cee-a086-7cffd9cc8826</link><description>About the Role 

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, data-driven team and an opportunity to hone your business intelligence and data visualization, and storytelling skills, look no further. As  Tokopedia Risk Analytics Manager you will be working with a team of risk professionals to define, measure, quantify and track risks in the Tokopedia ecosystem. Working closely with Risk teams in GoTo Group, you will help to identify and categorize risk types, define metrics to measure and create visualization and dashboards to monitor them.  The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to make Trust and Safety a top priority at Tokopedia. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 05:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Head of Partnership (Jago)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/12a63782-56d4-40b0-a3ea-c979b9bbb772</link><description>About the Role - 
To become a source of competitive advantage in creating a sustainable, strong, and long-term alliance with partners across Indonesia financial institutions. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Growth Ops Analyst - GoFin</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/a988eb34-bc13-4af3-86b1-b748ee901bae</link><description>About the role: 

As a Growth Ops Analyst on the Financial Services Platform, you will be working closely with the Marketing team, utilizing our voluminous data to improve the performance of both tactical and strategic campaigns. You will have ample opportunity to flex your analytics and project management skills, getting us even closer to the financial inclusion of all Indonesian. You will be based in the Jakarta office.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Growth Manager, Merchant Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3ab571c3-415c-421f-bf76-f8ec979e8aaf</link><description>About the role

Here comes a new challenge for you who is seeking the next leap in your career growth, being our Growth Manager for Merchant Payments (part of the GoPay group)! In this role, you will lead problem-solving processes and execute solutions with a focus on improving operations for merchant funded promotions. Combining business strategy, data prowess and merchant (and sales) experience, you will work on initiatives that will empower teams to run campaigns more seamlessly and efficiently. In short, you’ll get out of bed every day thinking about new ways to solve exciting problems and grow the merchant business. How cool is that?

</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 04:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Growth Manager, GoFood</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b794d4a3-ca94-4ba7-8769-e223ea06204f</link><description>About the Role

Here comes a new challenge for you who are seeking the next leap in your career growth, being our Growth Manager for GoFood! In this role, you will lead problem-solving processes and execute solutions with a focus on improving demand and growth metrics for GoFood. Combining business strategy and customer experience &amp; behavior analysis, you will do experiments and campaigns that will encourage our users to experience the product’s core value as quickly as possible which will also improve the product's account spending. In short, you’ll get out of bed every day thinking about new ways to solve exciting problems and grow the business, how cool is that!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 06:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Group Internal Control &amp; Compliance - Advisory Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f26de668-c635-41bb-b964-693458e8c10f</link><description>About the Role 

In this key strategic role, you will be part of the Vietnam GojekInternal Control (IC) and Compliance Team. Focusing heavily on performing corporate compliance programs, ensuring the establishment and the implementation of relevant group IC &amp; Compliance policies and Gojek procedures,  building the compliance culture through practical compliance training &amp; communication programs execution, and assisting the adoption of group IC &amp; Compliance standards (guideline) towards Gojek Vietnam. 

You will employ your subject matter expertise and organizational agility to assist the operationalization of corporate compliance programs for the Gojek ecosystem, particularly for Vietnam. Essentially, you will be part of the team who protects the company, manage risk related to the Gojek ecosystem by ensuring rigorous processes and controls are in place to meet regulatory and shareholders' expectations, align the business activities with the company code of conduct, group policies and international standards of good practices.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Group Compensation Systems &amp; Analytics Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6d30435e-5931-4dc9-86af-a4c7b04d9095</link><description>About the Role

GoTo is looking for a Group Compensation Systems &amp; Analytics Specialist to be a key strategic partner for our Group and People Business Partners. The role will focus on enabling Business outcomes by influencing decisions aligned with GoTo’s Compensation Philosophy. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 05:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Group Compensation Systems &amp; Analytics Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4773a143-18dd-440e-bb23-f0a4575821fb</link><description>About the Role

GoTo is looking for a Group Compensation Systems &amp; Analytics Specialist to be a key strategic partner for our Group and People Business Partners. The role will focus on enabling Business outcomes by influencing decisions aligned with GoTo’s Compensation Philosophy. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 05:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GoPay Content Writer - Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3f490b3a-b622-4221-bb31-d72e96f79e36</link><description>About the role: 
This role reports directly to the Head of Social Media &amp; Digital Content and works closely with the Brand team &amp; other pods to grow various social media channels and manage content production for GoPay marketing activities, leading a team of social media specialists. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GoPay Content Writer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8a9dde97-4485-4b02-b711-ec11a144b9e6</link><description>About the role: 
This role reports directly to the Head of Social Media &amp; Digital Content and works closely with the Brand team &amp; other pods to grow various social media channels and manage content production for GoPay marketing activities, leading a team of social media specialists. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Go-To-Market Manager - 7697</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cb14d7a7-ac15-4920-afac-7ac95301d7b4</link><description>About the Role

We’re looking for talented individuals to join us on our mission to become an indispensable business partner for merchants and to help set the strategic vision, determine that the vision is commercially viable, and then incubate,  launch and drive adoption of successful manifestations of the visions in partnership with the broader organization. 

The Go-To Market (GTM) team acts as the business team for the Merchant Platform Core Product. You need to lead the GTM working groups and collaborate closely with the product, sales, marketing, ops team for product rollout and adoption of platform features and/or various use cases hosted by GoBiz surfaces. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 02:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Full-Stack Engineer - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9700d9ea-6179-4b40-b058-d3cec31419a6</link><description>About the role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Full Stack Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Risk Team based in Indonesia. Your main objective will be to build services for the Merchant Risk platform. You'll work extensively with Data Scientists, Data Analysts, and Product Managers to detect and prevent fraudulent and/or abusive behaviors to ensure a trusted and fair core platform for our merchant-partners. You'll have ample opportunity to flex your collaboration and leadership skills, getting us even closer to our ultimate goal of creating a seamless app that will transport GoTo Financials to all corners of the globe

</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Stack Engineer Lead - Merchant Payment - 7867</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/acbb4573-e02a-4e6d-aadd-c79939567a60</link><description>About the role

Merchant Payment is looking for passionate, entrepreneurial technical leaders with a drive of building scalable applications and teams. In this role you will be responsible for the overall delivery of your team and will interface very closely with business stakeholders and product stakeholders to deliver a cutting edge product aimed at improving customer experience on Payment. A strong sense of prioritization, deep technical expertise along with taking care of growth and development of the team, are essential in this role
</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 09:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Stack Engineer - KYC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4b4421f5-d0e7-4910-808c-388a25f4ad67</link><description>About the role

You will be part of the risk mitigation team. In this role, you'll focus on building and scaling the sanctions platform. Sanctions platform is a single place where Analysts can write rules and take actions on fraudulent users/ transactions and operations can handle appeals and manage sanctions. This will be a generic/domain agnostic platform that can be used across organizations in GOTO Financial. You will also focus on building an effective sanctions and appeal workflow for customer care agents. You will be responsible for designing, developing, deploying frontend applications with a high sense of ownership. Additionally, you'll devise and manage our entire web infrastructure, and produce innovative solutions that our users will enjoy.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 09:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FP&amp;A Manager/Senior Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/822cdf4f-381d-4b66-b270-5b513fe4e9dd</link><description>About The Role 

We are currently seeking a Senior Financial Planning &amp; Analysis (FP&amp;A) Manager at the GoTo Group HoldCo level, supporting the coverage of the GoTo Financial vertical (includes GoPay, GoFinance, etc.). In this role, you will be involved in a broad range of finance activities including budgeting, business &amp; financial review, and financial modeling. You will be at the front seat to GoTo’s strategy formulation and some of the most important corporate decisions of the Senior Management (CEO, CFO, etc.) from a financial planning and analysis standpoint, particularly as we move towards an IPO.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Consolidation System Support</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2ae9e78c-4979-4ec9-a7a1-bdaf4bde88af</link><description>About the Role

As our Financial Consolidation System Support, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the Finance IT Business Partner (ITBP) wheel of Gojek that directly supports the Finance Accounting and Tax (FAT) team in performing their daily activities, to achieve accurate and timely financial closing especially in financial consolidation area. You’ll also collaborate with technical support, data analysts, and other stakeholders in handling day-to-day inquiries, providing consultation support, and helping to resolve their respective issues. The support your team provides the FAT platform will guide their decision-making process and steer the trajectory of the company’s business and financial endeavors.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 02:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Enterprise Sales Support Associate</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/49dac495-a24d-497b-b783-9c14f1ae8fdf</link><description>About the Role

They say no man is an island, and this notion holds particularly true for this role. As our Enterprise Sales Support Associate, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the Sales team wheel of Gojek that directly impacts the company’s SOP to solve day-to-day problems faced by Enterprise merchants and the HQ Enterprise Sales Team members. Your main objectives will be to uphold and improve business processes for the sales support team, work with the HQ Enterprise Sales Team to help advocate for our merchants’ needs internally, and ensure seamless implementation of Gojek solutions with and/or within the merchant’s ecosystem with the respective merchant’s IT team. The Enterprise Sales team will be your companions during this ride. You will have the opportunity to flex and hone in on your business strategy, multi-tasking, analytical, and time-management skills, catering to the day-to-day needs and issues of our beloved merchants. 



</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 09:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Enterprise Risk Management Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2d5b5cc3-2760-47d6-bfa0-19a9ad483ae0</link><description>About the Role 

As our Enterprise Risk and Governance Lead, you'll take the wheel in establishing various risk management frameworks and programs, as well as designing and executing risk related campaigns in efforts to cultivate a risk management culture centered around trust and confidence amongst our stakeholders.

As part of the Risk Governance team at our holding company GoTo, you’ll also establish a rigorous risk governance and risk reporting program to the Risk Management Committee and Audit Committee. Your efforts will directly bolster the continuous improvement of our ecosystem integrity aimed at further amplifying users’ trust perception of GoTo Group. This role is exciting as you will be interfacing with dynamic, ambitious, and result-driven individuals that are focused on improvements. Join us in a race to provide a safe and trusted platform that our customers count on and love to come back to.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 02:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Product</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d4fa1501-112b-430c-b58f-9f78ab543ca0</link><description>About the Role - 
We are looking for an experienced data engineer who has expertise and in-depth knowledge of building the products with the Do It Yourself(DIY) Vision. As a member of the Data Engineering team, you will be at the epicenter of an amazing company, experiencing extreme growth and solving the problems that come with scaling rapidly. 

You will work closely with the business teams and other data teams to improve the accessibility &amp; reliability of data while leveraging the largest-scale data processing technologies in the world. In order to succeed in this role, you should have a product mindset along with a strong vision of building data products for a massively scalable data engineering platform.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 09:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Payments - KYC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9ebbb2a2-e36a-43c6-9ac7-8e1af9f4eb5e</link><description>About the role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team that enjoys building creative solutions for users, look no further. 

As an engineering manager in the Payments Platform team, you will be responsible for developing innovative platform solutions, building &amp; grow a high-performance team, and responsible for the overall delivery of your team. You should be adept and passionate about solving problems blending technology with customer obsession. You will collaborate closely with business and product stakeholders to deliver high-quality products. With strong prioritization skills and deep technical expertise, you’ll get to pilot this team to greater heights. 

The cherry on top: This would be your chance to spearhead the change and redefine the KYC ecosystem in Indonesia and the rest of southeast Asia.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 08:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c279c9a4-512f-4e6d-88c2-1f351e4275f5</link><description>About the Role 

You will play an essential role in developing products and executing business strategies. You will be working very closely with business development manager, product manager, technical architect, and engineers to evaluate 3rd party vendors, available technology choices, conversion of product roadmap into an engineering execution plan, sprint management and work with engineers and the quality assurance team for timely quality deliverables. You will also be responsible for engineering team management and growth. Throughout this exciting experience, you’ll build relationships with internal and external stakeholders, from the product, marketing, research, and operation team among others to meet the fast-paced nature of the financial technology industry.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 09:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/023b2603-a5af-4855-8cd1-ed0572d79b6f</link><description>About the Role 

You will play an essential role in developing products and executing business strategies. You will be working very closely with business development manager, product manager, technical architect, and engineers to evaluate 3rd party vendors, available technology choices, conversion of product roadmap into an engineering execution plan, sprint management and work with engineers and the quality assurance team for timely quality deliverables. You will also be responsible for engineering team management and growth. Throughout this exciting experience, you’ll build relationships with internal and external stakeholders, from the product, marketing, research, and operation team among others to meet the fast-paced nature of the financial technology industry.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 05:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/82d76bb0-473c-497e-9021-113ef3523770</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our engineering manager. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 


</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/7c437543-7d37-4ac8-a992-51c35d51f538</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our engineering manager. GoBiz Merchant Platform team in Indonesia and India provides solutions for merchants across Indonesia and other southeast Asian countries. The GoBiz merchant platform supports a massive network of small, medium, and large businesses. 

The platform delivers a world-class merchant experience through multimodal surfaces on the mobile, web, and open APIs. The teams achieve this through the latest frontend architectures that enable internal product teams like GoFood and GoPay, to deliver rich experiences through the GoBiz surfaces. 

The platform provides efficient and effective capabilities for cross-cutting concerns across multiple GoJek teams. Internal teams can hence focus on delivering profound experiences without reinventing capabilities.  The platform teams invest in large-scale distributed event-driven systems with cloud-native frameworks to provide high-performance, stable, and operationally efficient systems. 


</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Marketplace</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/53612f12-b5b6-4b26-b84d-8a419d9fb3c3</link><description>About the Role 

Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Engineering Manager. In this role, you would be tasked with platformization of the Mobility Marketplace as a first-class problem, which requires understanding end-to-end use-cases and challenge the status quo at all times by reviewing current engineering techniques and tools and scout for opportunities and fundamental engineering solutions that would bring agility &amp; reliability to enable more business opportunities. 

To excel in this role we believe you need the ability to drive strategic technical, delivery and people decisions for the team by collaborating with cross-functional counterparts and stakeholders and also considering inputs from various parties, most importantly from the customers. You are also expected to coach and nurture your team.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Infrastructure Engineering</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/879d39f3-27fd-4faa-996d-39df986f3b19</link><description>About the Role :

We are looking for an experienced data engineer who has expertise and in depth knowledge of managing the data infrastructure in a cloud environment. In this role, you will be required to lead a small team of two Data Engineers and create a reliable infrastructure for Gojek Payments and Financial Services. In order to succeed in this role, you should have a product mindset along with a strong vision of automating and creating a scalable data infrastructure.
</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 09:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Groceries</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c6eb72c6-de04-4af4-b5cf-bd5c7b3cc710</link><description>About the Role

As our Engineering Manager for Gojek Groceries, you'll play an integral part in designing solutions for GoMart - Gojek's online groceries platform. You’ll spend your time writing elegant, bulletproof code, enhancing our engineering strategy, mentoring a talented troop of engineers, driving critical projects, and designing microservices to further evolve GoMart's system. With this team, you'll be presented with ample opportunities to tackle challenging problems and build systems from scratch. Your efforts will directly improve the productivity of our engineers and revolutionize grocery shopping in Indonesia and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Gopay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5f660c98-8f12-4700-94b2-0d053e658baa</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly analytical team that enjoys building creative solutions for users, look no further. As our Engineering Manager for the Payments group, you'll take the wheel in building a high-performing team of engineers, developing innovative payment solutions, and driving the overall delivery of your team. You'll get your hands dirty in solving complex issues that blend smart technology with a customer-centric focus, and lay out the roadmap for your team to follow. In collaboration with Business and Product stakeholders, you'll shape business OKRs and plans, and oversee any stakeholder communications related to deliverables and risks within your project. The cherry on top: your efforts will contribute in redefining the payments ecosystem in Indonesia, bringing wider and more inclusive financial services to the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Gofood</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/19a70706-5463-4524-980a-69a131343de3</link><description>About the Role 

At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Engineering Manager for the GoFood Consumer Booking team, you’ll take the wheel in leading a team of 10 to 15 engineers, overseeing the system design within the scope of your team. You will be responsible for defining the charter for the team by collaborating with product, design &amp; business stakeholders. You’ll have full accountability for the growth and development of your team, adjusting their work pace and consistently engaging in knowledge-sharing endeavours. As the first formal leadership role in the Gojek engineering organisation, you’ll help ensure the inner workings of your team are operating seamlessly, providing the most effective and reliable way of ordering by delivering a cutting-edge product aimed at improving customer experience on GoFood.

The consumer booking team is responsible for the overall ordering experience of the consumer at GoFood. The team focuses on building highly secure, high throughput &amp; resilient systems for the ordering flow to ensure the top-notch customer experience. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 08:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Data Engineering</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0938420e-20ab-4107-97b4-aa90ad63ea3e</link><description>At Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do: bringing our ideas to life and into the lives of our users. As our Engineering Manager for the Data Engineering team, you’ll take the wheel in overseeing Back-end Engineering at Gojek - designing and developing highly scalable, reliable, maintainable and fault tolerant systems for our Data Engineering team. Along with owning the entire life cycle of these projects, you will establish and evangelize the best engineering practices for your team to follow. Working closely with the data catalog team, data engineers and data scientists, you will get to contribute to the system that runs meaningful experiments for GoJEK. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to provide APIs for GoJEK’s millions of users and driver partners to use.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Cartography</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/83b3ad3e-27ec-4d27-b54e-ffb9de432257</link><description>Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Engineering Manager at Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do to bring cheer to the lives of millions. As an Engineering Manager,  you will be part of the team, building some of the most critical products for Gojek's ecosystem of consumers, drivers, and merchants. You will be accountable for leading a team of 10 - 15 engineers. Your ownership, drive, and passion would help provide a world-class user experience and stability for our Cartography products.
To excel in this role, we believe you need to have excellent ability in prioritizing and tactical decision making along with deep technical expertise and eagerness to take a hands-on approach as necessary in delivering values for the customers. 


</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 10:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering Manager - Cartography</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0c099907-51d9-4d27-99b4-42d377c574f2</link><description>Roll up your sleeves and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Engineering Manager at Gojek, engineering is central to everything we do to bring cheer to the lives of millions. As an Engineering Manager,  you will be part of the team, building some of the most critical products for Gojek's ecosystem of consumers, drivers, and merchants. You will be accountable for leading a team of 5 - 10 engineers. Your ownership, drive, and passion would help provide a world-class user experience and stability for our Cartography products.
To excel in this role, we believe you need to have excellent ability in prioritizing and tactical decision making along with deep technical expertise and eagerness to take a hands-on approach as necessary in delivering values for the customers. 

</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 06:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Employee Relations Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2a6f7f23-eeb7-4855-ae53-2eae03874f96</link><description>Buckle up if you’re ready to be our Employee Relations Manager. In this role, you will be an integral player within the HR Compliance team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing heavily on Employee Relations main processes, you will help to ensure that the company adheres to legal standards and policies, stay up to date on all general labor law compliance and issues, thoroughly understanding compliance laws, providing adequate communication to managers and employees about such laws, as well as being responsible for providing guidance on Employee Relation matters. The folks in the GTF People Operations team(s) will be your companions on this ride. Your efforts will band together to enhance the company's operational excellence.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 04:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>District Engagement Acquisition Associate (Central Java)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0fcfb0b5-c994-440a-a510-a1e2f90ee974</link><description>About the Role: 

District Engagement &amp; Acquisition Associate role is to acquire new promising merchants to Gojek's universe and provide the best set of merchants to customers. The role reports to the Direct Sales Manager
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 14:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital Sourcing Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0cb0d3e8-537b-4aee-8a8d-b1c28628f5a2</link><description>About the Role 

As our Sourcing Specialist in the Digital Marketing Sourcing Category, you’ll be an integral player within the Procurement team based in Jakarta. We oversee all Procurement things related to Digital Marketing and Sourcing categories. Specifically, we do sourcing activities that relate to goods/ services in several categories with nature of procuring Digital Marketing related i.e Above the line and Below the line, knowing about the details of marketing area Online, offline, Digital Platform and working with cross-business units who require such products/ services.

You’ll be assisting in leading Procurement buyers within the Digital Marketing Sourcing team and also as a single contributor in handling the assigned sourcing activities. If you’re looking for a chance to hone your skills vertically and horizontally, Procurement is the right place to learn it. You’ll employ your skills and experiences to add more power to enrich the team’s strategy and project fulfillment.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital Media Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/ea34839a-cc72-43da-adeb-977740b594e6</link><description>About the Role

Based in Jakarta, as the Digital Media Specialist you will be managing paid digital media campaign execution, optimization and reporting across display, video, search and others. These campaigns aim to strengthen awareness, drive new and repeat users, and ultimately business results for Gojek. You will be part of a young, dynamic and results-driven team, and will directly contribute to shaping the future of the team and the business.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital Marketing Procurement Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/48ff73d4-c1f6-488d-87b7-1740cd90637d</link><description>About the Role 

As our Procurement Specialist in the Digital Marketing Sourcing Category, you’ll be an integral player within the Procurement team based in Jakarta. We oversee all Procurement things related to Digital Marketing and Sourcing categories. Specifically, we do sourcing activities that relate to goods/ services in several categories with nature of procuring Digital Marketing related i.e Above the line and Below the line, knowing about the details of marketing area Online, offline, Digital Platform and working with cross-business units who require such products/ services.

You’ll be assisting in leading Procurement buyers within the Digital Marketing Sourcing team and also as a single contributor in handling the assigned sourcing activities. If you’re looking for a chance to hone your skills vertically and horizontally, Procurement is the right place to learn it. You’ll employ your skills and experiences to add more power to enrich the team’s strategy and project fulfillment.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 06:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DevOps Engineer - Merchant Payments</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e6789b40-7cac-4a1d-a83f-b6cc08ffbd9e</link><description>About the role

As a Devops Engineer you will be a part of the Merchant Payments Devops Team. Working with energetic and talented troop of engineers, Your primary focus will be on building, operating, and maintaining the Merchant Payments systems on cloud/on-premises, Constantly diagnosing the health of the system, responding to incidents, and providing support to all payment ecosystems. You will work very closely with developer and product stakeholders to deliver and support high-quality products and systems. An intermediate understanding of code/programming and automation is therefore necessary as well.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DesignOps Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/08da8283-38d2-4aab-a1c5-cbaf1cb376d5</link><description>About the Role

DesignOps is the central nervous system of the Design Team at Gojek. We strive to optimize the effectiveness and quality of the design at Gojek by evolving and accelerating our people, culture, practices, and tools. We strive to enable people to be their best possible selves. We are looking for someone to join our DesignOps team who has the first-hand experience in building and managing digital products with a strong background in project management and is excited by the idea of working with a large team of designers to help them realize their potential.

As a Design Program Manager, you will design how designers design. Dream, explore, create, and nurture other designers’ skills and processes, identifying areas for improvement through collaborating across functions at Gojek.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 11:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Warehouse Engineer - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9eb91374-99e1-48c1-a344-6dd8f6955d38</link><description>About the Role 

They say no man is an island, and this notion holds particularly true for this role. As our Data Warehouse Developer, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the Data Warehouse wheel of Gojek that directly impacts the company’s single source of truth of data. Your main objective will be to build out our data warehouse. Product Managers, BI Analytics and Product Engineers will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your SQL, data modeling and data warehouse concept skills, helping the team craft beautifully simple solutions for challenging user stories.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 03:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Warehouse Engineer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e651bf67-d9d7-4d12-8ef9-4f43e5297a99</link><description>About the Role

As our Data Warehouse Developer, you’ll be an instrumental player in Gojek’s Data team that drives the company’s analytical data infrastructure. You’ll take the wheel in designing, developing, and managing our data warehouse and data infrastructure that supports it, ensuring these systems operate reliably at scale through a high degree of automation. You’ll also oversee the single source of truth of data for analytics, partnering with product managers, product engineers, data engineers, BI/analytics, and data scientists during this ride. You’ll play an active role in ensuring data governance policies and tooling are implemented and adhered to, and assist the team in utilizing data to deliver beautifully simple and scalable solutions to meet user needs.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 09:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Warehouse Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/485affd9-aa19-48f1-805a-24a36cf59543</link><description>About the Role

As our Data Warehouse Developer, you’ll be an instrumental cog in the data warehouse that directly impacts the company’s single source of truth of data. You will be handling the data pipelines and warehouse for the products under the Commerce Enablement business of GTF. Product Managers, BI Analytics, and Product Engineers will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex your SQL, data modeling and data warehouse concept skills, helping the team craft beautifully simple solutions for challenging user stories.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 07:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Scientist - Risk Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/03d27ef9-b847-4ed0-85bb-72cd93f52044</link><description>About the Role

Gojek is committed to creating a safe and trusted platform for all - drivers, consumers and merchants. Fraud has a large impact on both the user experience and financials - you will thus be working in an area of high relevance and impact. Specifically, you will help develop data-driven methodologies to reduce fraud risk and improve user experience on the platform. This will entail identifying relevant data sources, evaluating them and building predictive models for fraud detection. You will have the opportunity to work in a dynamic, fast-paced environment in a cross-functional team with business and product stakeholders and leverage our vast data and the Big Data infrastructure.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 09:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Scientist - Risk - Gopay - 7897</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/36db42c8-5049-4db6-ba0d-340dd6621720</link><description>About the Role 

As a data scientist in our Risk Data team, you will create data science models which protect GoPay and its customers. You will have the opportunity to work with rich data to derive new intelligence and use various data science techniques. You will partner with Risk, product and engineering stakeholders to identify and solve some of the most impactful and stimulating business problems in the payments space. You will work in a fast-paced environment with direct impacts to the business.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 04:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Scientist - GoMart</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0d93fffc-36a4-4393-9ffc-7f29bdbb1eca</link><description>About the Role

They say no man is an island, and this holds true here at Gojek. As our Decision Scientist, you’ll be part of the data team that directly impacts GoMart's business, which is one of the top contributors to Gojek's business.. Your main objective will be to create business impact at scale. The Business and Product Team will be your companions during this ride. Best yet, you’ll have the opportunity to flex both your analytics and DS skills!. What differentiates Gojek from other companies is the pace at which you can see your analysis and insights come to life and impact millions of customers and thousands of merchants partners
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 04:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Science - Internship (Loyalty, Partnership &amp; Monetisation team)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f0388b78-594c-4bae-8129-1776aeab3c98</link><description>About the Role

In this role, you'll be working with teams that  generate impact by solving business/product problems using data science (DS) techniques/models. To add to the excitement, you’ll be exposed to working in diverse, cross-functional teams that may include Software Engineers, Analytics Team and Product Managers. In our humble opinion, the coolest part of this role is how your work will directly impact how the senior leaders at Gojek shape strategies around millions of customers across Southeast Asia.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Privacy Engineer-GoTo Financial</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8b0b98a8-9b61-486d-a7c6-8e5153308cff</link><description>About The Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding Data Privacy, look no further. As our Data Privacy Engineer for Data Security Privacy team, you’ll take the wheel inbuild privacy design structures for GoTo Financial. Along with Implement Data Discovery solutions, you will be in charge of Develop and maintain critical documentation and Coordinate with 3rd party security vendors. Working closely with various teams across GTF, you will get to implement data protection controls. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to ensure GoTo Financial data protected.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 02:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Privacy Engineer-GoTo Financial</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3217f957-c126-46bc-bf99-478febe69d49</link><description>About The Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding Data Privacy, look no further. As our Data Privacy Engineer for Data Security Privacy team, you’ll take the wheel inbuild privacy design structures for GoTo Financial. Along with Implement Data Discovery solutions, you will be in charge of Develop and maintain critical documentation and Coordinate with 3rd party security vendors. Working closely with various teams across GTF, you will get to implement data protection controls. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to ensure GoTo Financial data protected.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Privacy Analyst-GoTo Financial</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1f2981e6-77f1-4b57-85d7-152cbea938ae</link><description>About the Role 

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding data privacy, look no further. As Data Privacy Analyst, you’ll take the wheel in building privacy culture for GoTo Financial. Along with privacy compliance, you will help us drive adoption of privacy technologies and be in charge of overall data protection. Working closely with the Product, Engineering and Legal team, you will get to manage projects pertaining to Data Privacy Initiatives. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to protect customer, employee and partner’s data. 


</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Privacy Analyst-GoTo Financial</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1cbe0066-c9b6-4eaf-8939-8edbda0420ef</link><description>About the Role 

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding data privacy, look no further. As Data Privacy Analyst, you’ll take the wheel in building privacy culture for GoTo Financial. Along with privacy compliance, you will help us drive adoption of privacy technologies and be in charge of overall data protection. Working closely with the Product, Engineering and Legal team, you will get to manage projects pertaining to Data Privacy Initiatives. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to protect customer, employee and partner’s data. 


</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 07:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Engineering Manager, Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d5c5fc61-7a18-42ff-92f1-64a4194f0f62</link><description>About the Role

As GoPay is undergoing exponential growth, our data has followed the same growth curve. Thus, as an integral member of the Data Engineering team, you'll be at the epicenter of one of Southeast Asia's most coveted companies, and get to witness and solve the challenges that come with rapid scaling.

As our Data Engineering Lead for our Payments team, you'll focus heavily on building and scaling a data platform that enables and delivers reliable, trustworthy, and approachable data to our users. You'll also get to design, develop, and deploy applications with a high sense of ownership. Additionally, you’ll lead a lean team of Data Engineers and build robust data engineering products and infrastructures that'll propel the business to achieve their objectives through a data-driven approach. The core data platforms you’ll build will deliver, model, and curate data for the entire Gojek Payments platform.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Engineer - Data Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/764d0cf8-5b75-4053-bd60-94f36edb5fc6</link><description>About the role: 

We are a data driven company - we take pride in being hypothesis driven; our experimentation platform Litmus, has made it possible to run targeted experiments on-demand to guide our super app, driver app product experience and business decisions.  We are now in the process of evolving it to the next level through automation at scale and building decision ready analytics systems. In this role as our Data Engineer for the Experimentation Team, you will be handed the reins to build A/B tests analytical metric intelligent experimentation platform for Gojek. You will be in charge of writing ELT/ETL pipeline code in Batch and store them in an OLAP store for exploratory analytics. Some work involves in pre-aggregate billions of clickstream events, provide real time querying capabilities scanning billions of rows from a OLAP store. Working closely with backend engineers and data scientists, you will get to contribute to the system that runs meaningful experiments for Gojek.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Analyst - Consumer Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/5f7e640d-cbd3-4ad2-8249-a06ffa532975</link><description>About The Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Data Analyst. In this role, you'll be a pivotal member within the Customer Platform group, mining insights from the sea of data, building analytics products, generating insights and designing experiments with the ability to see the real-time impact of your contribution. A talented troop of business leads and fellow data scientists will be your companions on this ride. In our humble opinion, the coolest part of this role is how your work will directly impact how the senior leaders at Gojek shape strategies around millions of customers across Southeast Asia.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Risk Policy Analyst - Merchant Lending, Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/36016e2c-f8fc-465d-aa45-f74cc444694f</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb aboard if you’re ready to be our Credit Risk Policy Analyst. In this role, you will collaborate with Product Managers, Data Science, Growth, and Risk Analytics teams. Your main responsibility will be to strategically develop and manage credit risk policy to enable the business to grow by acquiring new users and manage the merchant's lending portfolio within risk appetite. With your expertise, you’ll be instrumental in helping to drive our team closer to our ultimate goal of providing financial service access to all Indonesians, ensuring everything they do works in harmony with Gojek’s goals and values.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Lead GoPay #7112</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/fd2b5533-fa4a-45a0-8bb3-4ca2fe9ea8fc</link><description>About the role: 
This role reports directly to the Head of Social Media &amp; Digital Content and works closely with the Brand team &amp; other pods to manage the creative development and production for GoPay marketing activities, leading a team of graphic designers. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 05:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Designer - GoPay</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/dc4efe2a-2ed0-40b2-b4ca-d52e9468e65f</link><description>About the Role 

GoPay Design Team is looking for a creative designer rooted in visual design and experienced in branding and UI/UX. You will be responsible for designing and maintaining GoPay brands and its products, supporting product team needs, collaborating with other creatives such as illustrators, writers, photographers and not limited to other teams from different streams.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Corporate Development Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e47fa478-4d5f-4dea-ad36-324ff219e161</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding funding and capital market strategy, valuation analysis, and trends in the industry, look no further. As our Corporate Development Manager for the Corporate Office, you’ll have a front seat to GoTo’s strategy formulation and some of the most important decisions of the organization from a corporate development standpoint, and will be exposed to a myriad of situations, not just in financial analysis, but also in deal structuring, M&amp;A, forming strategic partnerships, investor relations and more. The cherry on top: you’ll get to create leverage for our product teams to capture opportunities and establish our competitive edge, all whilst protecting the interests of GoTo and our stakeholders.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Corporate Development Analyst/Associate (M&amp;A, Investments, Valuation, Financial Modeling)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/78951895-434c-4e04-9560-51fed9254d2d</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly-analytical team and an opportunity to dive deep into projects surrounding funding and capital market strategy, valuation analysis, and trends in the industry, look no further. As our Corporate Development and Investor Relations Associate for the Corporate Office, you’ll have a front seat to GoTo’s strategy formulation and some of the most important decisions of the organization from a corporate development standpoint, and will be exposed to a myriad of situations, not just in financial analysis, but also in deal structuring, M&amp;A, forming strategic partnerships, investor relations and more. The cherry on top: you’ll get to create leverage for our product teams to capture opportunities and establish our competitive edge, all whilst protecting the interests of GoTo and our stakeholders.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 02:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Content Creator Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/43edfc96-a4e8-42d7-9f71-511b130cff87</link><description>About the Role

As Content Creator Specialist for Creative Lab, you’ll take the wheel in communicating ideas that inspire, inform, and captivate consumers. You will be in charge of producing the overall layout and design for any social media creative assets. Working closely with Content Planner and Art Director, you will get the chance to explore your imagination and create the best visual concepts for the Gojek’s social media projects.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Risk Project &amp; Policy Manager - Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/26559a25-770a-4fec-9c58-6395fa43c4fb</link><description>About the Role

Come and join new breeds of risk managers!

On Gojek's Financial Services Platform, Risk Managers are tasked to enable aggressive growth while maintaining long-term business sustainability. As Financial Technology has fast become an essential solution in daily life, new market segments are opening up for financial inclusion, new Fintech products are being launched, thus increasing more adoptions. Here at Gojek's Financial Services Platform, we strive to become a major player in the market, and we are looking for talents with a can-do attitude who have what it takes to make it happen! 

The role of Consumer Risk Project and Policy Manager requires a proactive, creative, logical, and well-structured individual to drive and deliver projects to completion, navigating through regulations, covering all aspects of risks, with sound judgment and mature decision-making process, with the ultimate goal of improving overall user experience.  You will be working together with various functions within Gojek's Financial Services Platform and across to sister companies, also various functions with expected regular interactions with senior managers. 


</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 18:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Risk Analyst - Trust/ Anti-Scam - 4982</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/59f30d84-ff78-4203-bce6-0527edb6650a</link><description>About the Role

We are looking for exceptional risk analyst to identify potential fraud risk, develop mitigating strategies in our expanding business.  The role holder will be responsible for delivering on target risk metrics - by analyzing data and implementing risk rules and recommending mitigation plans.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Lending - Software Engineer - SE2</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/132263d3-02d6-4b1c-9682-9ed0feef76d6</link><description>About the Role 

If you're looking to hone in on your engineering abilities and work on mission-critical high scalability distributed systems, this may be the job for you. As a Senior Software Engineer, your contributions will be crucial for development of financial products. You will help shape the future of our Consumer Lending products, and more importantly, help millions of users meet their financial needs responsibly. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Fraud Risk Policy Manager - Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/816d73b6-65a4-48f5-805e-76a2126cfd8d</link><description>About the Role

On Gojek's Financial Services Platform, Risk Managers are tasked to enable aggressive growth while maintaining long-term business sustainability. As Financial Technology has fast become an essential solution in daily life, new market segments are opening up for financial inclusion, new Fintech products are being launched, thus increasing more adoptions. Here at Financial Services Platform, we strive to become a major player in the market, and we are looking for talents with a can-do attitude who have what it takes to make it happen! 

The role of Consumer Fraud Risk Policy Manager requires a proactive and critical-thinking individual, with the hunger to learn and consistently have a sense of urgency for implementation. You will be working together with various functions within Financial Services Platform and across to various functions, such as risk, operations, data science, partnership, product, data engineering, legal, and compliance, where you will be expected to be the subject matter expert in fraud management for lending.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Engagement Associate Pay (Tangerang &amp; Depok) - GoPay - #7163</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/1d26af05-013c-4e6e-9b0b-7ea5be73287c</link><description>About the Role 

GoPay Consumer Engagement Associate will be responsible for any GoPay MTU acquisition and activation by creating and implementing strategic marketing plans across various touchpoints namely visibility, partnership, and digital to name a few. You will also be responsible for the marketing funnel of GoPay at the appointed district aligned with the headquarter initiatives. You will work closely with the GoPay Marketing, Regional Consumer Engagement Head, and GoPay sales team.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 05:04:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Credit Risk Policy Manager - Financial Services Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/c7810e3d-584d-4986-9a2b-6774c48484e5</link><description>About the Role

Come and join new breeds of risk managers!

On Gojek's Financial Services Platform, Risk Managers are tasked to enable aggressive growth while maintaining long-term business sustainability. As Financial Technology has fast become an essential solution in daily life, new market segments are opening up for financial inclusion, new Fintech products are being launched, thus increasing more adoptions. Here at Gojek's Financial Services Platform, we strive to become a major player in the market, and we are looking for talents with a can-do attitude who have what it takes to make it happen! 

The role of Consumer Credit Risk Policy Manager requires a logical thinking individual, with a passion for analysis, a highly proactive, and a consistent sense of urgency for implementation. You will be working together with various functions within Gojek's Financial Services Platform and across to sister companies and various functions, such as risk, operations, data science, partnership, product, data engineering, legal, and compliance, where you will be expected to be the subject matter expert in credit risk management.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Compensation Solutions Partner</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d709217b-0452-4dc2-9324-65b1273be64a</link><description>About the Role 

Join the team that stays relevant and innovative in driving competitive compensation for the GoTo Group. As our Compensation Solutions Partner, you will be a member of the Global Compensation Business Partnering Team, A where the main mission is to independently facilitate key compensation outcomes for their designated client groups with centrally developed products and core processes. Working alongside bright minds in GoTo, you’ll be part of the team that bring happiness to your partner!


</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 05:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Compensation Solutions Partner</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/859b642a-964e-4073-8b0a-2eb94c5a17b7</link><description>About the Role 

Join the team that stays relevant and innovative in driving competitive compensation for the GoTo Group. As our Compensation Solutions Partner, you will be a member of the Global Compensation Business Partnering Team, A where the main mission is to independently facilitate key compensation outcomes for their designated client groups with centrally developed products and core processes. Working alongside bright minds in GoTo, you’ll be part of the team that bring happiness to your partner!


</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Collection Strategy and Policy Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9690e789-a3ca-40b2-be6a-de5993ae7beb</link><description>About the Role The role is responsible for developing, maintaining, and improving Collection policies, strategies, MIS reports, processes and procedures, conducting complex analysis and providing accurate and concise results with recommendations to management.You will need to leverage data and score models to define and propose strategy/solutions that deliver measurable improvements in collections and recoveries performance.You will be using advanced analytical tools and techniques to and will be responsible for owning processes and will be accountable for driving continuous improvements in the end to end Collection activities.You will work closely with internal business partners in scoring and analytics and Collections Operations to re-define the Collections approach delivering a more analytical, measurable and cost-effective strategy.

What You Will Do - Create segmentation in the portfolio based on the risk for efficient handling
- Monitoring portfolio for increasing delinquency patterns based on the portfolio triggers
- Creating meaningful management reporting and analysis for portfolio review
- Analyze data to identify early warning signals (Productivity, efficiency &amp; effectiveness) and proactively provide feedback in order to take corrective actions
- Effective trigger based on monitoring to ensure adherence to the process in place and regular improvement ideas for initiating positive changes in the process.
- Proactively seeks, finds and recommends opportunities to improve customer experience, processes, policies, budget vs actual and profit for the company
- Provides accurate and concise results and presents findings, recommendations and presentations to Senior Management
- Proactively finds work/ analysis that helps collection/ recovery team to improve performance
- Expected to work on multiple projects with limited guidance
- Effectively mentors other team mates to help them develop their analytics tools &amp; techniques and risk management skills and knowledge about the business and processes
- Create regular champion challengers to drive continuous improvement(improved performance, reducing cost)



What You Will Need - Min 5years experience in the consumer lending industry with direct experience in managing Collection strategy/analytics will be a huge plus point. - Bachelor's/ Master degree in a quantitative discipline; Math, Finance, Statistics, Economics or equivalent work/training is required; advanced degree is preferred - Strong analytical, technical and statistical skills. Ability to synthesize / analyze diverse information, develop recommendations, and makes decisions - Ability to analyze, understand root cause - Strong communication and interpersonal skills, ability to interact with individuals across departments / functions and with senior-level individuals, should have the ability to present information confidently in a crisp and easily understandable way - Proven record in problem solving and business innovation. Ability to thrive in a dynamic and fast-paced environment - Project Management Skills - well-organized, structured approach. Ability to achieve tight timelines on complex deliverables. Ability to manage and prioritize projects across cross-functional groups - Hands on knowledge on tools like SAS, SQL, R and other analytics tools   About the Team GOFinance Consumer Risk team manages the Credit, Fraud and Operational Risk side of the lending business. The Head of Portfolio Risk Management will supervise a team of 3 Risk analysts.  
Our Objective as part of GoTo’s Risk Team, especially as the Financial Services Platform Risk Team, is to ensure a safe and trusted platform that our users can trust, rely on, and love to come back to. Based in Jakarta, Indonesia, our team manages the Credit and  Fraud Risk side of the consumer lending business. Our team consists of multi-background individuals. We work together to anticipate and predict potential credit risk and fraud threats by building tools to minimize the credit and fraud loss whilst maximizing net revenue. We partner closely with several cross-functional teams to ensure safe and sustainable business growth and reliable financial services for our users, our GoTo businesses, and our extended ecosystem. Our team is constantly working on projects that continuously bolster our risk management framework, maintain the highest standard of best practices, and improve the resilience of our GTF services products. This is a particularly exciting time to join our family as we’re focused on scaling this team to support GoTo’s growing markets, businesses, and future product launches, propelling our services to all corners of the globe. The questions that are always in the back of our minds are: How do we push the envelope in fortifying our risk mitigation efforts, making them stronger than their last iterations, and how can we effectively increase risk awareness throughout all factions of our company?
When we aren’t busy fighting potential credit risks and fraud on our business as usual, you’d probably find us binge-watching Netflix shows, testing out new food spots around town (mostly ordering in to social distance), and chatting about our coming week on our regular Zoom calls. Once COVID subsides, we’re excited to be able to meet and socialize over a meal again.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloud Infra Engineer - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/98314bd4-cf8a-45d9-a9e5-2f1476646776</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Cloud Infrastructure Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Commerce Enablement team based in Jakarta, Indonesia. Focusing your efforts on empowering our product engineers to drive their performance to the next level, you’ll take the wheel in ensuring operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and high availability of the system from an infrastructure point of view. Your infrastructure and standardization designs will not only be implemented for the CE group alone, but throughout the Gojek ecosystem as a whole.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 08:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Campaign &amp; Consumer Engagement Associate - Jakarta</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9dc870da-b5ac-4411-b447-cb2b291b0210</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a high-functioning, dynamic team whose efforts directly impact our user base, this may be the role for you. As our Campaign &amp; Consumer Engagement Associate for the Indo Region team and based in Jakarta, you’ll take the wheel in hacking consumer growth for Gojek in Jakarta. You’ll take the time to deeply understand our consumers’ preferences and concerns, then create consumer segmentation and experimentation programs that fit each segments’ needs. Working closely with the Regional Sales Manager and District Operation Manager you’ll get to drive the innovation process of removing daily frictions from our consumers’ lives through tech-based solutions, delivering a real social impact along the way.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Strategy, Financial Management</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f607a972-7756-41f2-bf7d-67d8d9710304</link><description>If you’re seeking a good challenge and a chance to take the next leap in your career, this role is for you. In Business Strategy for Financial Management, you’ll be part of a team responsible for allowing a customer to manage their money and linked sources of money. This would include the linked accounts, balances, digital account openings, history, categorisation of expenses, insights and actionable recommendations, default in/out channels for payments.
You’ll take charge over problem-solving processes and execute solutions focused on improving demand and growth metrics for the platform. Combining business strategy, customer experience, and behavior analysis, you’ll conduct experiments and execute campaigns that’ll encourage our users to experience the product’s core value as quickly as possible. Throughout this exciting experience, you’ll build relationships with internal and external stakeholders, from product, marketing, research, and operation team among others to meet the fast-paced nature of the financial technology industry.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 05:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Strategy Associate Manager - 7184</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f3870c5e-4f3b-4052-a095-a8d6cf56f737</link><description>About the Role

We’re looking for talented individuals to join us on our mission to become an indispensable business partner for merchants and to help them succeed and thrive in Indonesia as Business Strategy Associate Manager.

The Merchant lifecycle team acts as the business team for the Merchant Platform product. As a Business Strategy Associate Manager, You will work together with the GTM Core Services Lead and other product/business teams to create a go-to-market strategy for GoBiz App. You need to collaborate closely with the product, sales, marketing, ops team for product rollout and adoption of platform features and/or various use cases hosted by GoBiz App. In your day-to-day execution, You will need to monitor and analyze key metrics to produce insights and take initiatives/propose solutions to enhance the product/business process so that we can provide better services/products for our merchants.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 06:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Manager - Risk</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/920c6226-f1cf-4a75-9986-321c0645ec38</link><description>About the Role 

As a Business Intelligence Manager in our Risk Data team, you will lead a team of business intelligence analysts responsible for intelligence and data products which empower our sophisticated risk decisions in protecting GoPay and its customers. You will drive strategic directions of Risk BI and solve some of the most impactful and stimulating business problems in the payments space by partnering with Risk, product, engineering, and data science partners. You will work in a fast-paced environment with direct impacts to the business.



</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 03:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Analyst - Risk</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3abb32ee-c9f1-4b56-8b01-889b42b7d7a7</link><description>About the Role 

As a Business Intelligence Analyst in our Risk Data team, you will develop intelligence and data products which empower our sophisticated risk decisions in protecting GoPay and its customers. You will have the opportunity to work with rich data and partner with Risk, product, engineering, and data science partners to identify and solve some of the most impactful and stimulating business problems in the payments space. You will work in a fast-paced environment with direct impacts to the business.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 03:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Analyst - Merchant Platform</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/bb21f069-dedf-45c8-a596-31dea464a2fc</link><description>About the Role

As our Business Intelligence Analyst for the Merchant Platform, you’ll collaborate with other cross-functional teams (Product Managers, Business Strategist, Marketing, Research, and Data Science) to find useful business insights within a large amount of data. You’ll assist these teams in setting up success metrics for particular products/features, optimize existing services and systems, and ensure data quality and source of truth availability. 

On a daily basis, you’ll process data streams to produce data foundation, analytical dashboards, and product / feature trackers. Here, you'll get a front row seat in understanding how one of the largest Asian SuperApps makes use of its data. Your efforts will help remove highly-complex analytical blockers presented to the team, and contribute to the overall expansion and efficiency of Gojek's Merchant platform. 


</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Analyst</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d8c1265a-9087-48b2-addf-6f256eadf70e</link><description>About the Role

If you’re looking to be a part of a dynamic, highly analytical team who enjoys working with data, look no further. GoClub is a loyalty product that shapes Gojek’s long-term customer loyalty as part of the Loyalty, Partnership &amp; Monetisation (LPM) group. Your mission as a Data Analyst in Goclub is to use data that enhances our understanding about customer’s behaviour that shapes long-term loyalty. You will be involved in various initiatives, such as building data products to support the team,  be a steward for data driven business initiatives, and partner with the business team and product team and make great products together. From day one, you will learn and  work to solve some of the most challenging initiatives that produce high-value customers!


</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 07:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Intelligence - Financial Services</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b6c7839a-1400-4640-8fc9-b41dd4ae86d9</link><description>About the Role

In GoTo, we put a really high value on data. To get insight, and knowledge and eventually make a decision. That’s why one of our company values is “Become a Scientist”. As a BI Analyst, you will have tons of data to play with. From voices of customers and transactional information, just to name a few. You will be dealing with dashboards, and reports and even take part in experimentation to determine the best strategy. You will have close interactions with multiple stakeholders within the Insurance team and other teams in GoTo Financials Services.

</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 04:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brand Strategy &amp; Planning Lead</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f77d9fce-e034-4f42-83f7-f9c05783846e</link><description>About the Role

If you have the heart of a scientist and a curiosity of a cat, if you see data not just as numbers but a mean to tell a story, If you believe that there is always a way to solve a problem as long as we have good insights, then you might be the one we are looking for.

As Brand Strategy and Planning Lead for Gojek’s Brand Marketing team, you will get to work with other talented teams in Gojek - from product analyst, Research and Insights, in app and CRM teams - mining insights from internal/external data, which translates into a brand and communication strategy. You will spend a majority of your time diving deep into some of the most challenging analytical problems in the Gojek brand - in the very core of Gojek's vast ecosystem. The cherry on top: you’ll get to be a part of a team that works to create not only the most loved brand but also contributes to a sustainable growth of the Gojek brand.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Associate IT Internal Auditor</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/36164174-b1c8-420a-916d-c641a9563a07</link><description>About the Role 

In GoTo, the growth of our business is continuously challenged by the fast pace of technology development and regulatory changes. In this role, you will be part of the Internal Audit Team based in Indonesia. Focusing heavily on providing assurance by evaluating and improving the control process. you will employ analytical thinking skills, and communication skills, and be able to adapt to a fast phase environment in an effort to deliver the audit successfully. In our humble opinion, the coolest part is your ability to be eloquent in delivering communication with stakeholders and have high enthusiasm for learning.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Android Engineer - Mapan</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/83f9f2a5-cf38-4303-a9d1-66e6ab46dd55</link><description>About the Role

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our next Android Engineer. In this role, you will be an integral player in the Mapan Mobile team based in Jakarta, Indonesia - a team whose efforts are especially catered to aid lower-income users attain additional income through our platform. In collaboration with UX and backend teams, you'll get to build a large-scale, high-performing, fault-tolerant Android app for Gojek, providing simple, easy to use services for our users. With knowledge of the general mobile landscape, current user preferences and trends, and emerging technologies in the mobile engineering field, you'll employ your technical expertise and clean coding skills to deliver tangible solutions that'll bring a positive socioeconomic impact to all who use our app.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 07:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Manager (Sumatra) - MokaPOS</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8862fdba-c999-48b3-917f-aa179b6e3229</link><description>We are looking for a competent Account Manager  to find business opportunities and manage customer relationships in the F&amp;B and Retail industry in Sumatra Area. You’ll be directly responsible for the preservation and expansion of our key customer base.

The ideal candidate will be a candidate who has experience in customer service and sales. We expect you to be a reliable professional, who is able to balance customer orientation and a results-driven approach. Your overarching goal is to identify opportunities with prospects and new clients and build them into profitable long-term relationships.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 09:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Manager (East Indonesia) - MokaPOS - 7523</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6ddef7e3-1174-43cc-b6be-9d839185c613</link><description>We are looking for a competent Account Manager  to find business opportunities and manage customer relationships in the F&amp;B and Retail industry in East Indonesia Area. You’ll be directly responsible for the preservation and expansion of our key customer base.

The ideal candidate will be a candidate who has experience in customer service and sales. We expect you to be a reliable professional, who is able to balance customer orientation and a results-driven approach. Your overarching goal is to identify opportunities with prospects and new clients and build them into profitable long-term relationships.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 09:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive Pontianak</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/36816cf3-41e6-4058-939d-33e531d425b0</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Pontianak, you’ll be part of the East Indonesia Region team that oversees Gojek's merchant partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, as well as building and maintaining relationships with merchant partner networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions during this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, respect, and opportunities that they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive Bekasi</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8455043a-591b-4022-9e5c-60541531e949</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Bekasi, you’ll be part of the Jabodetabek Region team that oversees Gojek's merchant partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, as well as building and maintaining relationships with merchant partner networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions during this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, respect, and opportunities that they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 11:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive - Tangerang</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b84fabb8-bd26-4637-9952-e0fe7adcc405</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Tangerang, you’ll be part of the Indonesia Regional Sales team that oversees Gojek's merchant-partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, maintaining current merchant-partner campaigns, as well as building and strengthening relationships with merchant networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions on this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant-partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, care, and opportunities they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive - South Jakarta</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0261f8d6-269a-4c6e-ac10-90d1f2e95016</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Jakarta, you’ll be part of the Indonesia Regional Sales team that oversees Gojek's merchant-partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, maintaining current merchant-partner campaigns, as well as building and strengthening relationships with merchant networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions on this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant-partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, care, and opportunities they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive - North Jakarta</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cc23b672-1253-4b88-8e04-45cc89c8ba9a</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Jakarta, you’ll be part of the Indonesia Regional Sales team that oversees Gojek's merchant-partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, maintaining current merchant-partner campaigns, as well as building and strengthening relationships with merchant networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions on this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant-partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, care, and opportunities they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 03:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive - East Jakarta</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f034ef93-40da-46f8-abd1-bdc18f69a32b</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Jakarta, you’ll be part of the Indonesia Regional Sales team that oversees Gojek's merchant-partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, maintaining current merchant-partner campaigns, as well as building and strengthening relationships with merchant networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions on this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant-partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, care, and opportunities they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive - Balikpapan</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/d3beee33-1898-488f-96e8-da5c967bbe52</link><description>About the Role

Strap on your helmet and climb on board if you're ready to be our Account Executive. Based in Balikpapan, you’ll be part of the East  Indonesia Region team that oversees Gojek's merchant partners in the area. You'll play a critical role in executing sales strategy, as well as building and maintaining relationships with merchant partner networks here (including regular visits upon assigned leads!). The Merchant Engagement and Sales Support team will be your companions during this ride. You will get ample opportunity to flex and utilize your excellent business sense and market knowledge. Perhaps the most meaningful of all: your efforts will work to enhance the lives and businesses of our millions of merchant partners in Indonesia, providing them with the attention, respect, and opportunities that they deserve.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 03:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Online Commerce) Sales Executive (Jabodetabek) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0b90a0aa-1ef8-4db7-9282-897d7958e0d0</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for Online Commerce. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Online Commerce solution. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 02:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Tegal) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cdb7a662-aa63-4090-ba56-49c1d948dd6c</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Tegal region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 02:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Tasikmalaya) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/0c19261c-7fe8-4729-8147-1aa607749629</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Tasikmalaya region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 03:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Surabaya) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/2c560654-a0c4-4193-b83b-fa8b5616c7e9</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Surabaya region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 05:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Solo) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/fb0dd212-d3d0-4387-bde4-1abb3a0567a8</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Solo region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Semarang) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/9cb8a1d7-f381-44c8-b95c-4e69457eb6be</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Semarang region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Samarinda) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/6cfdcf86-1ea9-4364-9269-426a20421161</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Samarinda region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Purwokerto) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/faaeb910-3c8a-4ebf-bdf2-f87d6aa72d92</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Purwokerto region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 02:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Pontianak) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3f9af71a-8a20-4234-bb18-a97a24a05d94</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Pontianak region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Pekalongan) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/e26456de-a881-420f-90d1-d3f02692b552</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Pekalongan region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Pati) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/cd12988a-58aa-43cd-8073-6afde197eff3</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Pati region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 02:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Palu) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/f10623a3-6f88-4e7b-b58e-b6960f887141</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Palu region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 08:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Palembang) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/45c13e8c-f41b-43f2-b896-23b81b2cca15</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Palembang region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 11:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Palangkaraya) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/512eeadd-ac98-450c-9132-2ef8b88ebe23</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Palangkaraya region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 13:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Padang) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/aa0799fc-a7bb-4acd-9a44-714688d05e3b</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Padang region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 13:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Manado) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/44eeb3b8-0aaf-48b4-a2b5-e1046474eff1</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Manado region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 06:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Makassar) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/bb202ce3-4157-4d9a-b3a0-261ca2530e02</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Makassar region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Lampung) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/422768e1-943d-4b26-b976-716ad9110041</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Lampung region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 06:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Karawang) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/8598a2d6-efd7-47b3-a9ba-7b08370134bb</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Karawang region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 02:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Jogja) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/14d69a87-631b-45fd-ad26-8544e7f9913c</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Jogja region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 11:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Cirebon) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/b9027968-4d7f-45f0-b52e-86e94333606a</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Cirebon region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.

</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Banjarbaru) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/83499ab0-a121-4242-8b63-8206b8bd42ad</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Banjarbaru region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 10:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Bandung) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/4134bccd-da91-45e6-9061-9002b76d3be4</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Bandung region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Balikpapan) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/45ba94f1-854e-466d-bc3f-2ce5051168bc</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Balikpapan region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Moka) Sales Executive (Bali) - Commerce Enablement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/gojek/3657e361-d2f6-4c31-ba97-be74fc24aa6e</link><description>About the Role 

Fasten your helmet and climb on board if you’re ready to be our Sales Executive for the Bali region. In this role, you’ll focus your efforts on scouting out potential merchant-partners, boosting merchant acquisition initiatives, and spreading awareness about our Point of Sales system. You’ll go the extra mile to better understand our merchant-partners' concerns and experiences on the field to resolve their pain points, and relay the information you gather to our Product and Business development teams. Your efforts will help enhance our merchant-partners’ daily operations, and better position our platform as the most trusted solution provider in the region and beyond.


</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>