<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Polygon Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/Polygon?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Polygon from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:13:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Staff Software Engineer, Backend - Risk and Fraud</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/7540f8c7-ebc5-4f1c-8cbc-950f5ea7a331</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

As the Staff Engineer, you will own the architecture and technical vision for the systems driving a complex, major domain at Dave. You will spend the vast majority of your time designing elegant testable/scalable solutions, implementing secure applications, collaborating with product managers and engineers to deliver an exceptional experience to our Dave members. 

You will report directly to the Director of Engineering and help architect a technical vision for the Risk team to centralize our systems for compliance requirements and reduce/prevent fraud. You will be embedded in the Risk team but also collaborate with Data, Compliance and Fraud teams within Dave to guide the implementation of the Risk technical roadmap. You will help mentor and elevate other engineers at Dave to ensure a high technical bar of our solutions.

If you are someone who thrives on collaborating to solve hard problems, are passionate about finding innovative solutions, delights customers, and inspires colleagues, then this role is for you!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 23:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. User Acquisition Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/55e5f1f4-5542-4db9-ace0-d84de978d79f</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Dave is looking for an experienced, performance driven and resourceful Sr. User Acquisition Manager to lead the expansion and diversification of Dave’s growth channels.
The ideal person for this role has a passion for our mission with a strategic mind to help grow our business and establish Dave as America’s fintech brand. We want you to help raise the bar of Dave’s user acquisition strategy, bringing fresh ideas to and pushing us to the next level as a business. 

You will partner with stakeholders across the business to deliver user acquisition and re-engagement marketing for the full suite of products that Dave has to offer. You will own a substantial marketing budget and drive growth by building, measuring, optimizing and scaling a portfolio of paid media channels including but not limited to TV, Radio, Podcast, Mail, Affiliate, Job Boards, OOH. Success in the position requires expert problem-solving &amp; experimentation skills, a strong analytical and growth hacker mentality, and a passion for growth marketing.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 20:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Full Stack</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/b893e649-40b8-4746-bdd5-6ecca0e10c0d</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

Dave is looking for talented Senior Engineers to play an instrumental role in building products that help millions of people improve their relationship with money.  We're looking for passionate software engineers interested in full stack development.  If you're excited to join a tight-knit collaborative team with a mission of helping others, we'd love to hear from you.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer, Backend</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/c3156840-a1d1-43ba-a0af-58eca728b9ef</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

Dave is looking for a talented Senior Backend Engineer to continue building the foundation that empowers the engineers to build products that help millions of people improve their relationship with money. If you're excited to join a tight-knit collaborative team with a mission of helping others, we'd love to hear from you!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 19:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Manager - Credit</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/b502fb52-0be7-46e1-8ac2-efc1344b08a2</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

We are looking for a Senior Product Manager to join our Credit Group. This role will focus on Dave’s flagship ExtraCash product, with the aim of driving product growth, retention and margin performance through innovative underwriting algorithms and intuitive product design.   You will develop and evangelize the strategic roadmap for your product, as well as work to integrate with features across the Dave product suite, ensuring an integrated and robust customer experience. Our ideal candidate has a track record of success in creating and owning consumer facing Fintech products, while working in close collaboration with internal stakeholders.  While not your direct reports, critical to your success will be the ability to lead a team of designers, data scientists, and engineers while partnering with marketing, legal, finance and other cross functional teams to evolve our product to a place that creates more value for our members and our business. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Product Designer, Growth</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/225c1f00-0360-4474-b7db-8744b04b1f1a</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

As a Senior Product Designer aligned to the Growth Team, you’ll focus on creating targeted paths that help our users succeed. Whether it’s designing dedicated landing pages for a particular user category or developing rapid experiments to gather specific user insights, you’ll be engaging our users in ways that are truly meaningful to them and their unique needs.  

We’re looking for an on-trend, high-value aesthetic designer who thrives in the 0 to 1 space. We're not looking for growth hacks or spammy marketing tactics. It will be your responsibility to create and optimize a sustainable experience that leads to long-term, engaged users. 

To accomplish all this, you'll need to have a strong ability to balance user needs with business metrics at the widest of angles, an interest in solving fundamental user needs (like, access to money), and strong capacity to design for users who’s daily lives, circumstances, and needs might be very different than your own.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 19:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior People Partner (HRBP)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/4cde5a04-6f02-4670-bd02-526ddf8c80ed</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

As a Sr. People Partner, you support the senior leadership team and people leaders to achieve their business goals through a proactive talent strategy.  Equally important, you are viewed as a trusted coach and advisor to Daves on issues or opportunities impacting their engagement and success here at Dave.  You are deeply committed to the success of the organization and the teams that you support.  

Because of this, you help people leaders see what might be getting in their way of being more effective; you’ll work to uncover and consistently get ahead of challenges that could impact team performance and engagement. This could include employee relations, organizational design, role definition, career development or compensation.

As a People Partner, you’ll lead through change, ensuring adoption and buy-in of people programs that will help our employees thrive, reach their full potential through proactive talent strategies, and achieve Dave’s mission of building products that level the financial playing field.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Financial Platform and Risk</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/490d4d52-a7cd-4b71-80b8-a5f9c1c0f64b</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

As the Senior  Engineering Manager, you will own the engineering roadmap and technical landscape for the systems driving various product features at Dave. You will spend the vast majority of your time coaching and empowering engineers and managers, collaborating with product managers and business stakeholders to deliver an exceptional experience to our users.

You will report directly to the Director of Engineering and lead the engineering roadmap and vision for the Risk team to centralize our systems for compliance requirements, and reduce/prevent fraud. You will be collaborating with Product, Data, Compliance, Fraud teams at Dave to understand the problem space and deliver creative solutions. You will help mentor and elevate other engineers at Dave to ensure a high technical bar of our solutions.

If you are someone who thrives on collaborating to solve hard problems, are passionate about finding innovative solutions, delights customers, and inspires colleagues, then this role is for you!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 16:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Engineering Manager - Customer Lifecycle Group</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/c8ace765-2a18-4a14-8de3-348d23fbc787</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

As the Senior  Engineering Manager, you will own the engineering roadmap and technical landscape for the systems driving various product features at Dave. You will spend the vast majority of your time coaching and empowering engineers and managers,  collaborating with product managers and business stakeholders to deliver an exceptional experience to our users.

You will report directly to the Director of Engineering and lead the engineering roadmap and vision for the Customer Lifecycle Group to increase conversion, improve user experience on Dave with security and scalability in mind. You will be collaborating with Product, Data, Security, Member Success teams at Dave to understand the problem space and deliver creative solutions. You will help mentor and elevate other engineers at Dave to ensure a high technical bar of our solutions.

If you are someone who thrives on collaborating to solve hard problems, are passionate about finding innovative solutions, delights customers, and inspires colleagues, then this role is for you!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Developer Productivity Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/882a3f37-a2ee-4b34-8916-0b9330b1f6d7</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Dave is looking for an experienced Software Engineer in our Developer Productivity Engineering team to play an integral role in helping our Developers build quality products while shortening our product development lifecycle. This team’s mission is to help accelerate our product development lifecycle by building the next generation of CICD pipeline and automation tools so that our product development teams can focus on delivering an awesome virtual banking experience for our customers.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Designer, Design Systems</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/1bcb6bff-2525-49a0-8881-477bb9ab9943</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

We are building a high quality, high performing Design team.  If you have a strong sense of empathy, constantly look for ways to impact users' lives at scale and are curious, committed to collaboration and continuous learning and development, then this is the place for you. This is an opportunity to get in early and be a formative part of establishing the design culture here at Dave.

The design team is comprised of four distinct pillars (research, experience design, operations, and design systems/platform) The design platform team is integral  to the success of all our initiatives and spans content, illustration, design library, ui components, color, type, etc. In short, the components required to create a meaningful, beautiful, stateful experience. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Brand Marketing Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/1185ae14-a810-4363-961d-392d89c9c039</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Dave is looking for its first Sr. Brand Marketing Manager who will focus on the positioning of the company brand, developing brand campaigns, and collaborating with PMM to build a meaningful story between product and brand for Dave’s members. This role is well-grounded in achieving creative excellence and long-term brand health for Dave in a way that is meaningful to its members. The ideal person for this role has a strong background in developing effective, creative, and insights-driven brand strategies. They demonstrate cultural curiosity around the trends and drivers that are shaping consumer behavior. They are an ambitious doer with the unique ability to solve problems, collaborate, and drive cross-organizational alignment on some of our most timely and high-priority brand initiatives. They are adept at balancing the need for exceptional work while keeping up with the pace of a hyper-growth organization.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Product Designer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/8a5432a2-f2f8-4f6b-b066-9d17101fc1c2</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Design is a business differentiator at Dave and we are building a high quality, high performing Design team. If you have a strong sense of empathy, constantly look for ways to impact users' lives at scale and are committed to collaboration and continuous development, then this is the place for you.  It is our job to deeply understand our members’ needs and experience so that we can deliver unique, approachable and meaningful solutions to their already stressful lives.  

Our team values shipping early and often while also holding a high bar for shipping great products by pushing our engineering and product counterparts to perfect the product experience. We do this through the practice of UX design, the development of design systems and tooling, product writing, and design research. We go to extraordinary lengths to produce world-class work, and you will get to both deploy your hard-earned experience and build your skills in an organization where your area of work is highly valued.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer, Backend</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/b91b534f-7764-4f2e-b5b1-469e2df00974</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

Dave is looking for a talented Lead Backend Engineer to continue building the foundation that empowers the engineers to build products that help millions of people improve their relationship with money. If you're excited to join a tight-knit collaborative team with a mission of helping others, we'd love to hear from you!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 05:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Product Manager - Banking</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/9ee21c9e-6fde-47d4-b903-d7c307e5a6ed</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

We are looking for a Senior Product Manager to join our Product Management team. This role will focus on developing, launching and optimizing Dave’s spend account on the Dave banking platform.  The mission for you and your squad will be to help Dave’s users manage and spend their money in a  simple, safe, and delightful way.  You will develop and evangelize the strategic roadmap for your product, as well as work to integrate with features across the Dave product suite, ensuring an integrated and robust customer experience.

Our ideal candidate has a track record of success in creating and owning FinTech products in a competitive space, specifically in neobanks, cards and/or payments.  This Senior PM will have a strong background in product management, and be well versed in building financial products in partnership with a diverse range of stakeholders and a partner bank. The Senior PM will be responsible for the strategy and roadmap for their product in collaboration with our stakeholders. 

Communication and cross-functional collaboration is critically important, especially in our virtual first environment.  You are accountable for the success of your products, even if you don’t control all the teams contributing to that success.  So you must be comfortable and confident in influencing your colleagues without authority. You should lead and influence your colleagues through building relationships and leveraging data.  Critical to your success will be your ability to build productive collaborative relationships not only within product development with Design and Engineering but also with Data, Marketing, Product Marketing, Business Operations, Member Success, Compliance, People, Legal and Risk.  Through your strong collaborative approach, you should be able to build alignment and execute relentlessly.

You’ll also be an excellent product manager with a history of partnering with engineering and product design to ship releases that move the needle and impact our KPI’s.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 20:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Scientist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/0a89b71e-1041-4143-a38f-d1b8b4cc3999</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

Dave is looking for an experienced and passionate lead data scientist in our Data organization. This role will partner directly with product managers, engineers, marketing and other business partners across the business to research, develop, deploy and continuously improve the machine learning solutions to drive growth at Dave and improve user experience for our customers. 
</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 14:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Data Engineer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/dave/ea74c311-ee16-4cdc-8720-6ee195d1a017</link><description>Dave (Nasdaq: DAVE) is on a mission to build products that level the financial playing field. Our banking app helps millions of members bank, budget, find work, build credit, and access up to $500 advances without paying a fee.  With a growing suite of tools and services, we provide a superior banking experience for anyone living paycheck to paycheck. We’re looking for high performers to be part of our journey to bring access to financial opportunity for everyone.

Team Overview

We are looking for an experienced and passionate Lead Data Engineer for our Data organization. This role will partner directly with product managers, engineers, marketing and other business partners across the business to design, develop and continuously improve the data infrastructure, pipeline and applications to collect, track and monitor various formats of data to enable data-driven decision and growth at Dave. 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>