<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Sfcg Job Postings</title><link>https://api.lever.co/v0/postings/sfcg?mode=json</link><description>Job postings for Sfcg from lever.co</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Youth Protection &amp; Inclusion Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/b46b7bee-007b-4025-b85d-8c12b0f9bafe</link><description>The Children &amp; Youth Division at Search for Common Ground seeks a full-time or part-time Youth, Peace and Security Inten to provide support for the Children and Youth division’s youth advocacy and fundraising efforts.

The Youth, Peace and Security Intern will assist the world’s largest dedicated peacebuilding NGO in shaping Youth, Peace and Security Coalition’s communications, meetings, and advocacy strategies as well as doing research on fundraising opportunities for Youth, Peace and Security advocacy and supporting grant drafting. As the Youth, Peace and Security intern, you will be working closely with the core team of advocacy experts that are a part of the U.S. Youth, Peace and Security Coalition and the CY team.
If you are a student and would like to earn course credit from your internship, we are willing to work with you to develop a comprehensive workload that is relevant to your field of study and professional interests. 
 
We want our interns to make the most of this experience. To this end, we ask every intern to develop a set of strategic learning objectives at the beginning of their internship with their supervisor, outlining their key learning and professional needs. Search for Common Ground’s staff will work with you to ensure assignments are relevant to these learning objectives, and that you continue to grow throughout your internship.  
  

</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Termes de Références   Appel à Candidature pour Soumission d’Offre Technique et Financière</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/c35e5666-0756-41ae-a7da-8a9a1daeece3</link><description>À propos d’organisation
Search for Common Ground (SFCG) est une organisation internationale à but non lucratif créée en 1982. Elle a pour mission de transformer la façon dont sont gérés les conflits en favorisant des approches collaboratives plutôt que la confrontation. SFCG cherche à contribuer à une paix durable en se focalisant sur les activités communautaires, le dialogue et la médiation, ainsi que la production médiatique. SFCG a environ 750 employés dans le monde et des projets dans 35 pays au monde. SFCG est présente au Niger depuis 2011 et dispose de bureaux à Niamey, Diffa, Tahoua et Tillabéry ainsi que de studios de production radio à Niamey et à Diffa. Notre staff comprend des experts en matière de transformation des conflits et de gestion de projets promouvant la paix et le dialogue. SFCG possède une grande expertise dans le domaine du renforcement des capacités des jeunes pour prévenir l’extrémisme violent afin de promouvoir la paix. En effet, l’implication des jeunes dans la paix est au cœur des objectifs stratégiques de cette organisation.

 À propos du projet
Situées au Sud-Ouest du Niger, les régions de Tillabéri et celle voisine de Tahoua ont été fortement déstabilisées par les crises du Mali et du Burkina Faso voisins. Les attaques perpétrées par des groupes armés non-étatiques (GANE), pas toujours revendiquées, se sont multipliées au cours des deux dernières années dans les communes situées au niveau de la bande frontalière avec le Mali et le Burkina Faso. Les attaques de plus en plus meurtrières contre les positions des Forces Armées Nigériennes (FAN) d’Inatès (décembre 2019), de Chinagoder (janvier 2020) et plus récemment contre le camp de la Garde Nationale Nigérienne (GNN) à Ayorou (mars 2020) font craindre une montée en puissance de l’État Islamique au Grand Sahara (EIGS) dans la zone. Ciblant avant tout les forces de défense et de sécurité (FDS), les GANE s’en prennent également aux chefs traditionnels et religieux qui ont fait l’objet d’enlèvements et d’assassinats ciblés depuis la mi-2019. En outre, les communautés sont victimes d’extorsions régulières, en particulier les éleveurs nomades qui sont sommés de payer un impôt (zakat), tandis que des écoles ont été incendiées et des infrastructures pillées ou détruites au cours de l’année passée, la réponse de l’État Nigérien vise avant tout à préserver l’intégrité territoriale et contenir le débordement des conflits qui touchent les États voisins. Bien que le Gouvernement prenne en considération les dynamiques locales qui contribuent à l’instabilité, y compris par l'intermédiaire de l’action de la Haute Autorité de la Consolidation de la Paix (HACP), sa stratégie sécuritaire présente le risque d’être contre-productive en nourrissant les frustrations et la vulnérabilité des populations vis-à-vis des appels des groupes extrémistes violents. Ces éléments associés à la faible présence de l'État, aux déplacements des populations et à l’existence de conflits préexistants à la crise actuelle, créent un terreau fertile à l’extrémisme violent, surtout auprès des jeunes en manque de perspectives et souvent exclus des sphères de prise de décisions.  Dans l’optique de répondre à ces facteurs contribuant à la violence structurelle affectant les populations du Niger que Search implémente un projet de 24 mois, afin de Contribuer à la stabilisation des communes frontalières des régions de Tillabéri et Tahoua au Niger. 
Ce projet intitulé “ Mu Gina Gobé. Construisons demain’’ pour but deposer les bases d’une stabilisation à long terme des communes frontalières du Nord-Tillabéri et de Tahoua. Ce projet a été financé par la Commission de l’Union Européenne à travers l’Instrument contribuant à la Stabilité et à la Paix (IcSP). Cet objectif se décline en trois objectifs spécifiques : 
OS.1. Renforcer la confiance entre forces de défense et de sécurité, autorités et populations
OS.2. Renforcer la cohésion verticale entre autorités civiles, coutumières et populations
OS.3. Renforcer la cohésion horizontale inter et intra-communautaire
La théorie du Changement du projet est la suivante :
SI la sécurité telle que perçue par les populations est améliorée sous l’effet d’un processus de renforcement de la confiance et de la collaboration entre leadership communautaire et forces de défense et de sécurité;
SI les communautés et la société civile collaborent avec les autorités locales formelles et informelles pour la mise en œuvre d’initiatives conjointes de réhabilitation des infrastructures en adéquation avec certains besoins de base des populations dans le cadre d’un processus de dialogue transparent et inclusif, mis en œuvre de façon séquencée et coordonnée avec les acteurs des secteurs humanitaire et développement; 
SI les mécanismes de médiation et de résolution de conflits formels et informels sont renforcés pour permettre aux autorités et aux communautés de prévenir et gérer pacifiquement les différends; 
ET SI l’ensemble des acteurs ont accès àdes informations crédibles, vérifiées et sensibles au conflit sur la situation sociopolitique et sécuritaire locale ; 
ALORS la cohésion horizontale (intra-inter-communautaire) et la cohésion verticale (État-populations) seront renforcées, contribuant à minimiser ainsi certains éléments de vulnérabilité des populations ciblées à l’extrémisme violent et jetant les bases d’un processus de stabilisation de long terme dans les zones frontalières des régions de Tillabéri et Tahoua. 

Les résultats escomptés du projet sont :

Les différents résultats sont attendus de l’intervention : 
R.1.1 La collaboration entre les populations et les forces de défense et de sécurité pour l’amélioration de la sécurité est renforcée ;
R.1.2 Un processus de changement de comportements des forces de défense et de sécurité est amorcé ;
R 1.3. Le partage d’informations et la coordination entre FDS, autorités et communautés sont renforcés; R.2.1. Les capacités des autorités et des communautés à analyser et répondre aux conflits sont renforcées; R.2.2. Des projets de stabilisation sont définis et mis en œuvre conjointement par les autorités et les communautés ;
R3.1. La cohésion sociale inter et intra-communautaire est renforcée ;
R.3.2. L’architecture de paix locale est renforcée

Objectifs de l’évaluation finale
L’évaluation finale du projet “ Mu Gina Gobé’’ vise à mesurer le rendement du projet dans une perspective critique et objective qui favorisera l'apprentissage pour Search. Le/la consultant(e) ou le Cabinet d’études devra :
1. Mesurer les changements imputables aux actions du projet dans les communes cibles sur la base des indicateurs de performance objectivement vérifiables ;
2. Apprécier le changement de perception dans la relation de confiance entre forces de défense et de sécurité, autorités et populations, la cohésion horizontale et verticale ; 
3. Analyser la mise en œuvre du projet sur la base des critères de la CAD/OCDE parallèlement à celle des indicateurs de performance du projet.
4. Identifier et documenter les succès, les bonnes pratiques, les insuffisances relevées et les enseignements tirés, de même que les contraintes et opportunités relatives à la mise en œuvre du projet ;
5. Formuler des recommandations pertinentes pour ce projet qui s'achève et pour la conception de projets futurs sur la thématique de stabilisation des zones affectés par l’insécurité et prévention à l’extrémisme violent chez les jeunes (Proposez des actions concrètes à mettre en place par Search dans le cadre des objectifs de ce projet).
Les résultats de l’évaluation finale seront partagés avec l’UE et rendus publics sur le site internet de SFCG pour large diffusion. Pour évaluer le changement atteint suite à la mise en œuvre du projet, le consultant/cabinet postulant devront suggèrer un certain nombre de questionnements auxquels l’évaluation devra apporter des éléments de réponses : https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/132dhT-iNhwLAxmabzjm9_fdp-TLutMfn

</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Manager, State Resilience Program</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/dab9999d-5ff3-4644-8117-6064c6dc4b7f</link><description>Title: Senior Manager - State Resilience Program
Reports to: Executive Director
Department: Common Ground USA
Team: State Resilience 

Team Summary  

​​Recognizing the severity of the challenges we face requires nothing less than the best of all of us. We work to foster social cohesion—pushing back on toxic polarization—for a new way forward, built from our experience of supporting recovery from violent conflict in dozens of countries around the world.

Together, Search for Common Ground’s Common Ground USA (Search/CG-USA) and Over Zero (OZ) will build state-wide leader networks. These networks will empower diverse civil society stakeholders with strengthened relationships, skills, and tools to collaboratively prevent rising tensions and political and electoral crises.
 
The program is committed to starting in one state, but is exploring work in multiple. These state-level networks will be built and scaled through 2025, spanning the 2022 midterms (early stage work) and the 2024 election cycle, its aftermath, and any additional flashpoints throughout this period. 

The perfect candidate is a visionary, seasoned, collaborative leader who derives purpose from growing and supporting a diverse team, and is passionate about conflict transformation, inclusive democracy, and coalition-building.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Request for Proposals for Communication Firm</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/a4f07d70-f4d4-4bde-9d1b-53ce22f7b3f5</link><description>Overview

Search for Common Ground, the world’s largest peacebuilding organization and nominee for the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize, is seeking an international communications and marketing firm to provide whole-of-organization support to our public-facing awareness-raising and mobilization-campaigns, donor-engagement processes, and amplification of our recently-refreshed brand. 

The right firm would provide immediate and substantive content-development and amplification support. Celebrating our 40th anniversary in 2022 with a recent brand-refresh and having recently launched our most ambitious domestic program in the United States, Search for Common Ground is well positioned for a significant increase in public awareness, relevance, influence and support, and seeks a firm that can support us to capitalize on this moment.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 20:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Recording Studio</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/f6cab15b-7b3f-45cb-995b-03cb5ef2132e</link><description>Search For Common Ground in Sudan is looking for a recording studio to produce a radio drama series of 30 episodes focusing on peacebuilding and transforming the way we deal with conflict. 

Search is an international conflict transformation NGO that aims to transform the way individuals, groups, governments and companies deal with conflict – away from adversarial approaches and towards collaborative solutions. Headquartered in Washington DC, USA, and Brussels, Belgium, with 52 field offices in 29 countries, Search designs and implements multifaceted, culturally appropriate and conflict-sensitive programs using a diverse range of tools, including media and training, to promote dialogue, increase knowledge and determine a positive shift in behaviors.
 
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 11:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Program Manager, State Resilience</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/208e4c82-da75-40f1-8f51-88c4c938526c</link><description>Title: Program Manager
Reports to: Senior Program Manager 
Department: Common Ground USA
Team: State Resilience 

Recognizing the severity of the challenges we face requires nothing less than the best of all of us, we work to foster social cohesion, pushing back on toxic polarization, for a new way forward, built from our experience of supporting recovering from violent conflict in dozens of countries around the world.

Together, Search for Common Ground’s Common Ground USA (Search/CG-USA) and Over Zero (OZ) will build state-wide leader networks. These networks will empower diverse civil society stakeholders with strengthened relationships, skills, and tools to collaboratively prevent rising tensions and political and electoral crises.
 
The program is committed to starting in one state, but is exploring work in multiple. These state-level networks will be built and scaled through 2025, spanning the 2022 midterms (early stage work) and the 2024 election cycle, its aftermath, and any additional flashpoints throughout this period. 

The ideal candidate is passionate about conflict transformation and coalition-building. They also have extensive experience in program management, implementation, and facilitation.  
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Program Director</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/4b072ae1-6f6a-46a4-a9a5-50e8cc9023bf</link><description>In order to better manage the expanding portfolio of Search Afghanistan, the organization is hiring an enthusiastic leader with attention to detail to fill the position of Program Director. The Program Director will play an active role in the business development, manage grants, and oversee program implementation to deliver high-impact programs that are compliant with both internal and donor regulations. The Program Director will build and lead a strong program team that will manage the day-to-day activities of the country office. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 10:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Program Assistant Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/1660ef46-0c06-4e67-b8bb-1a6772509a19</link><description>Summary of Internship:
Search offers paid internships (based in Tashkent) to support its program activities in Tashkent, Uzbekistan. Duration of the internship is agreed upon the finalization of the selection process. 
 
Your Contribution:
Intern will assist Search for Common Ground (Search) Uzbekistan team with implementing project activities. S/he will provide assistance in organizing meetings (national and regional), workshops across Uzbekistan, and preparing activity reports.  The intern reports to the Regional Advisor, Administrative and Finance Coordinator and works in close collaboration with Project Assistants.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MENA youth capacity facilitator</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/2a10845b-c771-4461-924e-df6eb956462c</link><description>Summary of position

Search for Common Ground’s Children &amp; Youth division seeks an Arabic and English-speaking Consultant to facilitate a program based on the Youth 360 methodology, developed by Search for Common Ground with our partners. Participants will be around 8 youth-led and youth-serving groups from the Middle East and North Africa region who are shortlisted to receive funding through a competitive process for climate mitigation and adaptation efforts. 

The Consultant must have working proficiency in both English and Arabic. The Consultant will work under the guidance of the Children &amp; Youth division’s program manager and will be responsible for designing and implementing capacity strengthening for the youth organizations over a period of around 9 months. This includes organizing a series of workshops and supporting the set-up of a mentorship program for the youth-led organisations.

It is possible for this position to be remote or located in the MENA Region.  
</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Journaliste/Assistant Média</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/80b51ba6-f7ba-4019-895a-b36b45cdea88</link><description>Search for Common Ground (Search) est une organisation non-gouvernementale basée à Washington DC et Bruxelles qui œuvre pour la transformation des conflits à l’échelle mondiale. Au cours de ses 40 années d’expérience, l’organisation a développé et consolidé une vision spécifique appelé Approche Common Ground qui s’appuie sur les deux principes suivants: (1) le conflit est inévitable, mais pas la violence; (2) le changement est toujours possible, et il est durable lorsque tout le monde est gagnant. 
 
L’action de Search en République Démocratique du Congo (RDC) s’inscrit dans cette vision globale. Présente depuis 2001 en RDC, Search met en œuvre des programmes qui s’articulent autour des questions liées au dialogue démocratique, à la sensibilité au conflit, au renforcement de la gouvernance, à la protection des civils et à la réforme du secteur de la sécurité et à la lutte contre les violences basées sur le genre, avec toujours une focalisation sur l’engagement des jeunes. S’appuyant sur une large palette d’outils méthodologiques (formation, médiation, mobilisation communautaire, communication à travers les médias et le théâtre participatif) et en étroite collaboration avec les partenaires locaux, la présence de Search est établie à Goma, Bukavu, Kalemie et Kinshasa, ainsi qu’à travers des bureaux satellites, notamment en Ituri. L’ensemble du staff de l’organisation en RDC est d’environ 110 personnes.
 
En consortium avec World Vision International, Search met en œuvre le projet de “ Response to Health and Protection needs of CAR refugees and their host communities in North and South Ubangi ”, un projet de durée de 12 mois qui vise entre autre à mproved protection services to respond to protection challenges, including MHPSS, SGBV, and CP dans le Nord et le Sud Ubangi. 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: Youth, Peace and Security</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/7574761e-9877-4f49-8e43-6460d9290a34</link><description>The Children &amp; Youth Division at Search for Common Ground seeks a full-time or part-time Youth, Peace and Security Inten to provide support for the Children and Youth division’s youth advocacy and fundraising efforts.

The Youth, Peace and Security Intern will assist the world’s largest dedicated peacebuilding NGO in shaping Youth, Peace and Security Coalition’s communications, meetings, and advocacy strategies as well as doing research on fundraising opportunities for Youth, Peace and Security advocacy and supporting grant drafting. As the Youth, Peace and Security intern, you will be working closely with the core team of advocacy experts that are a part of the U.S. Youth, Peace and Security Coalition and the CY team.
If you are a student and would like to earn course credit from your internship, we are willing to work with you to develop a comprehensive workload that is relevant to your field of study and professional interests. 
 
We want our interns to make the most of this experience. To this end, we ask every intern to develop a set of strategic learning objectives at the beginning of their internship with their supervisor, outlining their key learning and professional needs. Search for Common Ground’s staff will work with you to ensure assignments are relevant to these learning objectives, and that you continue to grow throughout your internship.  
  

</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 16:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: Youth Engagement</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/99026dd4-bbe2-46c7-8da3-f9da7264239d</link><description>The Children &amp; Youth Division at Search for Common Ground seeks a full-time or part-time Youth, Peace and Security Inten to provide support for the Children and Youth division’s youth advocacy and fundraising efforts.

The Youth, Peace and Security Intern will assist the world’s largest dedicated peacebuilding NGO in shaping Youth, Peace and Security Coalition’s communications, meetings, and advocacy strategies as well as doing research on fundraising opportunities for Youth, Peace and Security advocacy and supporting grant drafting. As the Youth, Peace and Security intern, you will be working closely with the core team of advocacy experts that are a part of the U.S. Youth, Peace and Security Coalition and the CY team.
If you are a student and would like to earn course credit from your internship, we are willing to work with you to develop a comprehensive workload that is relevant to your field of study and professional interests. 
 
We want our interns to make the most of this experience. To this end, we ask every intern to develop a set of strategic learning objectives at the beginning of their internship with their supervisor, outlining their key learning and professional needs. Search for Common Ground’s staff will work with you to ensure assignments are relevant to these learning objectives, and that you continue to grow throughout your internship.  
  

</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: Safeguarding</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/593ec7ea-c7e7-407b-b143-fe6a1e37308e</link><description>Search is seeking an intern to provide support to the HQ  Human Resources &amp; Administration Department. SFCG is seeking interns on a rolling basis (with immediate openings) to learn about Human Resources and Administration in a practical environment as a supplement to their studies. Interns will be involved in supporting an active, internationally-focused, non-profit organization in many different facets of HR &amp; Administration. Interns will be able to gain wide exposure to employee relations, data management and analysis, organizational policy strategy, benefits administration, audits, and other projects as they occur day to day in the department. This particular role, Policy &amp; Internal Compliance Intern, will work primarily on the production of e-learning modules about Search’s Policies.


</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: European Affairs and Partnership Policy and Outreach</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/45fe838f-6f10-499b-9ac3-6d3a68d5fcbf</link><description>Search for Common Ground seeks a professional, motivated intern for its European Affairs and Partnership (EAP) team to assist European advocacy and outreach activities. Candidates must be enrolled at university during the internship, and available for at least 30 hours per week for a period of four to six months from March 2021 onward. Depending on the intern’s individual learning goals and interests, which will be determined at the beginning of the internship, the EAP Policy &amp; Outreach Intern will gain the following knowledge and skills:

- Knowledge of peacebuilding and conflict transformation methodologies and programming
- Knowledge of the work of European institutions and European governments on the topic of peacebuilding and related fields 
- Experience of advocacy and outreach in the field of peacebuilding 
- Skills to better organize and prioritize own work, time management
- Expanded network in Brussels

Progress against the learning objectives will be monitored by the intern and their supervisor. The learning objectives and/or tasks may be modified during the internship if this is deemed appropriate by both parties. 

The EAP Policy &amp; Outreach Intern will be an integral part of the EAP team and Search Brussels Headquarters team. The intern’s responsibilities will depend on the internship priorities and will include:
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 01:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: ConnexUs Communications</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/0515dad8-fed2-413a-8eba-d911663c2455</link><description>The Institutional Learning Team
The Institutional Learning Team (ILT) sits within the Strategy Alignment Department, at the heart of the organization. The Team is led by the Director of DM&amp;E in Brussels and the Senior Program Manager, based in DC. ILT includes DME Specialists, Coordinators, &amp; Associates around the world, and includes the DME for Peace and ConnexUs Teams. 

ConnexUs
ConnexUs is a global learning and collaboration platform that provides peacebuilding, humanitarian, development, and public health practitioners, academics, researchers, and activists with an interactive space to address local and global challenges. With discussion forums, a resource library, a live feed, an events page, private messaging features, and a digital influencer network, ConnexUs is a dynamic and  comprehensive site to exchange ideas and create solutions. You can visit the platform at www.cnxus.org.

Job Description
Supervised by the Communications Officer, Search seeks two (2) ConnexUs Knowledge Management &amp; Communications Interns on the Institutional Learning Team.

We want our interns to have as rich of an experience as possible. Toward this end, we ask every intern to develop a set of strategic learning objectives at the beginning of their internship with their manager, outlining their key learning and professional development needs. ILT staff will work with you to ensure assignments are relevant to these learning objectives, to any practicum or school-related objectives, and that you continue to grow throughout your internship.
 
If you are a student and would like to earn course credit from your internship, we are willing to work with you to develop a rigorous workload that is relevant to your field of study and professional interests.
 
This internship requires a minimum commitment of 3 days per week.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: Common Ground USA</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/ce611843-e835-4c46-a2f1-519c1201d877</link><description>Common Ground USA, Search for Common Ground’s US-focused peacebuilding program is seeking interns who will support the team in project design, reporting, business development, and overall fundraising efforts that will contribute to building peace and transforming violent conflict across the country. 

The interns will join a newly-formed team of highly motivated and dynamic members  based in Washington D.C. who are passionate about designing and implementing impactful programs aimed to prevent political, hate-based, and extremist violence in America and foster the conditions for a more inclusive, equitable, and peaceful society.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship: Asia Programs</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/c1c3a472-c4f3-42d4-9e21-a22ce6af0286</link><description>Based in Washington, DC or Bishkek the Asia Program Intern will support Search's Asia regional grants management team and country offices in Kyrgyzstan, Afghanistan, Pakistan, and Indonesia. Duties of this internship will include developing program learning and communications materials, project reporting, managing project databases, and supporting regional initiatives.

</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 23:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Internship:  Jordan Country</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/d8470b3f-ed48-42ce-8f18-a4593f5ff28a</link><description>Position Summary
 
Search for Common Ground is seeking a professional, motivated and creative intern to join our Jordan team. Based in Amman, Jordan, the intern will provide support to Search’s Jordan programming under the supervision of the Project Manager. The internship offers an excellent opportunity for interns to develop professional skills in peacebuilding and conflict transformation. Interns must be available to work full-time (40 hours per week) and must commit for 6 months. We are looking for an intern to begin as soon as possible. This is a paid internship program, interns will be receiving a $500 stipend per month. 
</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 09:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingénieur en génie civil</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/99f36860-c38b-41b5-84fd-b5b2cd095b7f</link><description>Search   For Common Ground (Search) est une Organisation Non Gouvernementale   internationale qui œuvre dans le domaine de la paix à travers la   transformation des conflits. Elle est présente dans 34 pays au monde.   Conformément à sa stratégie d’intervention, l’ONG renforce les capacités des   acteurs de la société civile notamment les structures de jeunes et des femmes   dans le domaine de la consolidation de la paix afin de renforcer la   résilience communautaire. Elle travaille aussi à consolider les relations entre   les autorités administratives et les populations.
 Search   met en œuvre  un projet de 24 mois qui vise à promouvoir la   stabilisation économique, politique, sociale et environnementale et la   résilience des communautés vivant dans les communes frontalières du Burkina Faso et du Mali et à favoriser la   résolution locale des conflits et la prévention de l’extrémisme violent. Le   projet proposé cible les douze communes de la phase I, situées dans les   régions du Sahel (2) et du Nord (4) au Burkina Faso et dans la région de   Mopti (6) au Mali. Il s’appuiera sur le processus de consultation engagé pour   financer un minimum de douze projets d’infrastructures (une par commune) qui   seront assortis d’activités génératrices de revenus (AGR) et de mécanismes de   gestion et de résolution de conflits pérenne, contribuant à la fois au   développement socioéconomique et au renforcement de la cohésion sociale   horizontale et verticale.
Dans   le cadre de la mise en œuvre de ce projet Search est à la recherche d’un (e)   ingénieur en génie civil/infrastructure.     Il/elle sera basé(e) à Mopti (Mali).

Organisation du poste
Reporte au : Chef de Projet
Objectifs

De   façon générale, il s’agit de contribuer à la réalisation des infrastructures   hydrauliques et des périmètres maraichers dans les cercles de Koro et   Bankass
De façon spécifique, il s’agit   de :
●         Appuyer le chef de   projet dans la planification et la réalisation des infrastructures dans les   communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Contribuer à   l’identification et la validation des infrastructures à réaliser dans   les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Evaluer les risques   liés à la mise en œuvre du projet dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro,   Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Assurer la mise en   place et fonctionnement des comités de gestion des infrastructures dans les   communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Contribuer à   l’identification des prestataires pour la réalisation des   infrastructures  dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo,   Koro et Yoro ;
●         Assurer le suivi de   la réalisation des infrastructures  dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro,   Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Appuier les   Groupements dans la mise en œuvre des AGR en lien avec les   infrastructures  dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo,   Koro et Yoro ;
●         Contribuer à la   validation des infrastructures  dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro,   Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Participer à la   mobilisation des parties prenantes pour la mise en œuvre du projet  dans   les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Participer au   renforcement des capacités des parties prenantes du projet  dans les   communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura,     Bondo, Koro    et    Yoro ;
●         Produire des   rapports d’activité, les rapports mensuels et trimestriels et de toute autre   activité menée dans le cadre du projet ;
●         Contribuer à la mise   à jour des données sécuritaires en collaboration avec le département sécurité   dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura, Bondo, Koro et Yoro ;
●         Appuyer toute   l’équipe Search en cas de besoin dans la mise en œuvre des autres projets en   fonction de sa disponibilité dans les communes de Baye, Ouenkoro, Sokoura,   Bondo, Koro et Yoro 

Tâches et responsabilités principales
●         Appuyer le chef de projet dans la   planification et la réalisation des infrastructures ;
●         Contribuer à l’identification et la validation   des infrastructures à réaliser ;
●         Evaluer les risques liés à la mise en œuvre du   projet ;
●         Concevoir les caractéristiques techniques des   infrastructures ;
●         Assurer la mise en place et fonctionnement des   comités de gestion des infrastructures ;
●         Contribuer à l’identification des prestataires   pour la réalisation des infrastructures ;
●         Assurer le suivi de la réalisation des   infrastructures ;
●         Contribuer à la validation des   infrastructures ;
●         Appuier les Groupements dans la mise en œuvre   des AGR en lien avec les infrastructures ;
●         Participer à la mobilisation des parties   prenantes pour la mise en œuvre du projet ;
●         Participer au renforcement des capacités des   parties prenantes du projet ;
●         Produire des rapports d’activité, les rapports   mensuels et trimestriels et de toute autre activité menée dans le cadre du   projet ;
●         Contribuer à la mise à jour des données sécuritaires   en collaboration avec le département sécurité ;
●         Apuier toute l’équipe Search en cas de besoin   dans la mise en œuvre des autres projets en fonction de sa disponibilité.
Étant donné que les descriptifs de poste   ne peuvent pas être exhaustifs, le/la titulaire du poste pourra être amené à   entreprendre d'autres tâches qui correspondent globalement aux   responsabilités principales ci-dessus.
Compétences et qualifications
●         Diplômes désirés : Minimum   BAC +3 en en génie civil option   bâtiment/infrastructure et travaux publics 
●         Expérience requise : 5   ans d’expérience dans un poste similaire
 
Connaissances, compétences et capacités :
●         Connaissance technique dans la gestion des   projets et programmes de préférence les projets liés à la cohésion   sociale ;
●         Expérience dans la réalisation des   d’infrastructures de stockage et de réapprovisionnement en eau type forage ou   système d'adduction d’eau ; magasins de stockage de produits maraîchers   ou d’aliment pour le bétail ;
●         Expérience dans la mise en œuvre des   AGR ;
●         Expérience de travail dans les cercles de Koro   et Bankass ;
●         Expérience terrain avec les ONG ;
●         Bonne aptitude en communication ;
●         Sens de l’organisation et de la   négociation ;
●         Flexibilité, adaptabilité, et capacité à   travailler sous pression ;
●         Maîtrise des outils bureautiques Word, Excel,   Powerpoint, Internet ;
●         Respect des délais ;     
●         Bonne capacité en production de   rapports ;
●         Bonne capacité en analyse et synthèse.
 
Autres compétences clés : 
●       Travailler en équipe : La capacité de   respecter les opinions et les contributions des autres membres de l’équipe ;   faire preuve d'empathie, d’écoute, de soutien ; consulter les autres et partager   les informations et l'expertise, construire l'esprit d'équipe et s'adapter à   l'équipe.
●       Flexibilité : La capacité de   s'adapter à l'évolution des circonstances et des priorités, à tolérer   l'ambiguïté, à adapter le style personnel à différentes personnes et   situations.
●       Recherche de résultats et d’efficacité : La   capacité d'établir des normes de qualité, de surveiller et de maintenir la   qualité du travail et de fixer des objectifs pour atteindre une amélioration   continue.
●       Gestion des relations : La capacité   de gérer les interactions, de fournir des services et de soutenir   l'organisation tout en créant un réseau interne et externe efficace.
●       Leadership et navigation : la   capacité de gérer et de contribuer aux initiatives et processus au sein de   l'organisation tout en progressant vers le changement et l'amélioration   continue.
●       Communication : La capacité   d'échanger efficacement des informations avec les autres, de fournir   efficacement des informations critiques, de recueillir des informations et de   communiquer avec les autres.
●       Abilité globale et culturelle : la   capacité de valoriser et de considérer les perspectives et les antécédents de   toutes les parties et de pouvoir travailler de manière interculturelle.
●       Pratique éthique : La capacité   d'intégrer la vision de Search, la mission et les valeurs fondamentales,   l'intégrité et la responsabilité dans toutes les pratiques organisationnelles   et professionnelles.
●         Évaluation   critique : La capacité d'interpréter les informations pour prendre des   décisions adaptées et des recommandations basées sur une analyse approfondie,   les meilleures pratiques et une compréhension des résultats attendus.
●         Sens des   affaires : La capacité de comprendre et d'appliquer les informations pour   contribuer au plan stratégique de l'organisation.
●         Développer les   autres : La capacité de fournir un soutien pour améliorer les   performances et la croissance professionnelle.
 Engagement envers les valeurs de Search :
 Humanité   partagée - Empathie - Impartialité - Inclusivité - Courage - Espoir -   Humilité - Audace
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Herbert Scoville Jr. Peace Fellowship</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/63368e4a-dcba-4afe-93ae-1d503d69c775</link><description>
Search for Common Ground is a participating organization for The Herbert Scoville Jr. Peace Fellowship. The Herbert Scoville Jr. Peace Fellowship pays a salary for recent college graduates to work with NGOs in Washington, DC, including the Search for Common Ground, on international peace and security issues for six to nine months. Scoville Fellows work on Search's Global Affairs &amp; Partnerships  team. 

For further information, and to apply please visit www.scoville.org. Please do not apply through this this website- please visit the Scoville website to apply directly.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Grant Accountant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/2659ddb7-9c0e-44ff-ae72-a289af1c58e3</link><description>Department Summary The Search for Common Ground Finance Team seeks to achieve excellence in financial management by providing accurate and timely financial information to Search management and programs and by adhering to established financial practices and accounting principles.

Team Summary The AccountingTeam has responsibility for the consolidated financial reporting, cash management, internal controls, and overall accounting operations at Search for Common Ground. The accounting process includes summarizing, analyzing and reporting these transactions to oversight agencies, regulators and tax collection entities; recording accounts, paying invoices, tracking assets and expenditures, managing payroll and keeping track of critical tax documents.
</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 05:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GAP Policy Intern</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/fb33123d-84a5-4597-86f9-33dc95646fd0</link><description>The Global Policy and Outreach team at Search for Common Ground (Search) is seeking an intern to provide research and administrative support to several ongoing policy advocacy initiatives. The Global Policy and Outreach team focuses on building the policy case for the peacebuilding field. It does this by working collaboratively with Search's teams and partners around the world and leveraging their analysis, data, and expertise to inform the policies of emerging and established actors relevant to Search’s work. It provides operational and locally-rooted policy analysis and recommendations that encourage policymakers to support and use peacebuilding more by advocating for more supportive institutional norms and structures, more and healthier funding to implementers, and more policies that encourage peacebuilding. 

Policy interns have the opportunity to contribute to outreach and advocacy on both specific countries/geographies as well as cross-cutting global issues through the responsibilities outlined below.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance Assistant</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/786200c0-ea09-4268-9611-f7918a9ae832</link><description>About Search for Common Ground
Search for Common Ground is an international non profit organization with operations in 30 conflict-affected countries across the globe, and headquarters in the USA and in Belgium. The Belgian entity is an international AISBL with 30 staff based in our Brussels office and 1000 colleagues across the globe, 90% of whom are locals to the places where we implement our peacebuilding work. Search for Common Ground is funded primarily by the European Union, bilateral European Governments (i.e. Belgium, UK, Netherlands, Germany, France, Sweden, etc.).
 
As per our 2018-2028 strategy, Search for Common Ground is entering its expansion phase and is looking at increasingly influencing policy-makers in Belgium, Europe and across the world to make peacebuilding a credible option. In that context, Search for Common Ground was granted (i) a 5-year advocacy project funded by the Belgian Directorate-General Development Cooperation and Humanitarian Aid (DGD) and (ii) several projects funded by the European Union. As part of this expansion and new portfolio, Search for Common Ground is looking to strengthen its finance team based in Brussels and providing support for timely planning, reporting, audit, expense managing, sub-granting relating to these contracts and grants. 

</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 05:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance &amp; Operations Manager</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/6cc7d8d7-13c0-42dd-8be3-669a7ed58192</link><description>The Finance and Operations Manager will ensure the integrity of country office financial management systems, support quality grant management in line with Search and donor policies, and oversees all administration, safety, and security policies, processes, and procedures, streamlining processes for effective day-to-day office management. The Finance and Operations Manager will lead the finance, security, human resources, and operations teams.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 10:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Director, Finance (DRC)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/1bdbd63a-9508-4f84-a9c1-eab37d8ea70f</link><description>Title: Director, Finance
Reports to: Country Director, DRC
Department: Finance
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Design, Monitoring &amp; Evaluation Coordinator</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/fded33c9-d6c8-4b5f-9a10-8da0b07b332f</link><description>The Design, Monitoring, and Evaluation (DM&amp;E) Coordinator will implement a comprehensive monitoring and evaluation system to oversee the successful implementation of Search for Common Ground’s programs across Afghanistan and establish systems to measure program progress and impact. They will liaise daily with different project coordinators to meet their specific DM&amp;E needs. The DME Officer will be primarily responsible for coordinating the research, design, monitoring and evaluation, and organizational learning efforts of Search’s projects in Afghanistan
</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Design Monitoring Evaluation &amp; Learning Specialist</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/63edf68d-0539-401c-8480-2edda86f9d9a</link><description>Team Summary 

Common Ground USA (CG-USA) is Search for Common Ground's most significant investment in supporting a self-sustaining peaceful and inclusive democracy in the United States. Informed by lessons learned as the world's largest and oldest peacebuilding-dedicated organization, CG-USA aims to strengthen collective resilience against political, hate-based, and extremist violence in America, while fostering the conditions for a more inclusive, equitable, and peaceful society. 

Our dynamic and passionate team is currently seeking an experienced Design, Monitoring, Evaluation, and Learning (DMEL) Specialist to provide leadership, technical support, and capacity building on design, monitoring, evaluation, and learning for CG-USA’s programs. They will coach, capacitate, and support the CG-USA team to understand DM&amp;E for peacebuilding, integrate Search’s DM&amp;E protocols to ensure the United States contributes to global targets, and will be accountable to develop knowledge management systems and tools to capture accurate and useful data, set up effective feedback loops, and capture and communicate results to inform effective programming. Furthermore, the DMEL Specialist will contribute to business development processes ensuring quality of program design which integrates lessons learned and evidence collected and alignment with global and conflict geography strategies. The DMEL Specialist will work closely with Search’s in-house Institutional Learning team, to ensure alignment of country programs with global standards, including the Evidence and Learning Protocols and the PeaceImpact Framework (PIF). 
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 17:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Country Program Associate, Jordan</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/a958e4ff-7c16-43f5-a899-3f8a0157a45c</link><description>Position Summary

The Jordan Country Program Associate is a member of the Jordan Country Program team and will support Search’s portfolio in Jordan. The Jordan Country Program Associate works with the country team to support grants management functions, reporting, project related communications and program development, as well as program implementation. The position is also responsible for supervising interns, as needed. The position holder will work closely with MENA team members and other staff based in the region, in Brussels and in Washington D.C. The position reports to the Jordan Country Director.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Country Director - DRC</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/0480d87e-6cea-4547-afa1-6b7bd4c89e49</link><description>Title: Country Director, Democratic Republic of Congo
Reports to: Regional Director, Central and East Africa
Department: Global Programs
Team: Programs Implementation
Location: Goma, DRC

Team Summary
The Program Implementation team has oversight for the implementation of Search’s programs and projects in its country offices, in accordance with Search and donor policies and procedures. The Program Implementation team works on the full life-cycle of the project, from the start-up phase to the full close-out. This involves designing work plans, implementing activities, reporting, financial management, and staffing management  The Program Implementation team collaborates with other departments, including Finance, Institutional Learning, Programs, Global Affairs and Partnerships, Human Resources, and Information Technology

Responsibilities
Oversight for Program Implementation 
Leadership for staffing, operations, and employee development

Contributions
Program Implementation: provide strategic input and guidance on implementation strategies/approaches
Compliance: Enforce processes to ensure internal policy and donor compliance; oversee management of organizational legal issues and compliance
Financial management: Oversee development of country operational budget; ensure accurate forecasts and revenue projections; enforce finance policies and procedures; ensure program-finance team coordination
Reporting: Develop country Quarterly Management Report (QMR); oversee development of country annual report
Personnel management: Supervise Director-level staff including Head Office 
	a. Monitor senior-level team management and address management issues
	b. Develop country staffing plan
	c. Ensure implementation of HR policies and processes
	d. Participate in Executive/Director-level recruitments
External engagement: Lead engagement with international actors and donors in the region
	a. Lead government engagement and relationship building
	b. Represent Search at national and international events
	c. Ensure Search’s reputation remains strong and relevant to position Search as an excellent potential partner
Program management, quality, and project design: Ensure that program portfolio reflects best practices, codified methodologies and embraces reflective practice and adaptive management
	a. Monitor program quality, reflection, and learning initiatives
	b. Advise on areas to improve program quality, reflection, and learning
	c. Amplify outcomes of program quality, reflection, and learning through external engagement
	d. Make go/no-go decisions
	e. Lead identification of unsolicited opportunities
	f. Coordinate input from program teams for new project design and proposal development
	g. Ensure new project budgets support the country office needs
Operations: Lead Senior Management Team (SMT)
	a. Member of the Leadership Management Team (LMT) for conflict geography structure group
	b. Lead strategy development and planning
	c. Lead country Objectives and Key Results (OKR) development
	d. Ensure strategy is supported by operational structures and across functional areas
	e. Ensure projects support strategy implementation
	f. Adapt operations and logistics systems to fit the needs of the country
	g. Ensure systems can support quality program implementation
	h. Ensure safety and security protocols are in place and followed
	i. Initiate development of new safety and security measures
	j. Management of the operational presence of country team
Infuses organizational Values into all work.
Other duties that are broadly in line with the above key contributions as assigned.
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Controller</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/4a8735df-6f2b-4d6c-a680-3abdf81836b1</link><description>Search for Common Ground seeks a Controller to provide leadership and management of its consolidated financial reporting and accounting operations. Reporting to the Vice President of Finance, the Controller oversees the monthly financial closings of the US and Belgium-based affiliate and provides daily supervision of the Corporate Accounting. S/he ensures accounting procedures conform to Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP) and International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS), as well as to company policy and donor regulations surrounding grants and contracts financial management. S/he maintains accounting systems that ensure the proper accounting and recording of organizational resources and respective use provides financial analysis and other key management reports, and assists with budget preparation.  The ideal candidate will have proven experience in financial management in the INGO nonprofit sector, consolidated financial statement preparation, and analysis, accounting system implementation, design, and workflows, as well as vast employee management experience in a multicultural environment.    
</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 20:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consultant Writer</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/3b24cb61-3ab9-4937-bfeb-69d0f4c86d5b</link><description>Search for Common Ground (Search) is seeking a consultant able to provide temporary support through March 2023 to two of its transition countries (Guinea and Tunisia).  The consultant’s main responsibilities will be supporting program development efforts, including leading fundraising on conflict transformation in these countries, and ensuring that quality and innovative concepts and proposals are developed and marketed, in line with Search’s legacy strategy. In addition, the consultant will facilitate the finalization and implementation of actionable fundraising strategies for the new local entities created in each of the transition countries: Talking Drum Studio (TDS) in Guinea and the Ifrikya Center for Common Ground (ICCG) in Tunisia. The consultant may be requested to support additional program support tasks for the transition countries, such as contributing to communications and visibility, capacity statements, country overviews, thematic or strategy documents. 

The consultant will report to the Sr Manager, Program Development Africa and Sr Manager, Program Development MENA/Asia and will work closely with other members of the regional Program Development  teams, as well as with the relevant country teams, in a manner that consistently builds capacity and enables creativity and country program strategies to be funded.  
</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 04:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consultancy:  Project Final Evaluation</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/c84dcdab-2dca-4d41-b5f1-1ed9ef1da5e0</link><description>The Organization:
Search is an international conflict transformation NGO that aims to transform the way individuals, groups, governments, and companies deal with conflict, away from adversarial approaches and towards collaborative solutions. Headquartered in Washington DC, USA, and Brussels, Belgium, with 55 offices in 34 countries, Search designs and implements multifaceted, culturally appropriate, and conflict-sensitive programs using a diverse range of tools, including media and training, to promote dialogue, increase knowledge and determine a positive shift in behaviors. Operating in Sudan since 2009, Search has developed and implemented innovative peacebuilding programs in collaboration with local Sudanese NGOs. Our work in Sudan seeks to empower women and other marginalized groups and encourage greater inclusivity in the peace processes and governance in Sudan. 

The Project:
Search for Common Ground (Search), in partnership with the Sudanese nongovernmental organization Badya Centre for Integrated Development Services (Badya), propose the project “Minatinaa Fi Tamasokona (“Strong in Our Social Cohesion”): Strengthening Nonviolence as a Strategy for Peacebuilding and Promoting Social Cohesion in the Abyei Area”. It is a 4 years project that seeks to advance inclusive collaboration on conflict transformation, human security issues, and socio-economic development between Misseriya and Ngok Dinka communities in the Abyei Administrative Area (AAA).


The Assignment:
Search for Common Ground (Search) is seeking a consultant who can conduct the end-line evaluation of our 14 years project titled: Strengthening Nonviolence as a Strategy for peacebuilding and Promoting Social Cohesion in the Abyei Area.   We are primarily interested in learning how the project contributes to strengthening social cohesion in the Abyei  Administrative Area, by promoting collaborative approaches across dividing lines that result in more effective conflict transformation interventions and a positive impact on the socio-economic well-being of the Misseriya and Ngok Dinka communities.

CLICK HERE FOR THE COMPLETE TERMS OF REFERENCE

</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Consultance - Expert Juridique (Bénin)</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/9d2de03b-0f60-47c5-b981-7ecde6a61d9e</link><description>Résumé de la consultance
Search for Common Ground (Search) recherche un conseiller juridique au Bénin afin de soutenir l’ouverture d’un nouveau programme pays. Il/elle sera notamment chargé(e) d’apporter une expertise juridique et administrative à l’équipe de Search afin de faciliter son enregistrement auprès du gouvernement béninois, de comprendre le droit du travail en vigueur, et fournir des conseils écrits et verbaux sur des questions juridiques au Bénin concernant le fonctionnement d'une organisation internationale à but non lucratif.
 
Search for Common Ground au Sahel 
Search for Common Ground est une organisation internationale à but non lucratif fondée en 1982, qui œuvre pour la transformation pacifique des conflits. Elle a pour mission de transformer la façon dont le monde gère les conflits, en aidant les parties prenantes à trouver des pistes de collaboration autour d’objectifs communs. Search a lancé ses programmes au Sahel, et plus particulièrement au Niger, en 2011, avant de renforcer sa présence dans la région en lançant des programmes au Mali en 2015 puis au Burkina Faso en 2020. Dans le cadre de notre stratégie d’expansion, nous visons désormais à étendre notre présence au Bénin, avec l’ouverture d’un bureau et le déploiement d’une équipe en 2022. 
Cette consultance relèvera du bureau opérationnel du Niger, où Search travaille depuis 2011 à travers des programmes axés sur l'autonomisation et le leadership des jeunes, la prévention des conflits et la stabilisation. Search a son bureau principal à Niamey et trois sous-bureaux à Tillaberi, Tahoua et Diffa avec un personnel de plus de 90 personnes. 

</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 17:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Call for proposals - Community Initiatives</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/edae8077-f6dc-416b-ba46-d750f6656ad6</link><description>About Search
Search for Common Ground (Search) is a world-wide Non-Profit Organisation with the primary objective to change the way the world deals with conflict, away from adversarial approaches towards collaborative solutions. Search has been working in Kenya since 2008, when we launched the award-winning series The Team. Our work has focused on overcoming ethnic, political, social and cultural divides, furthering constructive interaction and healthy relationships between civil society and key government actors, and transforming violent Conflict.
 
About the Project 
Search in partnership with the Human Rights Agenda (HURIA), Muslims for Human Rights (MUHURI), Kiunga Youth Bunge Initiative (KYBI), Ijara Women for Peace and Tana River Peace, Reconciliation, and Development Organisation (TRPRD) implements the 18-month project “Uchaguzi Bila Balaa: Violence Free Elections on Coastal Kenya.” 
 
The project targets Garissa, Lamu, Tana River, Kilifi, Kwale, and Mombasa counties, and has the overall objective to foster collaborative and inclusive community-led prevention of election-related conflicts in Coastal Kenya. The action has two interrelated objectives and corresponding outcomes, as follows:
Strengthen inclusive      multi-stakeholder identification of and response to election-related      violence risks in targeted communities
Mitigate the impact of narratives  contributing to electoral violence in targeted communities
 
 About the Community Initiatives
This project will support locally led community Initiatives to directly address issues and conflict drivers emerging at the local level and contribute to resolving an existing conflict or tension around the elections. 

Objective of the Call for Proposals
This call intends to support CSOs, CBOs, Media houses who will join forces with us in de-escalating tension before, during and after the elections through locally led interventions with two objectives:
1)      Addressing community-based election related risks and conflict drivers at the target counties.
2)      De-escalating tensions and strengthening community resilience to online and offline violence drivers.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Call for Proposal: Monitoring and Evaluation of Advancing Inclusive Peace and Security in the Levant and Yemen</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/186d54c1-fdae-42ac-bf4b-c0fcd3a3fc6d</link><description>Search for Common Ground (Search) is seeking a consultant(s)/firm to develop a holistic approach to monitor and evaluate the project “Advancing Inclusive Peace and Security in the Levant and Yemen (IPS)”. As a learning organisation, Search is committed to fostering a culture of learning across all projects, and is investing in developing and supporting its programmatic learning opportunities. To do this well, Search is seeking one consultant/firm to lead all external studies and set the tools for collection of evidence throughout the life of the project.

1. Context
Search for Common Ground
Search for Common Ground (Search) is an international conflict transformation NGO that aims to transform the way individuals, groups, governments and companies deal with conflict, away from adversarial approaches and towards collaborative solutions. Headquartered in Washington DC, USA, and Brussels, Belgium, with field offices in over 30 countries, Search designs and implements multifaceted, culturally appropriate and conflict-sensitive programs using a diverse range of tools, including media and training, to promote dialogue, increase knowledge and determine a positive shift in behaviours.

The Project
This project is a four-year project aiming to strengthen women and youth’s meaningful, enduring participation in advancing inclusive peace and security in Lebanon, Iraq, Yemen and other areas in the Levant. This will be achieved through (i) consolidating women’s rights organisations (WRO) and youth-led organisations (YLOs’) strategic engagement and influence in municipal and national peace and reconciliation processes; (ii) motivating (sub)national institutions to strengthen inclusive policies and standards facilitating women and youth’s participation in peace and security processes; and (iii) promoting shifts in social norms around women and youth’s meaningful inclusion in peace and security at all levels. Through this multi-pronged and comprehensive approach, IPS will catalyse an enabling environment for diverse women and youth’s increased and enduring participation in peace and security.

Expected results are listed here:
Goal: To strengthen women and youth’s meaningful, enduring participation in advancing inclusive peace and security in Yemen and the Levant.
Specific Objective 1: To consolidate WRO and YLOs’ strategic engagement and influence in municipal and national peace and reconciliation processes in Yemen and the Levant.
Outcome 1.1: Mentorship and strategy-building that foster the collective impact of WRO and YLOs’ peace and reconciliation efforts are strengthened.
Outcome 1.2: Expanded, influential, and diverse networks among WROs and YLOs, including those from historically marginalised groups, are reinforced in each country.

Specific Objective 2: To motivate key sub-national and national institutions to strengthen inclusive policies and standards facilitating inclusive youth and women’s participation in peace and security.
Outcome 2.1: Institutions and key decision-makers relevant to WPS and YPS have increased understanding of tools to conduct intersectional, gender and age-sensitive policymaking.
Outcome 2.2: Institutions and key decision-makers relevant to WPS and YPS have increased ability to mainstream gender and youth inclusion in peace and reconciliation processes.

Specific Objective 3: To promote shifts in social norms in Yemen and the Levant around women and youth’s meaningful inclusion in peace and security at all levels, including stronger alliances with men and boys.
Outcome 3.1: Young women and men are empowered to actively promote and amplify inclusive narratives around peace and security.
Outcome 3.2: Perceptions of target community groups are shifted towards increased support for women and youth’s meaningful enduring inclusion in peace and reconciliation processes.

To sensitise and mobilise influential male allies to promote women and youth’s leadership in peace and security.To advance regional networks, synergies, and cross-fertilization to strengthen inclusive peace and security.
To advance regional networks, synergies, and cross-fertilization to strengthen inclusive peace and security
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 19:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Call for Applications Partnership for Social Media Listening and Analysis</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/08dcfdd0-dd17-4059-8ead-f568e5b84629</link><description>Context
Search for Common Ground (Search) is the world’s largest dedicated peacebuilding organization working to transform the way the world deals with conflict, away from adversarial approaches towards collaborative solutions. For 40 years Search has implemented peacebuilding programs in more than 30 countries across Africa, Asia, the Middle East and in the United States. Teams across the world working for and partnering with Search deploy a wide range of peacebuilding approaches including media, dialogue, and the use of collaborative approaches to transform conflict. 

In line with Search for Common Ground’s strategic direction, we are seeking a strategic partnership which will grow our capability to understand the digital manifestations of conflict through using appropriate social media listening tools. We aim to equip our program and research teams to use social media listening tools effectively to generate insights on the manifestation of conflict online, inform programming (both online and off-line) and measure reach and impact of our digital programs. 

Search is seeking a consultant, company or organization (hereafter the ‘consultant’) that will be the go-to partner for a period up to 36 months, during which an estimated 10-12 teams will work in direct collaboration with the consultant.
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 21:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Associate, Human Resources and Administration</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/57d5fa6c-d9f4-45f6-8676-1e9025b5f45c</link><description>The Administration department supports the staff of Search for Common Ground AISBL particularly for the Brussels office. Members of this team collaborate with Search staff from offices across the world, including with teams from sister organization, Search for Common Ground in the USA. 
</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 17:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Assistant Finance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/ab56b2f4-c476-4132-9a18-431b32f491d1</link><description>Search for Common Ground (Search) est une organisation non-gouvernementale basée à Washington DC et Bruxelles qui œuvre pour la transformation des conflits à l’échelle mondiale. Au cours de ses 40 années d’expérience, l’organisation a développé et consolidé une vision spécifique appelé Approche Common Ground qui s’appuie sur les deux principes suivants: (1) le conflit est inévitable, mais pas la violence; (2) le changement est toujours possible, et il est durable lorsque tout le monde est gagnant. L’action de Search en République Démocratique du Congo s’inscrit dans cette vision globale. Présente depuis 2001 en RDC, Search met en œuvre des programmes qui s’articulent autour des questions liées au dialogue démocratique, à la sensibilité au conflit, au renforcement de la gouvernance, à la protection des civils et à la réforme du secteur de la sécurité, à la lutte contre les violences basées sur le genre, avec toujours une focalisation sur l’engagement des jeunes. S’appuyant sur une large palette d’outils méthodologiques (formation, médiation, mobilisation communautaire, communication à travers les médias et le théâtre participatif) et en étroite collaboration avec les partenaires locaux, la présence de Search est établie à Goma, Bukavu, Kalemie et Kinshasa, ainsi qu’à travers des bureaux satellites, notamment en Ituri. L’ensemble du staff de l’organisation en RDC est d’environ 110 personnes.
 
Search for Common Ground (Search), en partenariat avec Femmes Congolaise pour le Développement (FECONDE), met en œuvre le  projet “Msitu wetu, umilele wetu (Our Forest, Our Future)” qui vise à construire des relations  pacifiques et une propriété partagée dans la réserve de faune à  Okapis,financé par USAID, d’une durée de 36 mois et mis en œuvre dans trois chefferies du territoire de Mambasa : Wales-Karo et Babila-Babombi (dans la zone sanitaire de Mambasa) et Bandaka (dans la zone sanitaire de dans Nia-Nia).
Ce projet s’inscrit dans un contexte conflictuel autour de la réserve de faune à okapis (OWR) par l'exploitation des ressources naturelles, les opérations des groupes armés et les tensions sociales, qui se traduisent par la méfiance et le ressentiment entre les communautés locales et les autorités de la réserve. Des facteurs d’escalade des tensions dans la gestion des ressources naturelles autour et dans la réserve à cause de l’inégalité d'accès aux ressources, une population migrante croissante et des possibilités d'emploi insuffisantes, en particulier pour les jeunes, exacerbent encore les tensions au sein de la réserve.
l'Assistant financier assistera le finance officer lors de l'exécution et du suivi financier de l'ensemble des activités de l'action. Il sera le responsable direct de l'ensemble de la trésorerie de l'action et assurera le suivi financier des différentes transactions financières au quotidien.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Assistance Finance</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/6c907715-4496-4f5c-ae85-589a9498c832</link><description>Search for Common Ground (Search) est une organisation non-gouvernementale basée à Washington DC et Bruxelles qui œuvre pour la transformation des conflits à l’échelle mondiale. Au cours de ses 40 années d’expérience, l’organisation a développé et consolidé une vision spécifique appelé Approche Common Ground qui s’appuie sur les deux principes suivants: (1) le conflit est inévitable, mais pas la violence; (2) le changement est toujours possible, et il est durable lorsque tout le monde est gagnant. L’action de Search en République Démocratique du Congo s’inscrit dans cette vision globale. Présente depuis 2001 en RDC, Search met en œuvre des programmes qui s’articulent autour des questions liées au dialogue démocratique, à la sensibilité au conflit, au renforcement de la gouvernance, à la protection des civils et à la réforme du secteur de la sécurité, à la lutte contre les violences basées sur le genre, avec toujours une focalisation sur l’engagement des jeunes. S’appuyant sur une large palette d’outils méthodologiques (formation, médiation, mobilisation communautaire, communication à travers les médias et le théâtre participatif) et en étroite collaboration avec les partenaires locaux, la présence de Search est établie à Goma, Bukavu, Kalemie et Kinshasa, ainsi qu’à travers des bureaux satellites, notamment en Ituri. L’ensemble du staff de l’organisation en RDC est d’environ 110 personnes.
 
En consortium avec World Vision International, Search met en œuvre le projet de “ Response to Health and Protection needs of CAR refugees and their host communities in North and South Ubangi ”, un projet de durée de 12 mois qui vise entre autre à mproved protection services to respond to protection challenges, including MHPSS, SGBV, and CP dans le Nord et le Sud Ubangi.
 
l'Assistant financier assistera le finance officer lors de l'exécution et du suivi financier de l'ensemble des activités de l'action. Il sera le responsable direct de l'ensemble de la trésorerie de l'action et assurera le suivi financier des différentes transactions financières au quotidien.
</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Administrative and Finance Coordinator</title><link>https://jobs.lever.co/sfcg/f12a7b1e-939f-49f3-9299-c1e904b551f9</link><description>Administrative and Finance Coordinator  will be based in Tashkent and will work under supervision of the Regional Advisor, Uzbekistan Country Director and is an integral member of the country program. S/he will be responsible for the monitoring of expenses versus implemented activities, administrative and financial tasks and compliance with donor requirements.
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 05:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>